[
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 63 . We turned on the cooler for 52 minutes. What is the temperature after 52 minutes?",
        "answer": 57,
        "options": [
            57,
            65,
            69,
            85,
            82
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 57 . We turned on the cooler for 7 minutes. What is the temperature after 7 minutes?",
        "answer": 57,
        "options": [
            57,
            63,
            73,
            62,
            80
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 119 . We turned on the cooler for 14 minutes. What is the temperature after 14 minutes?",
        "answer": 118,
        "options": [
            124,
            118,
            150,
            123,
            125
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 80 . We turned on the cooler for 36 minutes. What is the temperature after 36 minutes?",
        "answer": 66,
        "options": [
            86,
            66,
            81,
            101,
            82
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 78 . We turned on the cooler for 104 minutes. What is the temperature after 104 minutes?",
        "answer": 78,
        "options": [
            78,
            84,
            108,
            84,
            81
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 107 . We turned on the cooler for 29 minutes. What is the temperature after 29 minutes?",
        "answer": 107,
        "options": [
            107,
            109,
            108,
            108,
            122
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 107 . We turned on the cooler for 107 minutes. What is the temperature after 107 minutes?",
        "answer": 102,
        "options": [
            130,
            129,
            111,
            108,
            102
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 116 . We turned on the cooler for 108 minutes. What is the temperature after 108 minutes?",
        "answer": 109,
        "options": [
            131,
            118,
            132,
            119,
            109
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 78 . We turned on the cooler for 119 minutes. What is the temperature after 119 minutes?",
        "answer": 76,
        "options": [
            93,
            98,
            95,
            84,
            76
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 82 . We turned on the cooler for 18 minutes. What is the temperature after 18 minutes?",
        "answer": 72,
        "options": [
            90,
            72,
            83,
            122,
            96
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 101 . We turned on the cooler for 17 minutes. What is the temperature after 17 minutes?",
        "answer": 98,
        "options": [
            131,
            102,
            124,
            98,
            105
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 104 . We turned on the cooler for 120 minutes. What is the temperature after 120 minutes?",
        "answer": 103,
        "options": [
            110,
            105,
            118,
            103,
            138
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 66 . We turned on the cooler for 30 minutes. What is the temperature after 30 minutes?",
        "answer": 66,
        "options": [
            66,
            74,
            76,
            99,
            72
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 64 . We turned on the cooler for 45 minutes. What is the temperature after 45 minutes?",
        "answer": 64,
        "options": [
            67,
            65,
            78,
            64,
            68
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 89 . We turned on the cooler for 74 minutes. What is the temperature after 74 minutes?",
        "answer": 86,
        "options": [
            105,
            100,
            86,
            92,
            101
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 100 . We turned on the cooler for 48 minutes. What is the temperature after 48 minutes?",
        "answer": 99,
        "options": [
            99,
            120,
            102,
            105,
            101
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 82 . We turned on the cooler for 31 minutes. What is the temperature after 31 minutes?",
        "answer": 73,
        "options": [
            110,
            103,
            83,
            73,
            90
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 52 . We turned on the cooler for 24 minutes. What is the temperature after 24 minutes?",
        "answer": 47,
        "options": [
            47,
            58,
            57,
            83,
            57
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 65 . We turned on the cooler for 37 minutes. What is the temperature after 37 minutes?",
        "answer": 57,
        "options": [
            73,
            67,
            57,
            97,
            73
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 72 . We turned on the cooler for 30 minutes. What is the temperature after 30 minutes?",
        "answer": 69,
        "options": [
            69,
            87,
            75,
            78,
            86
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 74 . We turned on the cooler for 80 minutes. What is the temperature after 80 minutes?",
        "answer": 60,
        "options": [
            92,
            79,
            79,
            60,
            84
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 53 . We turned on the cooler for 65 minutes. What is the temperature after 65 minutes?",
        "answer": 43,
        "options": [
            43,
            56,
            72,
            59,
            60
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 112 . We turned on the cooler for 88 minutes. What is the temperature after 88 minutes?",
        "answer": 107,
        "options": [
            115,
            107,
            115,
            115,
            118
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 68 . We turned on the cooler for 48 minutes. What is the temperature after 48 minutes?",
        "answer": 65,
        "options": [
            69,
            65,
            84,
            81,
            77
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 98 . We turned on the cooler for 7 minutes. What is the temperature after 7 minutes?",
        "answer": 98,
        "options": [
            98,
            102,
            103,
            102,
            115
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 75 . We turned on the cooler for 34 minutes. What is the temperature after 34 minutes?",
        "answer": 71,
        "options": [
            71,
            103,
            78,
            103,
            86
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 69 . We turned on the cooler for 112 minutes. What is the temperature after 112 minutes?",
        "answer": 65,
        "options": [
            82,
            72,
            65,
            89,
            75
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 64 . We turned on the cooler for 68 minutes. What is the temperature after 68 minutes?",
        "answer": 63,
        "options": [
            83,
            68,
            70,
            63,
            65
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 61 . We turned on the cooler for 108 minutes. What is the temperature after 108 minutes?",
        "answer": 50,
        "options": [
            50,
            77,
            78,
            88,
            64
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 105 . We turned on the cooler for 43 minutes. What is the temperature after 43 minutes?",
        "answer": 94,
        "options": [
            108,
            110,
            120,
            108,
            94
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 118 . We turned on the cooler for 78 minutes. What is the temperature after 78 minutes?",
        "answer": 116,
        "options": [
            123,
            124,
            122,
            116,
            135
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 74 . We turned on the cooler for 27 minutes. What is the temperature after 27 minutes?",
        "answer": 74,
        "options": [
            81,
            83,
            74,
            102,
            77
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 77 . We turned on the cooler for 79 minutes. What is the temperature after 79 minutes?",
        "answer": 75,
        "options": [
            75,
            97,
            96,
            99,
            94
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 65 . We turned on the cooler for 8 minutes. What is the temperature after 8 minutes?",
        "answer": 58,
        "options": [
            77,
            67,
            58,
            76,
            77
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 53 . We turned on the cooler for 103 minutes. What is the temperature after 103 minutes?",
        "answer": 40,
        "options": [
            40,
            90,
            59,
            61,
            67
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 71 . We turned on the cooler for 66 minutes. What is the temperature after 66 minutes?",
        "answer": 67,
        "options": [
            96,
            67,
            79,
            73,
            79
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 60 . We turned on the cooler for 53 minutes. What is the temperature after 53 minutes?",
        "answer": 60,
        "options": [
            60,
            74,
            66,
            64,
            82
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 117 . We turned on the cooler for 100 minutes. What is the temperature after 100 minutes?",
        "answer": 113,
        "options": [
            125,
            127,
            141,
            113,
            150
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 94 . We turned on the cooler for 62 minutes. What is the temperature after 62 minutes?",
        "answer": 92,
        "options": [
            105,
            112,
            101,
            92,
            107
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 117 . We turned on the cooler for 55 minutes. What is the temperature after 55 minutes?",
        "answer": 117,
        "options": [
            121,
            137,
            117,
            150,
            122
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 53 . We turned on the cooler for 61 minutes. What is the temperature after 61 minutes?",
        "answer": 46,
        "options": [
            60,
            59,
            66,
            56,
            46
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 104 . We turned on the cooler for 109 minutes. What is the temperature after 109 minutes?",
        "answer": 103,
        "options": [
            110,
            103,
            107,
            105,
            111
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 121 . We turned on the cooler for 47 minutes. What is the temperature after 47 minutes?",
        "answer": 113,
        "options": [
            143,
            139,
            125,
            113,
            152
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 57 . We turned on the cooler for 54 minutes. What is the temperature after 54 minutes?",
        "answer": 50,
        "options": [
            68,
            94,
            71,
            64,
            50
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 111 . We turned on the cooler for 85 minutes. What is the temperature after 85 minutes?",
        "answer": 108,
        "options": [
            118,
            112,
            114,
            113,
            108
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 116 . We turned on the cooler for 71 minutes. What is the temperature after 71 minutes?",
        "answer": 115,
        "options": [
            115,
            148,
            119,
            120,
            119
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 97 . We turned on the cooler for 115 minutes. What is the temperature after 115 minutes?",
        "answer": 95,
        "options": [
            95,
            104,
            116,
            102,
            119
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 78 . We turned on the cooler for 114 minutes. What is the temperature after 114 minutes?",
        "answer": 77,
        "options": [
            92,
            91,
            87,
            80,
            77
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 75 . We turned on the cooler for 110 minutes. What is the temperature after 110 minutes?",
        "answer": 73,
        "options": [
            89,
            88,
            93,
            73,
            77
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 67 . We turned on the cooler for 20 minutes. What is the temperature after 20 minutes?",
        "answer": 66,
        "options": [
            73,
            81,
            66,
            70,
            69
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 77 . We turned on the cooler for 104 minutes. What is the temperature after 104 minutes?",
        "answer": 68,
        "options": [
            86,
            80,
            68,
            78,
            80
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 120 . We turned on the cooler for 91 minutes. What is the temperature after 91 minutes?",
        "answer": 120,
        "options": [
            148,
            125,
            143,
            120,
            122
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 90 . We turned on the cooler for 31 minutes. What is the temperature after 31 minutes?",
        "answer": 81,
        "options": [
            100,
            81,
            92,
            101,
            111
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 83 . We turned on the cooler for 66 minutes. What is the temperature after 66 minutes?",
        "answer": 79,
        "options": [
            98,
            86,
            90,
            106,
            79
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 88 . We turned on the cooler for 101 minutes. What is the temperature after 101 minutes?",
        "answer": 87,
        "options": [
            90,
            97,
            87,
            92,
            97
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 89 . We turned on the cooler for 112 minutes. What is the temperature after 112 minutes?",
        "answer": 87,
        "options": [
            96,
            91,
            87,
            100,
            109
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 66 . We turned on the cooler for 6 minutes. What is the temperature after 6 minutes?",
        "answer": 60,
        "options": [
            86,
            60,
            70,
            83,
            80
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 105 . We turned on the cooler for 45 minutes. What is the temperature after 45 minutes?",
        "answer": 105,
        "options": [
            115,
            123,
            130,
            105,
            121
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 65 . We turned on the cooler for 74 minutes. What is the temperature after 74 minutes?",
        "answer": 65,
        "options": [
            81,
            65,
            66,
            68,
            67
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 74 . We turned on the cooler for 108 minutes. What is the temperature after 108 minutes?",
        "answer": 68,
        "options": [
            104,
            85,
            80,
            68,
            90
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 113 . We turned on the cooler for 72 minutes. What is the temperature after 72 minutes?",
        "answer": 111,
        "options": [
            125,
            114,
            111,
            114,
            132
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 65 . We turned on the cooler for 58 minutes. What is the temperature after 58 minutes?",
        "answer": 65,
        "options": [
            72,
            69,
            67,
            65,
            78
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 104 . We turned on the cooler for 98 minutes. What is the temperature after 98 minutes?",
        "answer": 98,
        "options": [
            116,
            98,
            110,
            107,
            115
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 101 . We turned on the cooler for 97 minutes. What is the temperature after 97 minutes?",
        "answer": 88,
        "options": [
            88,
            107,
            114,
            102,
            103
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 59 . We turned on the cooler for 116 minutes. What is the temperature after 116 minutes?",
        "answer": 54,
        "options": [
            54,
            66,
            65,
            67,
            66
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 78 . We turned on the cooler for 112 minutes. What is the temperature after 112 minutes?",
        "answer": 77,
        "options": [
            77,
            81,
            81,
            79,
            80
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 60 . We turned on the cooler for 41 minutes. What is the temperature after 41 minutes?",
        "answer": 57,
        "options": [
            79,
            68,
            67,
            57,
            67
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 71 . We turned on the cooler for 21 minutes. What is the temperature after 21 minutes?",
        "answer": 66,
        "options": [
            75,
            84,
            73,
            75,
            66
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 110 . We turned on the cooler for 114 minutes. What is the temperature after 114 minutes?",
        "answer": 105,
        "options": [
            127,
            105,
            132,
            135,
            111
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 109 . We turned on the cooler for 38 minutes. What is the temperature after 38 minutes?",
        "answer": 97,
        "options": [
            129,
            120,
            114,
            110,
            97
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 107 . We turned on the cooler for 19 minutes. What is the temperature after 19 minutes?",
        "answer": 96,
        "options": [
            120,
            96,
            110,
            127,
            112
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 103 . We turned on the cooler for 90 minutes. What is the temperature after 90 minutes?",
        "answer": 88,
        "options": [
            107,
            104,
            105,
            88,
            139
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 102 . We turned on the cooler for 44 minutes. What is the temperature after 44 minutes?",
        "answer": 98,
        "options": [
            108,
            110,
            115,
            98,
            128
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 115 . We turned on the cooler for 13 minutes. What is the temperature after 13 minutes?",
        "answer": 103,
        "options": [
            139,
            116,
            147,
            123,
            103
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 84 . We turned on the cooler for 16 minutes. What is the temperature after 16 minutes?",
        "answer": 82,
        "options": [
            100,
            86,
            82,
            105,
            98
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 70 . We turned on the cooler for 104 minutes. What is the temperature after 104 minutes?",
        "answer": 66,
        "options": [
            78,
            75,
            66,
            75,
            74
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 103 . We turned on the cooler for 111 minutes. What is the temperature after 111 minutes?",
        "answer": 97,
        "options": [
            106,
            106,
            97,
            137,
            122
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 66 . We turned on the cooler for 13 minutes. What is the temperature after 13 minutes?",
        "answer": 57,
        "options": [
            70,
            80,
            57,
            71,
            79
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 89 . We turned on the cooler for 68 minutes. What is the temperature after 68 minutes?",
        "answer": 86,
        "options": [
            90,
            91,
            91,
            95,
            86
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 75 . We turned on the cooler for 94 minutes. What is the temperature after 94 minutes?",
        "answer": 70,
        "options": [
            88,
            76,
            86,
            70,
            86
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 74 . We turned on the cooler for 71 minutes. What is the temperature after 71 minutes?",
        "answer": 56,
        "options": [
            81,
            75,
            77,
            102,
            56
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 108 . We turned on the cooler for 38 minutes. What is the temperature after 38 minutes?",
        "answer": 90,
        "options": [
            124,
            90,
            128,
            115,
            111
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 85 . We turned on the cooler for 105 minutes. What is the temperature after 105 minutes?",
        "answer": 84,
        "options": [
            88,
            89,
            93,
            105,
            84
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 66 . We turned on the cooler for 81 minutes. What is the temperature after 81 minutes?",
        "answer": 65,
        "options": [
            65,
            73,
            94,
            89,
            68
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 87 . We turned on the cooler for 82 minutes. What is the temperature after 82 minutes?",
        "answer": 77,
        "options": [
            88,
            77,
            118,
            105,
            96
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 73 . We turned on the cooler for 10 minutes. What is the temperature after 10 minutes?",
        "answer": 66,
        "options": [
            98,
            66,
            78,
            96,
            78
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 95 . We turned on the cooler for 64 minutes. What is the temperature after 64 minutes?",
        "answer": 94,
        "options": [
            94,
            103,
            100,
            111,
            100
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 54 . We turned on the cooler for 71 minutes. What is the temperature after 71 minutes?",
        "answer": 48,
        "options": [
            57,
            48,
            76,
            71,
            58
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 120 . We turned on the cooler for 14 minutes. What is the temperature after 14 minutes?",
        "answer": 118,
        "options": [
            121,
            123,
            118,
            123,
            133
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 108 . We turned on the cooler for 96 minutes. What is the temperature after 96 minutes?",
        "answer": 108,
        "options": [
            123,
            108,
            112,
            119,
            136
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 53 . We turned on the cooler for 46 minutes. What is the temperature after 46 minutes?",
        "answer": 50,
        "options": [
            50,
            57,
            64,
            67,
            64
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 75 . We turned on the cooler for 45 minutes. What is the temperature after 45 minutes?",
        "answer": 71,
        "options": [
            85,
            94,
            71,
            84,
            77
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 91 . We turned on the cooler for 13 minutes. What is the temperature after 13 minutes?",
        "answer": 89,
        "options": [
            95,
            107,
            120,
            89,
            96
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 63 . We turned on the cooler for 50 minutes. What is the temperature after 50 minutes?",
        "answer": 58,
        "options": [
            75,
            64,
            73,
            58,
            101
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 96 . We turned on the cooler for 103 minutes. What is the temperature after 103 minutes?",
        "answer": 85,
        "options": [
            116,
            85,
            106,
            117,
            103
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 50 . We turned on the cooler for 82 minutes. What is the temperature after 82 minutes?",
        "answer": 48,
        "options": [
            60,
            48,
            66,
            59,
            90
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 53 . We turned on the cooler for 31 minutes. What is the temperature after 31 minutes?",
        "answer": 45,
        "options": [
            57,
            66,
            45,
            54,
            76
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 78 . We turned on the cooler for 104 minutes. What is the temperature after 104 minutes?",
        "answer": 76,
        "options": [
            83,
            79,
            95,
            76,
            105
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 119 . We turned on the cooler for 100 minutes. What is the temperature after 100 minutes?",
        "answer": 111,
        "options": [
            120,
            152,
            121,
            124,
            111
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 94 . We turned on the cooler for 109 minutes. What is the temperature after 109 minutes?",
        "answer": 92,
        "options": [
            107,
            115,
            92,
            111,
            110
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 115 . We turned on the cooler for 113 minutes. What is the temperature after 113 minutes?",
        "answer": 112,
        "options": [
            136,
            121,
            112,
            133,
            119
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 116 . We turned on the cooler for 93 minutes. What is the temperature after 93 minutes?",
        "answer": 113,
        "options": [
            119,
            135,
            125,
            121,
            113
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 109 . We turned on the cooler for 8 minutes. What is the temperature after 8 minutes?",
        "answer": 104,
        "options": [
            142,
            119,
            104,
            133,
            117
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 96 . We turned on the cooler for 9 minutes. What is the temperature after 9 minutes?",
        "answer": 96,
        "options": [
            98,
            96,
            104,
            118,
            122
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 54 . We turned on the cooler for 110 minutes. What is the temperature after 110 minutes?",
        "answer": 53,
        "options": [
            59,
            70,
            53,
            63,
            63
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 87 . We turned on the cooler for 62 minutes. What is the temperature after 62 minutes?",
        "answer": 86,
        "options": [
            93,
            103,
            86,
            90,
            105
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 64 . We turned on the cooler for 114 minutes. What is the temperature after 114 minutes?",
        "answer": 54,
        "options": [
            66,
            84,
            54,
            94,
            69
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 114 . We turned on the cooler for 116 minutes. What is the temperature after 116 minutes?",
        "answer": 113,
        "options": [
            124,
            120,
            115,
            113,
            118
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 91 . We turned on the cooler for 41 minutes. What is the temperature after 41 minutes?",
        "answer": 86,
        "options": [
            86,
            94,
            95,
            93,
            106
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 110 . We turned on the cooler for 111 minutes. What is the temperature after 111 minutes?",
        "answer": 103,
        "options": [
            111,
            117,
            119,
            118,
            103
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 80 . We turned on the cooler for 72 minutes. What is the temperature after 72 minutes?",
        "answer": 79,
        "options": [
            92,
            89,
            82,
            79,
            81
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 71 . We turned on the cooler for 46 minutes. What is the temperature after 46 minutes?",
        "answer": 53,
        "options": [
            93,
            74,
            72,
            53,
            77
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 66 . We turned on the cooler for 28 minutes. What is the temperature after 28 minutes?",
        "answer": 52,
        "options": [
            75,
            75,
            84,
            52,
            86
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 78 . We turned on the cooler for 71 minutes. What is the temperature after 71 minutes?",
        "answer": 67,
        "options": [
            67,
            108,
            88,
            92,
            87
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 85 . We turned on the cooler for 26 minutes. What is the temperature after 26 minutes?",
        "answer": 85,
        "options": [
            85,
            88,
            86,
            87,
            91
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 53 . We turned on the cooler for 28 minutes. What is the temperature after 28 minutes?",
        "answer": 49,
        "options": [
            73,
            71,
            70,
            64,
            49
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 73 . We turned on the cooler for 106 minutes. What is the temperature after 106 minutes?",
        "answer": 73,
        "options": [
            88,
            84,
            103,
            73,
            104
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 64 . We turned on the cooler for 99 minutes. What is the temperature after 99 minutes?",
        "answer": 64,
        "options": [
            78,
            64,
            67,
            71,
            97
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 88 . We turned on the cooler for 28 minutes. What is the temperature after 28 minutes?",
        "answer": 87,
        "options": [
            99,
            87,
            111,
            93,
            109
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 99 . We turned on the cooler for 15 minutes. What is the temperature after 15 minutes?",
        "answer": 97,
        "options": [
            97,
            103,
            100,
            107,
            101
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 100 . We turned on the cooler for 15 minutes. What is the temperature after 15 minutes?",
        "answer": 100,
        "options": [
            103,
            108,
            102,
            100,
            103
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 71 . We turned on the cooler for 10 minutes. What is the temperature after 10 minutes?",
        "answer": 60,
        "options": [
            60,
            73,
            80,
            96,
            75
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 53 . We turned on the cooler for 66 minutes. What is the temperature after 66 minutes?",
        "answer": 49,
        "options": [
            83,
            85,
            69,
            49,
            65
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 97 . We turned on the cooler for 43 minutes. What is the temperature after 43 minutes?",
        "answer": 88,
        "options": [
            99,
            112,
            88,
            101,
            99
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 119 . We turned on the cooler for 28 minutes. What is the temperature after 28 minutes?",
        "answer": 108,
        "options": [
            108,
            152,
            138,
            152,
            120
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 72 . We turned on the cooler for 58 minutes. What is the temperature after 58 minutes?",
        "answer": 66,
        "options": [
            81,
            66,
            83,
            74,
            75
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 114 . We turned on the cooler for 37 minutes. What is the temperature after 37 minutes?",
        "answer": 103,
        "options": [
            125,
            118,
            103,
            124,
            124
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 64 . We turned on the cooler for 16 minutes. What is the temperature after 16 minutes?",
        "answer": 58,
        "options": [
            66,
            67,
            76,
            58,
            78
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 85 . We turned on the cooler for 76 minutes. What is the temperature after 76 minutes?",
        "answer": 82,
        "options": [
            101,
            114,
            82,
            90,
            91
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 107 . We turned on the cooler for 117 minutes. What is the temperature after 117 minutes?",
        "answer": 99,
        "options": [
            119,
            118,
            108,
            111,
            99
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 94 . We turned on the cooler for 19 minutes. What is the temperature after 19 minutes?",
        "answer": 93,
        "options": [
            102,
            93,
            122,
            116,
            105
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 81 . We turned on the cooler for 5 minutes. What is the temperature after 5 minutes?",
        "answer": 71,
        "options": [
            82,
            95,
            71,
            98,
            86
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 65 . We turned on the cooler for 101 minutes. What is the temperature after 101 minutes?",
        "answer": 59,
        "options": [
            67,
            86,
            99,
            59,
            66
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 84 . We turned on the cooler for 120 minutes. What is the temperature after 120 minutes?",
        "answer": 78,
        "options": [
            88,
            114,
            78,
            85,
            87
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 84 . We turned on the cooler for 58 minutes. What is the temperature after 58 minutes?",
        "answer": 79,
        "options": [
            85,
            85,
            79,
            87,
            99
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 62 . We turned on the cooler for 48 minutes. What is the temperature after 48 minutes?",
        "answer": 50,
        "options": [
            73,
            69,
            66,
            50,
            72
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 90 . We turned on the cooler for 32 minutes. What is the temperature after 32 minutes?",
        "answer": 90,
        "options": [
            104,
            94,
            90,
            98,
            98
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 120 . We turned on the cooler for 18 minutes. What is the temperature after 18 minutes?",
        "answer": 118,
        "options": [
            118,
            139,
            148,
            128,
            124
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 86 . We turned on the cooler for 46 minutes. What is the temperature after 46 minutes?",
        "answer": 78,
        "options": [
            89,
            99,
            111,
            102,
            78
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 57 . We turned on the cooler for 27 minutes. What is the temperature after 27 minutes?",
        "answer": 51,
        "options": [
            80,
            51,
            70,
            65,
            58
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 105 . We turned on the cooler for 60 minutes. What is the temperature after 60 minutes?",
        "answer": 104,
        "options": [
            118,
            104,
            126,
            106,
            106
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 89 . We turned on the cooler for 117 minutes. What is the temperature after 117 minutes?",
        "answer": 86,
        "options": [
            98,
            86,
            95,
            99,
            102
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 50 . We turned on the cooler for 115 minutes. What is the temperature after 115 minutes?",
        "answer": 49,
        "options": [
            54,
            49,
            52,
            53,
            67
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 57 . We turned on the cooler for 109 minutes. What is the temperature after 109 minutes?",
        "answer": 43,
        "options": [
            43,
            70,
            93,
            60,
            58
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 69 . We turned on the cooler for 32 minutes. What is the temperature after 32 minutes?",
        "answer": 64,
        "options": [
            75,
            84,
            71,
            75,
            64
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 114 . We turned on the cooler for 119 minutes. What is the temperature after 119 minutes?",
        "answer": 114,
        "options": [
            124,
            118,
            116,
            114,
            120
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 78 . We turned on the cooler for 73 minutes. What is the temperature after 73 minutes?",
        "answer": 76,
        "options": [
            113,
            102,
            76,
            80,
            92
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 62 . We turned on the cooler for 67 minutes. What is the temperature after 67 minutes?",
        "answer": 58,
        "options": [
            71,
            68,
            58,
            88,
            79
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 70 . We turned on the cooler for 48 minutes. What is the temperature after 48 minutes?",
        "answer": 65,
        "options": [
            72,
            88,
            98,
            65,
            71
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 98 . We turned on the cooler for 32 minutes. What is the temperature after 32 minutes?",
        "answer": 96,
        "options": [
            111,
            96,
            118,
            112,
            122
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 81 . We turned on the cooler for 8 minutes. What is the temperature after 8 minutes?",
        "answer": 71,
        "options": [
            115,
            84,
            71,
            88,
            85
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 77 . We turned on the cooler for 67 minutes. What is the temperature after 67 minutes?",
        "answer": 75,
        "options": [
            93,
            83,
            75,
            85,
            107
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 111 . We turned on the cooler for 110 minutes. What is the temperature after 110 minutes?",
        "answer": 95,
        "options": [
            129,
            119,
            124,
            131,
            95
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 51 . We turned on the cooler for 77 minutes. What is the temperature after 77 minutes?",
        "answer": 51,
        "options": [
            52,
            59,
            52,
            55,
            51
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 50 . We turned on the cooler for 98 minutes. What is the temperature after 98 minutes?",
        "answer": 42,
        "options": [
            42,
            52,
            55,
            53,
            65
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 83 . We turned on the cooler for 100 minutes. What is the temperature after 100 minutes?",
        "answer": 83,
        "options": [
            87,
            88,
            85,
            84,
            83
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 119 . We turned on the cooler for 7 minutes. What is the temperature after 7 minutes?",
        "answer": 117,
        "options": [
            121,
            117,
            129,
            140,
            120
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 59 . We turned on the cooler for 42 minutes. What is the temperature after 42 minutes?",
        "answer": 55,
        "options": [
            81,
            61,
            60,
            55,
            72
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 89 . We turned on the cooler for 51 minutes. What is the temperature after 51 minutes?",
        "answer": 88,
        "options": [
            92,
            88,
            99,
            90,
            96
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 103 . We turned on the cooler for 54 minutes. What is the temperature after 54 minutes?",
        "answer": 98,
        "options": [
            106,
            124,
            98,
            111,
            104
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 121 . We turned on the cooler for 103 minutes. What is the temperature after 103 minutes?",
        "answer": 102,
        "options": [
            125,
            134,
            142,
            102,
            125
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 91 . We turned on the cooler for 50 minutes. What is the temperature after 50 minutes?",
        "answer": 85,
        "options": [
            104,
            96,
            85,
            94,
            103
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 67 . We turned on the cooler for 72 minutes. What is the temperature after 72 minutes?",
        "answer": 55,
        "options": [
            55,
            94,
            79,
            80,
            84
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 53 . We turned on the cooler for 22 minutes. What is the temperature after 22 minutes?",
        "answer": 51,
        "options": [
            67,
            76,
            51,
            56,
            58
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 85 . We turned on the cooler for 86 minutes. What is the temperature after 86 minutes?",
        "answer": 84,
        "options": [
            105,
            92,
            120,
            84,
            87
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 83 . We turned on the cooler for 111 minutes. What is the temperature after 111 minutes?",
        "answer": 78,
        "options": [
            104,
            101,
            78,
            91,
            97
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 68 . We turned on the cooler for 85 minutes. What is the temperature after 85 minutes?",
        "answer": 61,
        "options": [
            97,
            61,
            69,
            79,
            96
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 121 . We turned on the cooler for 6 minutes. What is the temperature after 6 minutes?",
        "answer": 120,
        "options": [
            126,
            122,
            120,
            124,
            130
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 107 . We turned on the cooler for 15 minutes. What is the temperature after 15 minutes?",
        "answer": 105,
        "options": [
            121,
            122,
            117,
            108,
            105
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 116 . We turned on the cooler for 76 minutes. What is the temperature after 76 minutes?",
        "answer": 113,
        "options": [
            119,
            128,
            124,
            113,
            131
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 105 . We turned on the cooler for 19 minutes. What is the temperature after 19 minutes?",
        "answer": 94,
        "options": [
            109,
            110,
            94,
            109,
            108
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 117 . We turned on the cooler for 9 minutes. What is the temperature after 9 minutes?",
        "answer": 106,
        "options": [
            120,
            136,
            150,
            121,
            106
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 74 . We turned on the cooler for 31 minutes. What is the temperature after 31 minutes?",
        "answer": 66,
        "options": [
            108,
            75,
            78,
            66,
            88
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 108 . We turned on the cooler for 99 minutes. What is the temperature after 99 minutes?",
        "answer": 106,
        "options": [
            119,
            106,
            136,
            130,
            120
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 107 . We turned on the cooler for 117 minutes. What is the temperature after 117 minutes?",
        "answer": 106,
        "options": [
            106,
            108,
            123,
            112,
            108
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 66 . We turned on the cooler for 95 minutes. What is the temperature after 95 minutes?",
        "answer": 62,
        "options": [
            90,
            62,
            76,
            69,
            91
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 105 . We turned on the cooler for 12 minutes. What is the temperature after 12 minutes?",
        "answer": 103,
        "options": [
            103,
            112,
            107,
            107,
            133
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 113 . We turned on the cooler for 81 minutes. What is the temperature after 81 minutes?",
        "answer": 104,
        "options": [
            134,
            115,
            115,
            104,
            126
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 106 . We turned on the cooler for 104 minutes. What is the temperature after 104 minutes?",
        "answer": 103,
        "options": [
            108,
            126,
            103,
            125,
            109
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 94 . We turned on the cooler for 116 minutes. What is the temperature after 116 minutes?",
        "answer": 93,
        "options": [
            93,
            112,
            95,
            98,
            99
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 98 . We turned on the cooler for 93 minutes. What is the temperature after 93 minutes?",
        "answer": 88,
        "options": [
            122,
            88,
            102,
            118,
            100
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 84 . We turned on the cooler for 84 minutes. What is the temperature after 84 minutes?",
        "answer": 72,
        "options": [
            97,
            101,
            107,
            86,
            72
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 98 . We turned on the cooler for 43 minutes. What is the temperature after 43 minutes?",
        "answer": 96,
        "options": [
            105,
            96,
            112,
            105,
            119
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 110 . We turned on the cooler for 109 minutes. What is the temperature after 109 minutes?",
        "answer": 103,
        "options": [
            144,
            115,
            125,
            119,
            103
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 58 . We turned on the cooler for 28 minutes. What is the temperature after 28 minutes?",
        "answer": 46,
        "options": [
            70,
            63,
            67,
            46,
            63
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 105 . We turned on the cooler for 99 minutes. What is the temperature after 99 minutes?",
        "answer": 101,
        "options": [
            116,
            101,
            110,
            110,
            112
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 80 . We turned on the cooler for 99 minutes. What is the temperature after 99 minutes?",
        "answer": 80,
        "options": [
            83,
            83,
            98,
            80,
            89
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 77 . We turned on the cooler for 7 minutes. What is the temperature after 7 minutes?",
        "answer": 76,
        "options": [
            82,
            81,
            87,
            95,
            76
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 81 . We turned on the cooler for 12 minutes. What is the temperature after 12 minutes?",
        "answer": 75,
        "options": [
            84,
            89,
            82,
            85,
            75
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 80 . We turned on the cooler for 46 minutes. What is the temperature after 46 minutes?",
        "answer": 76,
        "options": [
            76,
            92,
            98,
            102,
            85
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 94 . We turned on the cooler for 116 minutes. What is the temperature after 116 minutes?",
        "answer": 91,
        "options": [
            130,
            104,
            91,
            123,
            109
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 104 . We turned on the cooler for 26 minutes. What is the temperature after 26 minutes?",
        "answer": 104,
        "options": [
            111,
            122,
            106,
            111,
            104
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 96 . We turned on the cooler for 64 minutes. What is the temperature after 64 minutes?",
        "answer": 95,
        "options": [
            99,
            117,
            95,
            104,
            99
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 73 . We turned on the cooler for 23 minutes. What is the temperature after 23 minutes?",
        "answer": 71,
        "options": [
            71,
            75,
            84,
            106,
            82
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 72 . We turned on the cooler for 110 minutes. What is the temperature after 110 minutes?",
        "answer": 72,
        "options": [
            100,
            76,
            72,
            93,
            73
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 65 . We turned on the cooler for 109 minutes. What is the temperature after 109 minutes?",
        "answer": 62,
        "options": [
            97,
            75,
            76,
            62,
            75
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 100 . We turned on the cooler for 11 minutes. What is the temperature after 11 minutes?",
        "answer": 96,
        "options": [
            121,
            106,
            105,
            103,
            96
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 77 . We turned on the cooler for 8 minutes. What is the temperature after 8 minutes?",
        "answer": 62,
        "options": [
            79,
            85,
            91,
            62,
            86
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 97 . We turned on the cooler for 115 minutes. What is the temperature after 115 minutes?",
        "answer": 86,
        "options": [
            113,
            121,
            103,
            100,
            86
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 115 . We turned on the cooler for 20 minutes. What is the temperature after 20 minutes?",
        "answer": 105,
        "options": [
            105,
            129,
            118,
            118,
            130
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 94 . We turned on the cooler for 10 minutes. What is the temperature after 10 minutes?",
        "answer": 82,
        "options": [
            107,
            82,
            130,
            112,
            99
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 113 . We turned on the cooler for 82 minutes. What is the temperature after 82 minutes?",
        "answer": 108,
        "options": [
            128,
            108,
            117,
            128,
            117
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 114 . We turned on the cooler for 10 minutes. What is the temperature after 10 minutes?",
        "answer": 111,
        "options": [
            111,
            117,
            118,
            119,
            133
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 56 . We turned on the cooler for 109 minutes. What is the temperature after 109 minutes?",
        "answer": 43,
        "options": [
            68,
            60,
            82,
            70,
            43
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 86 . We turned on the cooler for 58 minutes. What is the temperature after 58 minutes?",
        "answer": 81,
        "options": [
            102,
            91,
            81,
            97,
            90
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 121 . We turned on the cooler for 29 minutes. What is the temperature after 29 minutes?",
        "answer": 120,
        "options": [
            141,
            134,
            125,
            131,
            120
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 65 . We turned on the cooler for 105 minutes. What is the temperature after 105 minutes?",
        "answer": 63,
        "options": [
            66,
            67,
            63,
            89,
            96
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 103 . We turned on the cooler for 13 minutes. What is the temperature after 13 minutes?",
        "answer": 97,
        "options": [
            97,
            104,
            104,
            108,
            107
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 99 . We turned on the cooler for 105 minutes. What is the temperature after 105 minutes?",
        "answer": 99,
        "options": [
            104,
            101,
            121,
            99,
            118
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 111 . We turned on the cooler for 58 minutes. What is the temperature after 58 minutes?",
        "answer": 111,
        "options": [
            111,
            113,
            115,
            134,
            112
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 68 . We turned on the cooler for 112 minutes. What is the temperature after 112 minutes?",
        "answer": 63,
        "options": [
            95,
            77,
            98,
            77,
            63
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 78 . We turned on the cooler for 107 minutes. What is the temperature after 107 minutes?",
        "answer": 70,
        "options": [
            80,
            91,
            89,
            70,
            99
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 105 . We turned on the cooler for 85 minutes. What is the temperature after 85 minutes?",
        "answer": 95,
        "options": [
            110,
            114,
            95,
            113,
            114
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 108 . We turned on the cooler for 64 minutes. What is the temperature after 64 minutes?",
        "answer": 106,
        "options": [
            110,
            106,
            139,
            109,
            144
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 112 . We turned on the cooler for 106 minutes. What is the temperature after 106 minutes?",
        "answer": 102,
        "options": [
            113,
            124,
            128,
            113,
            102
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 115 . We turned on the cooler for 6 minutes. What is the temperature after 6 minutes?",
        "answer": 98,
        "options": [
            117,
            116,
            116,
            98,
            140
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 53 . We turned on the cooler for 81 minutes. What is the temperature after 81 minutes?",
        "answer": 52,
        "options": [
            68,
            54,
            65,
            73,
            52
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 114 . We turned on the cooler for 66 minutes. What is the temperature after 66 minutes?",
        "answer": 105,
        "options": [
            153,
            105,
            128,
            116,
            136
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 80 . We turned on the cooler for 34 minutes. What is the temperature after 34 minutes?",
        "answer": 77,
        "options": [
            82,
            95,
            77,
            90,
            81
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 58 . We turned on the cooler for 120 minutes. What is the temperature after 120 minutes?",
        "answer": 39,
        "options": [
            89,
            39,
            62,
            75,
            59
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 65 . We turned on the cooler for 16 minutes. What is the temperature after 16 minutes?",
        "answer": 56,
        "options": [
            56,
            81,
            67,
            94,
            101
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 78 . We turned on the cooler for 24 minutes. What is the temperature after 24 minutes?",
        "answer": 74,
        "options": [
            93,
            94,
            82,
            82,
            74
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 88 . We turned on the cooler for 100 minutes. What is the temperature after 100 minutes?",
        "answer": 85,
        "options": [
            90,
            92,
            98,
            91,
            85
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 119 . We turned on the cooler for 119 minutes. What is the temperature after 119 minutes?",
        "answer": 104,
        "options": [
            127,
            122,
            144,
            142,
            104
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 53 . We turned on the cooler for 60 minutes. What is the temperature after 60 minutes?",
        "answer": 51,
        "options": [
            56,
            51,
            64,
            56,
            72
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 77 . We turned on the cooler for 25 minutes. What is the temperature after 25 minutes?",
        "answer": 74,
        "options": [
            101,
            78,
            84,
            74,
            90
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 84 . We turned on the cooler for 91 minutes. What is the temperature after 91 minutes?",
        "answer": 79,
        "options": [
            113,
            86,
            79,
            89,
            108
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 74 . We turned on the cooler for 80 minutes. What is the temperature after 80 minutes?",
        "answer": 68,
        "options": [
            76,
            79,
            87,
            68,
            78
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 56 . We turned on the cooler for 103 minutes. What is the temperature after 103 minutes?",
        "answer": 40,
        "options": [
            58,
            40,
            65,
            60,
            61
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 75 . We turned on the cooler for 48 minutes. What is the temperature after 48 minutes?",
        "answer": 73,
        "options": [
            73,
            80,
            98,
            82,
            86
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 76 . We turned on the cooler for 112 minutes. What is the temperature after 112 minutes?",
        "answer": 76,
        "options": [
            82,
            76,
            87,
            80,
            89
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 100 . We turned on the cooler for 94 minutes. What is the temperature after 94 minutes?",
        "answer": 100,
        "options": [
            106,
            103,
            106,
            100,
            111
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 108 . We turned on the cooler for 22 minutes. What is the temperature after 22 minutes?",
        "answer": 105,
        "options": [
            109,
            122,
            128,
            105,
            118
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 115 . We turned on the cooler for 12 minutes. What is the temperature after 12 minutes?",
        "answer": 113,
        "options": [
            116,
            123,
            125,
            125,
            113
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 114 . We turned on the cooler for 35 minutes. What is the temperature after 35 minutes?",
        "answer": 105,
        "options": [
            123,
            120,
            116,
            122,
            105
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 94 . We turned on the cooler for 52 minutes. What is the temperature after 52 minutes?",
        "answer": 87,
        "options": [
            113,
            97,
            117,
            87,
            132
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 59 . We turned on the cooler for 47 minutes. What is the temperature after 47 minutes?",
        "answer": 59,
        "options": [
            91,
            65,
            73,
            59,
            61
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 90 . We turned on the cooler for 21 minutes. What is the temperature after 21 minutes?",
        "answer": 89,
        "options": [
            94,
            104,
            121,
            89,
            106
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 107 . We turned on the cooler for 118 minutes. What is the temperature after 118 minutes?",
        "answer": 106,
        "options": [
            109,
            106,
            108,
            111,
            111
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 106 . We turned on the cooler for 33 minutes. What is the temperature after 33 minutes?",
        "answer": 94,
        "options": [
            126,
            118,
            113,
            94,
            109
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 93 . We turned on the cooler for 57 minutes. What is the temperature after 57 minutes?",
        "answer": 93,
        "options": [
            114,
            97,
            93,
            112,
            114
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 102 . We turned on the cooler for 81 minutes. What is the temperature after 81 minutes?",
        "answer": 97,
        "options": [
            97,
            105,
            103,
            125,
            106
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 100 . We turned on the cooler for 85 minutes. What is the temperature after 85 minutes?",
        "answer": 92,
        "options": [
            122,
            123,
            92,
            106,
            103
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 51 . We turned on the cooler for 77 minutes. What is the temperature after 77 minutes?",
        "answer": 45,
        "options": [
            76,
            45,
            53,
            68,
            55
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 62 . We turned on the cooler for 19 minutes. What is the temperature after 19 minutes?",
        "answer": 62,
        "options": [
            62,
            63,
            72,
            66,
            65
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 80 . We turned on the cooler for 11 minutes. What is the temperature after 11 minutes?",
        "answer": 73,
        "options": [
            82,
            84,
            97,
            104,
            73
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 94 . We turned on the cooler for 118 minutes. What is the temperature after 118 minutes?",
        "answer": 92,
        "options": [
            92,
            105,
            96,
            122,
            114
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 107 . We turned on the cooler for 90 minutes. What is the temperature after 90 minutes?",
        "answer": 101,
        "options": [
            114,
            132,
            127,
            101,
            113
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 60 . We turned on the cooler for 45 minutes. What is the temperature after 45 minutes?",
        "answer": 59,
        "options": [
            76,
            59,
            61,
            92,
            87
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 98 . We turned on the cooler for 95 minutes. What is the temperature after 95 minutes?",
        "answer": 94,
        "options": [
            117,
            94,
            101,
            117,
            103
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 70 . We turned on the heater for 49 minutes. What is the temperature after 49 minutes?",
        "answer": 78,
        "options": [
            48,
            78,
            62,
            56,
            66
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 0 . We turned on the heater for 42 minutes. What is the temperature after 42 minutes?",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            1,
            -12,
            -9,
            -18,
            -2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 12 . We turned on the heater for 114 minutes. What is the temperature after 114 minutes?",
        "answer": 16,
        "options": [
            -1,
            16,
            4,
            7,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 65 . We turned on the heater for 75 minutes. What is the temperature after 75 minutes?",
        "answer": 68,
        "options": [
            29,
            68,
            53,
            51,
            54
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 0 . We turned on the heater for 54 minutes. What is the temperature after 54 minutes?",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            1,
            -16,
            -2,
            -1,
            -2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 9 . We turned on the heater for 113 minutes. What is the temperature after 113 minutes?",
        "answer": 18,
        "options": [
            18,
            -22,
            -3,
            2,
            -1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 43 . We turned on the heater for 25 minutes. What is the temperature after 25 minutes?",
        "answer": 47,
        "options": [
            47,
            33,
            36,
            41,
            30
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 0 . We turned on the heater for 82 minutes. What is the temperature after 82 minutes?",
        "answer": 16,
        "options": [
            -3,
            16,
            -1,
            -3,
            -1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 18 . We turned on the heater for 119 minutes. What is the temperature after 119 minutes?",
        "answer": 22,
        "options": [
            9,
            22,
            5,
            6,
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 25 . We turned on the heater for 54 minutes. What is the temperature after 54 minutes?",
        "answer": 32,
        "options": [
            3,
            32,
            -7,
            22,
            14
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 67 . We turned on the heater for 52 minutes. What is the temperature after 52 minutes?",
        "answer": 75,
        "options": [
            41,
            75,
            42,
            32,
            65
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 9 . We turned on the heater for 39 minutes. What is the temperature after 39 minutes?",
        "answer": 11,
        "options": [
            7,
            -8,
            -4,
            -1,
            11
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 1 . We turned on the heater for 13 minutes. What is the temperature after 13 minutes?",
        "answer": 13,
        "options": [
            -13,
            13,
            -4,
            -5,
            -5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 65 . We turned on the heater for 58 minutes. What is the temperature after 58 minutes?",
        "answer": 69,
        "options": [
            69,
            55,
            29,
            55,
            63
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 50 . We turned on the heater for 79 minutes. What is the temperature after 79 minutes?",
        "answer": 54,
        "options": [
            54,
            49,
            41,
            38,
            45
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 21 . We turned on the heater for 16 minutes. What is the temperature after 16 minutes?",
        "answer": 22,
        "options": [
            22,
            20,
            14,
            15,
            20
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 21 . We turned on the heater for 35 minutes. What is the temperature after 35 minutes?",
        "answer": 32,
        "options": [
            8,
            20,
            20,
            18,
            32
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 16 . We turned on the heater for 47 minutes. What is the temperature after 47 minutes?",
        "answer": 26,
        "options": [
            15,
            26,
            -22,
            15,
            14
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 3 . We turned on the heater for 98 minutes. What is the temperature after 98 minutes?",
        "answer": 7,
        "options": [
            7,
            -7,
            -21,
            0,
            -21
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 66 . We turned on the heater for 115 minutes. What is the temperature after 115 minutes?",
        "answer": 70,
        "options": [
            57,
            65,
            54,
            63,
            70
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 57 . We turned on the heater for 48 minutes. What is the temperature after 48 minutes?",
        "answer": 63,
        "options": [
            53,
            47,
            56,
            54,
            63
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 24 . We turned on the heater for 116 minutes. What is the temperature after 116 minutes?",
        "answer": 33,
        "options": [
            33,
            18,
            -6,
            17,
            19
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 41 . We turned on the heater for 36 minutes. What is the temperature after 36 minutes?",
        "answer": 42,
        "options": [
            42,
            38,
            33,
            21,
            37
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 59 . We turned on the heater for 6 minutes. What is the temperature after 6 minutes?",
        "answer": 62,
        "options": [
            62,
            52,
            57,
            43,
            52
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 70 . We turned on the heater for 108 minutes. What is the temperature after 108 minutes?",
        "answer": 75,
        "options": [
            75,
            63,
            62,
            52,
            53
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 60 . We turned on the heater for 115 minutes. What is the temperature after 115 minutes?",
        "answer": 67,
        "options": [
            59,
            32,
            67,
            27,
            53
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 68 . We turned on the heater for 36 minutes. What is the temperature after 36 minutes?",
        "answer": 77,
        "options": [
            55,
            77,
            65,
            67,
            55
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 16 . We turned on the heater for 90 minutes. What is the temperature after 90 minutes?",
        "answer": 19,
        "options": [
            -2,
            -15,
            9,
            15,
            19
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 69 . We turned on the heater for 26 minutes. What is the temperature after 26 minutes?",
        "answer": 75,
        "options": [
            55,
            65,
            75,
            38,
            55
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 50 . We turned on the heater for 7 minutes. What is the temperature after 7 minutes?",
        "answer": 59,
        "options": [
            59,
            31,
            35,
            40,
            33
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 8 . We turned on the heater for 59 minutes. What is the temperature after 59 minutes?",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            4,
            -10,
            9,
            -8,
            -4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 47 . We turned on the heater for 11 minutes. What is the temperature after 11 minutes?",
        "answer": 56,
        "options": [
            32,
            45,
            39,
            56,
            40
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 14 . We turned on the heater for 40 minutes. What is the temperature after 40 minutes?",
        "answer": 19,
        "options": [
            11,
            -11,
            -20,
            19,
            13
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 8 . We turned on the heater for 95 minutes. What is the temperature after 95 minutes?",
        "answer": 16,
        "options": [
            7,
            -1,
            6,
            2,
            16
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 36 . We turned on the heater for 9 minutes. What is the temperature after 9 minutes?",
        "answer": 45,
        "options": [
            45,
            16,
            15,
            14,
            21
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 41 . We turned on the heater for 100 minutes. What is the temperature after 100 minutes?",
        "answer": 45,
        "options": [
            45,
            21,
            12,
            40,
            31
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 36 . We turned on the heater for 58 minutes. What is the temperature after 58 minutes?",
        "answer": 48,
        "options": [
            48,
            35,
            35,
            20,
            27
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 19 . We turned on the heater for 92 minutes. What is the temperature after 92 minutes?",
        "answer": 25,
        "options": [
            -16,
            3,
            25,
            16,
            17
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 66 . We turned on the heater for 17 minutes. What is the temperature after 17 minutes?",
        "answer": 70,
        "options": [
            61,
            52,
            70,
            45,
            57
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 54 . We turned on the heater for 23 minutes. What is the temperature after 23 minutes?",
        "answer": 55,
        "options": [
            25,
            49,
            41,
            26,
            55
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 27 . We turned on the heater for 68 minutes. What is the temperature after 68 minutes?",
        "answer": 32,
        "options": [
            22,
            26,
            23,
            22,
            32
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 54 . We turned on the heater for 101 minutes. What is the temperature after 101 minutes?",
        "answer": 63,
        "options": [
            30,
            24,
            63,
            34,
            51
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 14 . We turned on the heater for 99 minutes. What is the temperature after 99 minutes?",
        "answer": 19,
        "options": [
            19,
            13,
            -14,
            -24,
            -16
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 15 . We turned on the heater for 99 minutes. What is the temperature after 99 minutes?",
        "answer": 20,
        "options": [
            -18,
            1,
            14,
            20,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 37 . We turned on the heater for 62 minutes. What is the temperature after 62 minutes?",
        "answer": 40,
        "options": [
            36,
            15,
            18,
            40,
            26
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 19 . We turned on the heater for 8 minutes. What is the temperature after 8 minutes?",
        "answer": 38,
        "options": [
            38,
            7,
            0,
            17,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 2 . We turned on the heater for 58 minutes. What is the temperature after 58 minutes?",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            6,
            -2,
            -26,
            -7,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 9 . We turned on the heater for 33 minutes. What is the temperature after 33 minutes?",
        "answer": 18,
        "options": [
            2,
            4,
            18,
            -3,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 41 . We turned on the heater for 91 minutes. What is the temperature after 91 minutes?",
        "answer": 48,
        "options": [
            28,
            36,
            48,
            27,
            31
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 41 . We turned on the heater for 97 minutes. What is the temperature after 97 minutes?",
        "answer": 44,
        "options": [
            37,
            44,
            40,
            38,
            35
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 0 . We turned on the heater for 103 minutes. What is the temperature after 103 minutes?",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            -13,
            -4,
            6,
            -13,
            -15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 44 . We turned on the heater for 56 minutes. What is the temperature after 56 minutes?",
        "answer": 59,
        "options": [
            28,
            43,
            40,
            59,
            38
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 43 . We turned on the heater for 46 minutes. What is the temperature after 46 minutes?",
        "answer": 58,
        "options": [
            40,
            40,
            42,
            25,
            58
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 21 . We turned on the heater for 66 minutes. What is the temperature after 66 minutes?",
        "answer": 27,
        "options": [
            0,
            16,
            18,
            27,
            20
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 9 . We turned on the heater for 95 minutes. What is the temperature after 95 minutes?",
        "answer": 27,
        "options": [
            1,
            -4,
            7,
            27,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 26 . We turned on the heater for 105 minutes. What is the temperature after 105 minutes?",
        "answer": 29,
        "options": [
            23,
            25,
            18,
            29,
            23
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 18 . We turned on the heater for 23 minutes. What is the temperature after 23 minutes?",
        "answer": 19,
        "options": [
            19,
            13,
            -8,
            17,
            14
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 44 . We turned on the heater for 56 minutes. What is the temperature after 56 minutes?",
        "answer": 48,
        "options": [
            48,
            27,
            29,
            32,
            23
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 22 . We turned on the heater for 88 minutes. What is the temperature after 88 minutes?",
        "answer": 24,
        "options": [
            16,
            11,
            2,
            24,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 47 . We turned on the heater for 40 minutes. What is the temperature after 40 minutes?",
        "answer": 48,
        "options": [
            30,
            37,
            37,
            23,
            48
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 61 . We turned on the heater for 86 minutes. What is the temperature after 86 minutes?",
        "answer": 62,
        "options": [
            60,
            31,
            56,
            58,
            62
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 46 . We turned on the heater for 36 minutes. What is the temperature after 36 minutes?",
        "answer": 49,
        "options": [
            32,
            49,
            45,
            33,
            22
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 0 . We turned on the heater for 88 minutes. What is the temperature after 88 minutes?",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            1,
            -1,
            -15,
            -10,
            -19
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 9 . We turned on the heater for 60 minutes. What is the temperature after 60 minutes?",
        "answer": 15,
        "options": [
            -14,
            4,
            15,
            8,
            -5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 42 . We turned on the heater for 119 minutes. What is the temperature after 119 minutes?",
        "answer": 46,
        "options": [
            9,
            46,
            40,
            39,
            40
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 37 . We turned on the heater for 48 minutes. What is the temperature after 48 minutes?",
        "answer": 39,
        "options": [
            26,
            35,
            9,
            35,
            39
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 10 . We turned on the heater for 82 minutes. What is the temperature after 82 minutes?",
        "answer": 16,
        "options": [
            9,
            0,
            -12,
            16,
            -10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 8 . We turned on the heater for 61 minutes. What is the temperature after 61 minutes?",
        "answer": 23,
        "options": [
            23,
            7,
            3,
            5,
            -2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 68 . We turned on the heater for 65 minutes. What is the temperature after 65 minutes?",
        "answer": 73,
        "options": [
            36,
            63,
            31,
            58,
            73
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 12 . We turned on the heater for 66 minutes. What is the temperature after 66 minutes?",
        "answer": 20,
        "options": [
            20,
            4,
            -16,
            -10,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 26 . We turned on the heater for 68 minutes. What is the temperature after 68 minutes?",
        "answer": 41,
        "options": [
            18,
            12,
            19,
            41,
            13
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 64 . We turned on the heater for 48 minutes. What is the temperature after 48 minutes?",
        "answer": 66,
        "options": [
            34,
            35,
            56,
            66,
            52
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 33 . We turned on the heater for 88 minutes. What is the temperature after 88 minutes?",
        "answer": 37,
        "options": [
            28,
            24,
            37,
            24,
            25
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 61 . We turned on the heater for 55 minutes. What is the temperature after 55 minutes?",
        "answer": 70,
        "options": [
            49,
            40,
            53,
            70,
            57
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 28 . We turned on the heater for 82 minutes. What is the temperature after 82 minutes?",
        "answer": 29,
        "options": [
            26,
            19,
            17,
            29,
            27
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 15 . We turned on the heater for 47 minutes. What is the temperature after 47 minutes?",
        "answer": 23,
        "options": [
            -2,
            23,
            4,
            14,
            14
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 6 . We turned on the heater for 15 minutes. What is the temperature after 15 minutes?",
        "answer": 7,
        "options": [
            7,
            -2,
            -3,
            -5,
            -14
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 40 . We turned on the heater for 25 minutes. What is the temperature after 25 minutes?",
        "answer": 44,
        "options": [
            44,
            32,
            24,
            37,
            39
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 59 . We turned on the heater for 84 minutes. What is the temperature after 84 minutes?",
        "answer": 62,
        "options": [
            29,
            62,
            44,
            55,
            45
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 36 . We turned on the heater for 62 minutes. What is the temperature after 62 minutes?",
        "answer": 45,
        "options": [
            34,
            28,
            45,
            19,
            26
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 16 . We turned on the heater for 120 minutes. What is the temperature after 120 minutes?",
        "answer": 20,
        "options": [
            20,
            14,
            1,
            15,
            12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 5 . We turned on the heater for 40 minutes. What is the temperature after 40 minutes?",
        "answer": 18,
        "options": [
            0,
            -20,
            -18,
            -6,
            18
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 63 . We turned on the heater for 12 minutes. What is the temperature after 12 minutes?",
        "answer": 65,
        "options": [
            61,
            62,
            65,
            55,
            57
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 64 . We turned on the heater for 49 minutes. What is the temperature after 49 minutes?",
        "answer": 68,
        "options": [
            51,
            50,
            58,
            68,
            43
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 18 . We turned on the heater for 98 minutes. What is the temperature after 98 minutes?",
        "answer": 21,
        "options": [
            21,
            15,
            15,
            13,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 11 . We turned on the heater for 93 minutes. What is the temperature after 93 minutes?",
        "answer": 25,
        "options": [
            -7,
            -4,
            7,
            -4,
            25
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 37 . We turned on the heater for 82 minutes. What is the temperature after 82 minutes?",
        "answer": 38,
        "options": [
            33,
            20,
            35,
            38,
            25
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 19 . We turned on the heater for 22 minutes. What is the temperature after 22 minutes?",
        "answer": 24,
        "options": [
            14,
            24,
            12,
            -8,
            14
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 64 . We turned on the heater for 56 minutes. What is the temperature after 56 minutes?",
        "answer": 69,
        "options": [
            43,
            59,
            69,
            56,
            52
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 38 . We turned on the heater for 92 minutes. What is the temperature after 92 minutes?",
        "answer": 51,
        "options": [
            22,
            15,
            15,
            51,
            34
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 13 . We turned on the heater for 65 minutes. What is the temperature after 65 minutes?",
        "answer": 32,
        "options": [
            32,
            -10,
            9,
            5,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 6 . We turned on the heater for 48 minutes. What is the temperature after 48 minutes?",
        "answer": 16,
        "options": [
            16,
            -18,
            -6,
            3,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 37 . We turned on the heater for 33 minutes. What is the temperature after 33 minutes?",
        "answer": 43,
        "options": [
            43,
            36,
            31,
            18,
            27
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 37 . We turned on the heater for 41 minutes. What is the temperature after 41 minutes?",
        "answer": 39,
        "options": [
            19,
            23,
            35,
            32,
            39
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 60 . We turned on the heater for 56 minutes. What is the temperature after 56 minutes?",
        "answer": 73,
        "options": [
            73,
            59,
            56,
            55,
            58
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 16 . We turned on the heater for 76 minutes. What is the temperature after 76 minutes?",
        "answer": 21,
        "options": [
            15,
            13,
            15,
            11,
            21
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 40 . We turned on the heater for 114 minutes. What is the temperature after 114 minutes?",
        "answer": 45,
        "options": [
            36,
            33,
            45,
            25,
            15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 69 . We turned on the heater for 24 minutes. What is the temperature after 24 minutes?",
        "answer": 74,
        "options": [
            65,
            74,
            49,
            55,
            63
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 46 . We turned on the heater for 55 minutes. What is the temperature after 55 minutes?",
        "answer": 48,
        "options": [
            34,
            45,
            43,
            32,
            48
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 7 . We turned on the heater for 119 minutes. What is the temperature after 119 minutes?",
        "answer": 12,
        "options": [
            0,
            -7,
            12,
            3,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 60 . We turned on the heater for 61 minutes. What is the temperature after 61 minutes?",
        "answer": 61,
        "options": [
            55,
            45,
            46,
            61,
            55
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 39 . We turned on the heater for 80 minutes. What is the temperature after 80 minutes?",
        "answer": 54,
        "options": [
            33,
            54,
            38,
            37,
            38
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 16 . We turned on the heater for 82 minutes. What is the temperature after 82 minutes?",
        "answer": 20,
        "options": [
            -5,
            14,
            20,
            5,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 17 . We turned on the heater for 22 minutes. What is the temperature after 22 minutes?",
        "answer": 18,
        "options": [
            -10,
            16,
            9,
            4,
            18
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 16 . We turned on the heater for 13 minutes. What is the temperature after 13 minutes?",
        "answer": 22,
        "options": [
            -6,
            -5,
            22,
            5,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 3 . We turned on the heater for 85 minutes. What is the temperature after 85 minutes?",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            2,
            2,
            -6,
            6,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 62 . We turned on the heater for 42 minutes. What is the temperature after 42 minutes?",
        "answer": 64,
        "options": [
            54,
            60,
            41,
            48,
            64
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 19 . We turned on the heater for 63 minutes. What is the temperature after 63 minutes?",
        "answer": 24,
        "options": [
            4,
            1,
            4,
            24,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 6 . We turned on the heater for 68 minutes. What is the temperature after 68 minutes?",
        "answer": 7,
        "options": [
            -1,
            -5,
            -11,
            5,
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 6 . We turned on the heater for 75 minutes. What is the temperature after 75 minutes?",
        "answer": 8,
        "options": [
            2,
            3,
            8,
            -4,
            -9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 17 . We turned on the heater for 8 minutes. What is the temperature after 8 minutes?",
        "answer": 22,
        "options": [
            14,
            22,
            6,
            13,
            15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 61 . We turned on the heater for 100 minutes. What is the temperature after 100 minutes?",
        "answer": 63,
        "options": [
            55,
            63,
            44,
            46,
            60
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 27 . We turned on the heater for 95 minutes. What is the temperature after 95 minutes?",
        "answer": 35,
        "options": [
            22,
            17,
            35,
            24,
            21
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 62 . We turned on the heater for 45 minutes. What is the temperature after 45 minutes?",
        "answer": 65,
        "options": [
            54,
            60,
            51,
            42,
            65
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 37 . We turned on the heater for 41 minutes. What is the temperature after 41 minutes?",
        "answer": 44,
        "options": [
            13,
            44,
            16,
            26,
            33
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 4 . We turned on the heater for 10 minutes. What is the temperature after 10 minutes?",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            -4,
            -7,
            -5,
            3,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 26 . We turned on the heater for 95 minutes. What is the temperature after 95 minutes?",
        "answer": 27,
        "options": [
            0,
            9,
            27,
            23,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 29 . We turned on the heater for 85 minutes. What is the temperature after 85 minutes?",
        "answer": 32,
        "options": [
            25,
            24,
            25,
            32,
            28
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 56 . We turned on the heater for 106 minutes. What is the temperature after 106 minutes?",
        "answer": 59,
        "options": [
            59,
            39,
            44,
            55,
            40
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 23 . We turned on the heater for 29 minutes. What is the temperature after 29 minutes?",
        "answer": 24,
        "options": [
            8,
            24,
            13,
            4,
            13
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 42 . We turned on the heater for 102 minutes. What is the temperature after 102 minutes?",
        "answer": 49,
        "options": [
            31,
            30,
            37,
            33,
            49
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 57 . We turned on the heater for 23 minutes. What is the temperature after 23 minutes?",
        "answer": 60,
        "options": [
            45,
            44,
            60,
            37,
            53
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 49 . We turned on the heater for 115 minutes. What is the temperature after 115 minutes?",
        "answer": 51,
        "options": [
            48,
            51,
            35,
            48,
            48
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 54 . We turned on the heater for 119 minutes. What is the temperature after 119 minutes?",
        "answer": 55,
        "options": [
            52,
            51,
            51,
            55,
            27
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 32 . We turned on the heater for 45 minutes. What is the temperature after 45 minutes?",
        "answer": 35,
        "options": [
            18,
            30,
            35,
            15,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 13 . We turned on the heater for 34 minutes. What is the temperature after 34 minutes?",
        "answer": 24,
        "options": [
            -3,
            -2,
            7,
            24,
            -3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 27 . We turned on the heater for 44 minutes. What is the temperature after 44 minutes?",
        "answer": 40,
        "options": [
            40,
            26,
            23,
            25,
            24
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 24 . We turned on the heater for 83 minutes. What is the temperature after 83 minutes?",
        "answer": 26,
        "options": [
            6,
            26,
            5,
            17,
            23
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 40 . We turned on the heater for 66 minutes. What is the temperature after 66 minutes?",
        "answer": 46,
        "options": [
            12,
            26,
            18,
            10,
            46
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 54 . We turned on the heater for 116 minutes. What is the temperature after 116 minutes?",
        "answer": 58,
        "options": [
            32,
            52,
            58,
            50,
            52
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 69 . We turned on the heater for 70 minutes. What is the temperature after 70 minutes?",
        "answer": 78,
        "options": [
            40,
            34,
            46,
            44,
            78
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 5 . We turned on the heater for 72 minutes. What is the temperature after 72 minutes?",
        "answer": 25,
        "options": [
            3,
            0,
            25,
            2,
            -7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 25 . We turned on the heater for 20 minutes. What is the temperature after 20 minutes?",
        "answer": 27,
        "options": [
            12,
            6,
            15,
            20,
            27
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 69 . We turned on the heater for 25 minutes. What is the temperature after 25 minutes?",
        "answer": 77,
        "options": [
            48,
            41,
            77,
            64,
            61
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 45 . We turned on the heater for 34 minutes. What is the temperature after 34 minutes?",
        "answer": 49,
        "options": [
            49,
            28,
            44,
            43,
            19
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 52 . We turned on the heater for 15 minutes. What is the temperature after 15 minutes?",
        "answer": 55,
        "options": [
            13,
            55,
            49,
            27,
            44
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 7 . We turned on the heater for 74 minutes. What is the temperature after 74 minutes?",
        "answer": 11,
        "options": [
            -5,
            5,
            6,
            11,
            -9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 27 . We turned on the heater for 84 minutes. What is the temperature after 84 minutes?",
        "answer": 37,
        "options": [
            21,
            37,
            19,
            20,
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 12 . We turned on the heater for 8 minutes. What is the temperature after 8 minutes?",
        "answer": 15,
        "options": [
            -5,
            15,
            -14,
            -6,
            -11
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 8 . We turned on the heater for 84 minutes. What is the temperature after 84 minutes?",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            10,
            -8,
            3,
            7,
            -8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 18 . We turned on the heater for 117 minutes. What is the temperature after 117 minutes?",
        "answer": 22,
        "options": [
            7,
            2,
            -16,
            5,
            22
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 8 . We turned on the heater for 9 minutes. What is the temperature after 9 minutes?",
        "answer": 19,
        "options": [
            19,
            -31,
            3,
            -23,
            -11
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 31 . We turned on the heater for 10 minutes. What is the temperature after 10 minutes?",
        "answer": 40,
        "options": [
            17,
            29,
            40,
            29,
            29
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 39 . We turned on the heater for 35 minutes. What is the temperature after 35 minutes?",
        "answer": 41,
        "options": [
            36,
            33,
            30,
            41,
            27
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 53 . We turned on the heater for 23 minutes. What is the temperature after 23 minutes?",
        "answer": 58,
        "options": [
            48,
            49,
            15,
            58,
            23
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 63 . We turned on the heater for 21 minutes. What is the temperature after 21 minutes?",
        "answer": 71,
        "options": [
            58,
            60,
            37,
            61,
            71
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 62 . We turned on the heater for 82 minutes. What is the temperature after 82 minutes?",
        "answer": 77,
        "options": [
            45,
            54,
            41,
            77,
            61
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 58 . We turned on the heater for 27 minutes. What is the temperature after 27 minutes?",
        "answer": 65,
        "options": [
            57,
            65,
            44,
            57,
            54
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 62 . We turned on the heater for 38 minutes. What is the temperature after 38 minutes?",
        "answer": 68,
        "options": [
            68,
            50,
            60,
            37,
            58
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 35 . We turned on the heater for 84 minutes. What is the temperature after 84 minutes?",
        "answer": 42,
        "options": [
            22,
            34,
            34,
            42,
            23
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 61 . We turned on the heater for 34 minutes. What is the temperature after 34 minutes?",
        "answer": 71,
        "options": [
            49,
            60,
            47,
            29,
            71
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 28 . We turned on the heater for 23 minutes. What is the temperature after 23 minutes?",
        "answer": 31,
        "options": [
            31,
            23,
            12,
            27,
            27
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 38 . We turned on the heater for 31 minutes. What is the temperature after 31 minutes?",
        "answer": 39,
        "options": [
            32,
            37,
            16,
            39,
            23
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 40 . We turned on the heater for 95 minutes. What is the temperature after 95 minutes?",
        "answer": 47,
        "options": [
            30,
            31,
            26,
            47,
            39
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 20 . We turned on the heater for 52 minutes. What is the temperature after 52 minutes?",
        "answer": 26,
        "options": [
            10,
            2,
            9,
            26,
            -6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 41 . We turned on the heater for 88 minutes. What is the temperature after 88 minutes?",
        "answer": 44,
        "options": [
            29,
            24,
            44,
            40,
            33
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 12 . We turned on the heater for 110 minutes. What is the temperature after 110 minutes?",
        "answer": 13,
        "options": [
            10,
            5,
            13,
            -2,
            -9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 35 . We turned on the heater for 84 minutes. What is the temperature after 84 minutes?",
        "answer": 40,
        "options": [
            32,
            19,
            8,
            40,
            22
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 36 . We turned on the heater for 93 minutes. What is the temperature after 93 minutes?",
        "answer": 45,
        "options": [
            32,
            30,
            5,
            35,
            45
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 21 . We turned on the heater for 92 minutes. What is the temperature after 92 minutes?",
        "answer": 33,
        "options": [
            33,
            -2,
            17,
            9,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 41 . We turned on the heater for 58 minutes. What is the temperature after 58 minutes?",
        "answer": 44,
        "options": [
            38,
            25,
            44,
            23,
            39
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 7 . We turned on the heater for 13 minutes. What is the temperature after 13 minutes?",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            5,
            1,
            -10,
            -5,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 43 . We turned on the heater for 110 minutes. What is the temperature after 110 minutes?",
        "answer": 50,
        "options": [
            42,
            42,
            36,
            50,
            40
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 60 . We turned on the heater for 94 minutes. What is the temperature after 94 minutes?",
        "answer": 70,
        "options": [
            70,
            54,
            53,
            49,
            40
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 2 . We turned on the heater for 12 minutes. What is the temperature after 12 minutes?",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            0,
            -13,
            1,
            3,
            -18
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 68 . We turned on the heater for 29 minutes. What is the temperature after 29 minutes?",
        "answer": 71,
        "options": [
            44,
            61,
            56,
            43,
            71
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 59 . We turned on the heater for 26 minutes. What is the temperature after 26 minutes?",
        "answer": 61,
        "options": [
            61,
            35,
            56,
            38,
            44
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 32 . We turned on the heater for 38 minutes. What is the temperature after 38 minutes?",
        "answer": 43,
        "options": [
            18,
            4,
            6,
            29,
            43
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 48 . We turned on the heater for 66 minutes. What is the temperature after 66 minutes?",
        "answer": 51,
        "options": [
            45,
            37,
            51,
            39,
            38
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 56 . We turned on the heater for 86 minutes. What is the temperature after 86 minutes?",
        "answer": 59,
        "options": [
            30,
            51,
            48,
            43,
            59
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 43 . We turned on the heater for 61 minutes. What is the temperature after 61 minutes?",
        "answer": 48,
        "options": [
            36,
            21,
            41,
            32,
            48
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 55 . We turned on the heater for 75 minutes. What is the temperature after 75 minutes?",
        "answer": 60,
        "options": [
            44,
            49,
            30,
            45,
            60
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 69 . We turned on the heater for 85 minutes. What is the temperature after 85 minutes?",
        "answer": 75,
        "options": [
            62,
            75,
            47,
            58,
            47
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 41 . We turned on the heater for 114 minutes. What is the temperature after 114 minutes?",
        "answer": 47,
        "options": [
            39,
            47,
            40,
            31,
            37
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 9 . We turned on the heater for 32 minutes. What is the temperature after 32 minutes?",
        "answer": 15,
        "options": [
            15,
            1,
            5,
            -7,
            -29
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 43 . We turned on the heater for 42 minutes. What is the temperature after 42 minutes?",
        "answer": 48,
        "options": [
            38,
            48,
            19,
            40,
            16
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 49 . We turned on the heater for 83 minutes. What is the temperature after 83 minutes?",
        "answer": 53,
        "options": [
            46,
            48,
            42,
            45,
            53
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 6 . We turned on the heater for 56 minutes. What is the temperature after 56 minutes?",
        "answer": 8,
        "options": [
            2,
            -10,
            8,
            -8,
            -1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 28 . We turned on the heater for 25 minutes. What is the temperature after 25 minutes?",
        "answer": 42,
        "options": [
            18,
            42,
            25,
            13,
            24
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 26 . We turned on the heater for 9 minutes. What is the temperature after 9 minutes?",
        "answer": 35,
        "options": [
            16,
            24,
            22,
            9,
            35
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 38 . We turned on the heater for 22 minutes. What is the temperature after 22 minutes?",
        "answer": 51,
        "options": [
            36,
            16,
            31,
            20,
            51
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 63 . We turned on the heater for 103 minutes. What is the temperature after 103 minutes?",
        "answer": 69,
        "options": [
            56,
            69,
            60,
            60,
            53
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 19 . We turned on the heater for 71 minutes. What is the temperature after 71 minutes?",
        "answer": 24,
        "options": [
            11,
            24,
            15,
            18,
            -15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 43 . We turned on the heater for 120 minutes. What is the temperature after 120 minutes?",
        "answer": 46,
        "options": [
            40,
            46,
            36,
            15,
            36
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 51 . We turned on the heater for 98 minutes. What is the temperature after 98 minutes?",
        "answer": 54,
        "options": [
            37,
            49,
            54,
            38,
            49
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 17 . We turned on the heater for 22 minutes. What is the temperature after 22 minutes?",
        "answer": 26,
        "options": [
            -7,
            3,
            26,
            0,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 2 . We turned on the heater for 100 minutes. What is the temperature after 100 minutes?",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            -14,
            6,
            -14,
            -14,
            -3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 64 . We turned on the heater for 55 minutes. What is the temperature after 55 minutes?",
        "answer": 67,
        "options": [
            60,
            67,
            40,
            52,
            57
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 31 . We turned on the heater for 99 minutes. What is the temperature after 99 minutes?",
        "answer": 32,
        "options": [
            29,
            32,
            28,
            -5,
            11
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 34 . We turned on the heater for 93 minutes. What is the temperature after 93 minutes?",
        "answer": 37,
        "options": [
            22,
            32,
            17,
            37,
            28
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 23 . We turned on the heater for 46 minutes. What is the temperature after 46 minutes?",
        "answer": 26,
        "options": [
            21,
            16,
            26,
            15,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 6 . We turned on the heater for 50 minutes. What is the temperature after 50 minutes?",
        "answer": 8,
        "options": [
            0,
            2,
            3,
            -14,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 16 . We turned on the heater for 10 minutes. What is the temperature after 10 minutes?",
        "answer": 34,
        "options": [
            14,
            -18,
            34,
            11,
            -5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 44 . We turned on the heater for 105 minutes. What is the temperature after 105 minutes?",
        "answer": 46,
        "options": [
            40,
            43,
            37,
            46,
            22
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 70 . We turned on the heater for 115 minutes. What is the temperature after 115 minutes?",
        "answer": 72,
        "options": [
            52,
            68,
            69,
            65,
            72
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 45 . We turned on the heater for 107 minutes. What is the temperature after 107 minutes?",
        "answer": 57,
        "options": [
            37,
            17,
            42,
            26,
            57
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 12 . We turned on the heater for 7 minutes. What is the temperature after 7 minutes?",
        "answer": 22,
        "options": [
            -11,
            5,
            22,
            10,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 15 . We turned on the heater for 59 minutes. What is the temperature after 59 minutes?",
        "answer": 20,
        "options": [
            9,
            -9,
            20,
            -5,
            13
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 61 . We turned on the heater for 68 minutes. What is the temperature after 68 minutes?",
        "answer": 65,
        "options": [
            60,
            52,
            56,
            65,
            46
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 13 . We turned on the heater for 112 minutes. What is the temperature after 112 minutes?",
        "answer": 14,
        "options": [
            12,
            14,
            9,
            8,
            -1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 68 . We turned on the heater for 104 minutes. What is the temperature after 104 minutes?",
        "answer": 69,
        "options": [
            52,
            69,
            50,
            42,
            60
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 64 . We turned on the heater for 32 minutes. What is the temperature after 32 minutes?",
        "answer": 72,
        "options": [
            59,
            62,
            59,
            61,
            72
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 66 . We turned on the heater for 99 minutes. What is the temperature after 99 minutes?",
        "answer": 82,
        "options": [
            65,
            82,
            56,
            49,
            59
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 64 . We turned on the heater for 25 minutes. What is the temperature after 25 minutes?",
        "answer": 67,
        "options": [
            60,
            62,
            67,
            58,
            63
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 59 . We turned on the heater for 104 minutes. What is the temperature after 104 minutes?",
        "answer": 68,
        "options": [
            49,
            68,
            51,
            53,
            44
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 48 . We turned on the heater for 65 minutes. What is the temperature after 65 minutes?",
        "answer": 51,
        "options": [
            44,
            43,
            44,
            32,
            51
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 35 . We turned on the heater for 98 minutes. What is the temperature after 98 minutes?",
        "answer": 51,
        "options": [
            15,
            3,
            13,
            34,
            51
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 51 . We turned on the heater for 95 minutes. What is the temperature after 95 minutes?",
        "answer": 65,
        "options": [
            65,
            46,
            48,
            44,
            32
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 66 . We turned on the heater for 30 minutes. What is the temperature after 30 minutes?",
        "answer": 75,
        "options": [
            75,
            62,
            61,
            47,
            60
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 36 . We turned on the heater for 19 minutes. What is the temperature after 19 minutes?",
        "answer": 40,
        "options": [
            31,
            40,
            32,
            31,
            34
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 27 . We turned on the heater for 61 minutes. What is the temperature after 61 minutes?",
        "answer": 45,
        "options": [
            45,
            16,
            18,
            20,
            26
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 46 . We turned on the heater for 90 minutes. What is the temperature after 90 minutes?",
        "answer": 50,
        "options": [
            38,
            43,
            50,
            38,
            38
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 13 . We turned on the heater for 105 minutes. What is the temperature after 105 minutes?",
        "answer": 19,
        "options": [
            2,
            19,
            10,
            6,
            -13
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 39 . We turned on the heater for 37 minutes. What is the temperature after 37 minutes?",
        "answer": 47,
        "options": [
            12,
            37,
            34,
            47,
            29
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 61 . We turned on the heater for 104 minutes. What is the temperature after 104 minutes?",
        "answer": 77,
        "options": [
            52,
            56,
            47,
            77,
            50
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 36 . We turned on the heater for 46 minutes. What is the temperature after 46 minutes?",
        "answer": 45,
        "options": [
            31,
            45,
            16,
            30,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 34 . We turned on the heater for 99 minutes. What is the temperature after 99 minutes?",
        "answer": 38,
        "options": [
            23,
            38,
            22,
            12,
            23
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 10 . We turned on the heater for 23 minutes. What is the temperature after 23 minutes?",
        "answer": 18,
        "options": [
            18,
            -4,
            -1,
            -17,
            -28
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 32 . We turned on the heater for 34 minutes. What is the temperature after 34 minutes?",
        "answer": 49,
        "options": [
            5,
            49,
            30,
            16,
            29
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 29 . We turned on the heater for 34 minutes. What is the temperature after 34 minutes?",
        "answer": 44,
        "options": [
            21,
            16,
            44,
            27,
            13
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 58 . We turned on the heater for 72 minutes. What is the temperature after 72 minutes?",
        "answer": 60,
        "options": [
            54,
            60,
            56,
            49,
            54
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 62 . We turned on the heater for 116 minutes. What is the temperature after 116 minutes?",
        "answer": 63,
        "options": [
            61,
            58,
            63,
            57,
            46
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 12 . We turned on the heater for 97 minutes. What is the temperature after 97 minutes?",
        "answer": 25,
        "options": [
            0,
            25,
            4,
            9,
            -10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 9 . We turned on the heater for 68 minutes. What is the temperature after 68 minutes?",
        "answer": 13,
        "options": [
            -7,
            13,
            -29,
            7,
            -3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 15 . We turned on the heater for 34 minutes. What is the temperature after 34 minutes?",
        "answer": 27,
        "options": [
            -4,
            14,
            13,
            27,
            12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 3 . We turned on the heater for 35 minutes. What is the temperature after 35 minutes?",
        "answer": 4,
        "options": [
            1,
            -25,
            4,
            -7,
            -1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 1 . We turned on the heater for 66 minutes. What is the temperature after 66 minutes?",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            -25,
            -18,
            9,
            -16,
            0
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 54 . We turned on the heater for 46 minutes. What is the temperature after 46 minutes?",
        "answer": 72,
        "options": [
            47,
            39,
            48,
            72,
            31
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 2 . We turned on the heater for 41 minutes. What is the temperature after 41 minutes?",
        "answer": 5,
        "options": [
            -1,
            -16,
            5,
            -18,
            -5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 49 . We turned on the heater for 85 minutes. What is the temperature after 85 minutes?",
        "answer": 54,
        "options": [
            44,
            36,
            48,
            41,
            54
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 11 . We turned on the heater for 60 minutes. What is the temperature after 60 minutes?",
        "answer": 21,
        "options": [
            -2,
            21,
            10,
            -7,
            -25
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 23 . We turned on the heater for 35 minutes. What is the temperature after 35 minutes?",
        "answer": 26,
        "options": [
            12,
            26,
            20,
            8,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 56 . We turned on the heater for 77 minutes. What is the temperature after 77 minutes?",
        "answer": 62,
        "options": [
            31,
            62,
            48,
            51,
            30
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 50 . We turned on the heater for 64 minutes. What is the temperature after 64 minutes?",
        "answer": 53,
        "options": [
            53,
            36,
            21,
            23,
            48
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 12 . We turned on the heater for 31 minutes. What is the temperature after 31 minutes?",
        "answer": 15,
        "options": [
            1,
            15,
            6,
            11,
            -9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 6 . We turned on the heater for 91 minutes. What is the temperature after 91 minutes?",
        "answer": 17,
        "options": [
            -11,
            -7,
            -1,
            17,
            -3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 20 . We turned on the heater for 61 minutes. What is the temperature after 61 minutes?",
        "answer": 21,
        "options": [
            -16,
            11,
            1,
            21,
            -6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 43 . We turned on the heater for 99 minutes. What is the temperature after 99 minutes?",
        "answer": 61,
        "options": [
            42,
            41,
            40,
            61,
            31
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 43 . We turned on the heater for 44 minutes. What is the temperature after 44 minutes?",
        "answer": 47,
        "options": [
            34,
            37,
            28,
            47,
            37
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 8 . We turned on the heater for 91 minutes. What is the temperature after 91 minutes?",
        "answer": 14,
        "options": [
            0,
            -9,
            3,
            14,
            -15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 44 . We turned on the heater for 22 minutes. What is the temperature after 22 minutes?",
        "answer": 49,
        "options": [
            36,
            49,
            26,
            26,
            11
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 66 . We turned on the heater for 88 minutes. What is the temperature after 88 minutes?",
        "answer": 69,
        "options": [
            61,
            65,
            52,
            69,
            54
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 62 . We turned on the heater for 67 minutes. What is the temperature after 67 minutes?",
        "answer": 68,
        "options": [
            68,
            53,
            57,
            57,
            42
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 10 . We turned on the heater for 111 minutes. What is the temperature after 111 minutes?",
        "answer": 11,
        "options": [
            6,
            -12,
            8,
            11,
            -12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 23 . We turned on the heater for 119 minutes. What is the temperature after 119 minutes?",
        "answer": 24,
        "options": [
            21,
            6,
            11,
            -11,
            24
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 28 . We turned on the heater for 109 minutes. What is the temperature after 109 minutes?",
        "answer": 30,
        "options": [
            0,
            30,
            27,
            24,
            16
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 19 . We turned on the heater for 54 minutes. What is the temperature after 54 minutes?",
        "answer": 25,
        "options": [
            7,
            25,
            17,
            -5,
            14
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 64 . We turned on the heater for 110 minutes. What is the temperature after 110 minutes?",
        "answer": 67,
        "options": [
            35,
            53,
            56,
            67,
            58
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 51 . We turned on the heater for 36 minutes. What is the temperature after 36 minutes?",
        "answer": 53,
        "options": [
            53,
            39,
            36,
            46,
            39
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The current temperature of the living room is 52 . We turned on the heater for 32 minutes. What is the temperature after 32 minutes?",
        "answer": 56,
        "options": [
            41,
            47,
            32,
            49,
            56
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of venus around sun is 67200000 miles.It takes 7 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take uranus whose orbit is 1783700000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "1009",
        "options": [
            6,
            3,
            1009,
            3,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of jupiter around sun is 483600000 miles.It takes 142 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take mars whose orbit is 141600000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "23",
        "options": [
            23,
            162,
            226,
            166,
            168
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of pluto around sun is 3670100000 miles.It takes 2977 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take uranus whose orbit is 1783700000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "1009",
        "options": [
            3648,
            5478,
            3716,
            5946,
            1009
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of mercury around sun is 223700000 miles.It takes 3 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take earth whose orbit is 93000000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "12",
        "options": [
            5,
            6,
            12,
            3,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of mercury around sun is 223700000 miles.It takes 3 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take pluto whose orbit is 3670100000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "2977",
        "options": [
            2,
            2977,
            2,
            1,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of pluto around sun is 3670100000 miles.It takes 2977 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take saturn whose orbit is 886500000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "354",
        "options": [
            3166,
            3685,
            4132,
            3385,
            354
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of uranus around sun is 1783700000 miles.It takes 1009 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take venus whose orbit is 67200000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "7",
        "options": [
            1621,
            7,
            1944,
            1160,
            1075
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of mercury around sun is 223700000 miles.It takes 3 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take neptune whose orbit is 2795200000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "1979",
        "options": [
            1,
            2,
            1,
            2,
            1979
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of earth around sun is 93000000 miles.It takes 12 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take venus whose orbit is 67200000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "7",
        "options": [
            7,
            13,
            16,
            16,
            13
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of jupiter around sun is 483600000 miles.It takes 142 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take neptune whose orbit is 2795200000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "1979",
        "options": [
            1979,
            126,
            41,
            81,
            11
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of earth around sun is 93000000 miles.It takes 12 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take uranus whose orbit is 1783700000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "1009",
        "options": [
            8,
            11,
            4,
            10,
            1009
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of uranus around sun is 1783700000 miles.It takes 1009 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take earth whose orbit is 93000000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "12",
        "options": [
            12,
            1462,
            1638,
            1847,
            1211
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of earth around sun is 93000000 miles.It takes 12 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take earth whose orbit is 93000000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "12",
        "options": [
            10,
            12,
            3,
            10,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of venus around sun is 67200000 miles.It takes 7 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take uranus whose orbit is 1783700000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "1009",
        "options": [
            1,
            3,
            6,
            4,
            1009
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of neptune around sun is 2795200000 miles.It takes 1979 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take jupiter whose orbit is 483600000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "142",
        "options": [
            3788,
            3863,
            2908,
            142,
            3155
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of neptune around sun is 2795200000 miles.It takes 1979 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take pluto whose orbit is 3670100000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "2977",
        "options": [
            376,
            889,
            553,
            2977,
            1784
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of earth around sun is 93000000 miles.It takes 12 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take venus whose orbit is 67200000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "7",
        "options": [
            24,
            20,
            17,
            18,
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of jupiter around sun is 483600000 miles.It takes 142 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take neptune whose orbit is 2795200000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "1979",
        "options": [
            1979,
            123,
            58,
            63,
            103
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of uranus around sun is 1783700000 miles.It takes 1009 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take venus whose orbit is 67200000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "7",
        "options": [
            2015,
            1869,
            1598,
            7,
            1330
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of neptune around sun is 2795200000 miles.It takes 1979 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take jupiter whose orbit is 483600000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "142",
        "options": [
            2593,
            142,
            3769,
            3882,
            2306
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of mercury around sun is 223700000 miles.It takes 3 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take mercury whose orbit is 223700000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "3",
        "options": [
            1,
            2,
            2,
            3,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of pluto around sun is 3670100000 miles.It takes 2977 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take uranus whose orbit is 1783700000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "1009",
        "options": [
            4238,
            3970,
            5323,
            1009,
            5020
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of mercury around sun is 223700000 miles.It takes 3 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take uranus whose orbit is 1783700000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "1009",
        "options": [
            1009,
            2,
            2,
            1,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of venus around sun is 67200000 miles.It takes 7 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take venus whose orbit is 67200000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "7",
        "options": [
            3,
            7,
            5,
            2,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of pluto around sun is 3670100000 miles.It takes 2977 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take uranus whose orbit is 1783700000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "1009",
        "options": [
            5206,
            4179,
            1009,
            4029,
            5585
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of earth around sun is 93000000 miles.It takes 12 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take saturn whose orbit is 886500000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "354",
        "options": [
            7,
            11,
            8,
            1,
            354
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of earth around sun is 93000000 miles.It takes 12 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take mars whose orbit is 141600000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "23",
        "options": [
            8,
            10,
            7,
            23,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of saturn around sun is 886500000 miles.It takes 354 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take saturn whose orbit is 886500000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "354",
        "options": [
            34,
            4,
            305,
            85,
            354
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of neptune around sun is 2795200000 miles.It takes 1979 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take saturn whose orbit is 886500000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "354",
        "options": [
            354,
            2407,
            3753,
            2928,
            3066
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of pluto around sun is 3670100000 miles.It takes 2977 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take pluto whose orbit is 3670100000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "2977",
        "options": [
            2927,
            1917,
            854,
            896,
            2977
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of venus around sun is 67200000 miles.It takes 7 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take saturn whose orbit is 886500000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "354",
        "options": [
            2,
            5,
            4,
            354,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of earth around sun is 93000000 miles.It takes 12 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take earth whose orbit is 93000000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "12",
        "options": [
            5,
            1,
            12,
            3,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of mars around sun is 141600000 miles.It takes 23 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take neptune whose orbit is 2795200000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "1979",
        "options": [
            1979,
            5,
            1,
            6,
            14
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of venus around sun is 67200000 miles.It takes 7 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take saturn whose orbit is 886500000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "354",
        "options": [
            3,
            5,
            354,
            6,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of jupiter around sun is 483600000 miles.It takes 142 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take earth whose orbit is 93000000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "12",
        "options": [
            12,
            254,
            216,
            200,
            208
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of saturn around sun is 886500000 miles.It takes 354 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take earth whose orbit is 93000000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "12",
        "options": [
            529,
            444,
            688,
            12,
            477
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of venus around sun is 67200000 miles.It takes 7 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take mercury whose orbit is 223700000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "3",
        "options": [
            3,
            5,
            3,
            5,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of jupiter around sun is 483600000 miles.It takes 142 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take uranus whose orbit is 1783700000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "1009",
        "options": [
            71,
            36,
            1009,
            68,
            121
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of pluto around sun is 3670100000 miles.It takes 2977 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take venus whose orbit is 67200000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "7",
        "options": [
            4292,
            5334,
            4529,
            7,
            3268
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of neptune around sun is 2795200000 miles.It takes 1979 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take pluto whose orbit is 3670100000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "2977",
        "options": [
            547,
            2977,
            1579,
            1678,
            1192
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of uranus around sun is 1783700000 miles.It takes 1009 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take pluto whose orbit is 3670100000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "2977",
        "options": [
            82,
            2977,
            597,
            728,
            96
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of earth around sun is 93000000 miles.It takes 12 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take mercury whose orbit is 223700000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "3",
        "options": [
            9,
            8,
            10,
            6,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of venus around sun is 67200000 miles.It takes 7 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take uranus whose orbit is 1783700000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "1009",
        "options": [
            4,
            6,
            1,
            1,
            1009
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of neptune around sun is 2795200000 miles.It takes 1979 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take venus whose orbit is 67200000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "7",
        "options": [
            2228,
            2427,
            2500,
            2718,
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of neptune around sun is 2795200000 miles.It takes 1979 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take neptune whose orbit is 2795200000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "1979",
        "options": [
            1754,
            397,
            1979,
            1061,
            601
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of mercury around sun is 223700000 miles.It takes 3 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take neptune whose orbit is 2795200000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "1979",
        "options": [
            1979,
            1,
            1,
            1,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of mars around sun is 141600000 miles.It takes 23 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take jupiter whose orbit is 483600000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "142",
        "options": [
            142,
            5,
            10,
            18,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of earth around sun is 93000000 miles.It takes 12 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take earth whose orbit is 93000000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "12",
        "options": [
            9,
            5,
            9,
            12,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of saturn around sun is 886500000 miles.It takes 354 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take jupiter whose orbit is 483600000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "142",
        "options": [
            399,
            667,
            362,
            142,
            636
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of saturn around sun is 886500000 miles.It takes 354 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take saturn whose orbit is 886500000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "354",
        "options": [
            348,
            77,
            354,
            52,
            109
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of mercury around sun is 223700000 miles.It takes 3 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take earth whose orbit is 93000000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "12",
        "options": [
            5,
            4,
            3,
            12,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of venus around sun is 67200000 miles.It takes 7 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take mercury whose orbit is 223700000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "3",
        "options": [
            2,
            3,
            1,
            4,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of venus around sun is 67200000 miles.It takes 7 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take venus whose orbit is 67200000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "7",
        "options": [
            4,
            7,
            4,
            6,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of jupiter around sun is 483600000 miles.It takes 142 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take earth whose orbit is 93000000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "12",
        "options": [
            145,
            167,
            164,
            188,
            12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of mercury around sun is 223700000 miles.It takes 3 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take jupiter whose orbit is 483600000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "142",
        "options": [
            1,
            2,
            142,
            2,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of pluto around sun is 3670100000 miles.It takes 2977 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take neptune whose orbit is 2795200000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "1979",
        "options": [
            3886,
            1979,
            4929,
            4969,
            5144
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of venus around sun is 67200000 miles.It takes 7 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take saturn whose orbit is 886500000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "354",
        "options": [
            3,
            354,
            1,
            5,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of venus around sun is 67200000 miles.It takes 7 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take mars whose orbit is 141600000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "23",
        "options": [
            4,
            23,
            6,
            4,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of neptune around sun is 2795200000 miles.It takes 1979 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take jupiter whose orbit is 483600000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "142",
        "options": [
            142,
            3155,
            2198,
            2293,
            3074
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of jupiter around sun is 483600000 miles.It takes 142 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take neptune whose orbit is 2795200000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "1979",
        "options": [
            1979,
            8,
            8,
            104,
            130
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of mars around sun is 141600000 miles.It takes 23 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take venus whose orbit is 67200000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "7",
        "options": [
            33,
            7,
            44,
            26,
            25
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of neptune around sun is 2795200000 miles.It takes 1979 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take pluto whose orbit is 3670100000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "2977",
        "options": [
            449,
            1226,
            1319,
            1682,
            2977
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of saturn around sun is 886500000 miles.It takes 354 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take mercury whose orbit is 223700000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "3",
        "options": [
            354,
            450,
            576,
            690,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of uranus around sun is 1783700000 miles.It takes 1009 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take mars whose orbit is 141600000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "23",
        "options": [
            1657,
            1324,
            1240,
            1209,
            23
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of jupiter around sun is 483600000 miles.It takes 142 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take pluto whose orbit is 3670100000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "2977",
        "options": [
            8,
            2977,
            137,
            2,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of mercury around sun is 223700000 miles.It takes 3 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take jupiter whose orbit is 483600000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "142",
        "options": [
            2,
            2,
            2,
            2,
            142
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of mars around sun is 141600000 miles.It takes 23 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take saturn whose orbit is 886500000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "354",
        "options": [
            354,
            17,
            16,
            4,
            21
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of uranus around sun is 1783700000 miles.It takes 1009 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take pluto whose orbit is 3670100000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "2977",
        "options": [
            898,
            523,
            937,
            2977,
            435
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of mercury around sun is 223700000 miles.It takes 3 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take neptune whose orbit is 2795200000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "1979",
        "options": [
            1979,
            2,
            1,
            1,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of earth around sun is 93000000 miles.It takes 12 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take saturn whose orbit is 886500000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "354",
        "options": [
            354,
            3,
            3,
            5,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of saturn around sun is 886500000 miles.It takes 354 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take venus whose orbit is 67200000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "7",
        "options": [
            521,
            529,
            461,
            687,
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of mars around sun is 141600000 miles.It takes 23 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take mercury whose orbit is 223700000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "3",
        "options": [
            17,
            19,
            7,
            22,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of uranus around sun is 1783700000 miles.It takes 1009 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take mercury whose orbit is 223700000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "3",
        "options": [
            1983,
            1901,
            1926,
            1746,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of pluto around sun is 3670100000 miles.It takes 2977 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take mercury whose orbit is 223700000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "3",
        "options": [
            5731,
            3,
            5003,
            3761,
            2999
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of mercury around sun is 223700000 miles.It takes 3 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take mars whose orbit is 141600000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "23",
        "options": [
            6,
            23,
            3,
            3,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of jupiter around sun is 483600000 miles.It takes 142 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take mercury whose orbit is 223700000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "3",
        "options": [
            238,
            3,
            275,
            263,
            240
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of jupiter around sun is 483600000 miles.It takes 142 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take saturn whose orbit is 886500000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "354",
        "options": [
            354,
            21,
            81,
            84,
            77
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of mars around sun is 141600000 miles.It takes 23 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take pluto whose orbit is 3670100000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "2977",
        "options": [
            12,
            2977,
            8,
            1,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of mercury around sun is 223700000 miles.It takes 3 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take jupiter whose orbit is 483600000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "142",
        "options": [
            2,
            1,
            2,
            142,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of pluto around sun is 3670100000 miles.It takes 2977 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take pluto whose orbit is 3670100000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "2977",
        "options": [
            2931,
            690,
            1583,
            2977,
            114
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of mars around sun is 141600000 miles.It takes 23 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take pluto whose orbit is 3670100000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "2977",
        "options": [
            2977,
            5,
            22,
            7,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of earth around sun is 93000000 miles.It takes 12 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take mars whose orbit is 141600000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "23",
        "options": [
            1,
            6,
            23,
            4,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of mars around sun is 141600000 miles.It takes 23 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take venus whose orbit is 67200000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "7",
        "options": [
            7,
            24,
            44,
            26,
            45
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of venus around sun is 67200000 miles.It takes 7 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take mars whose orbit is 141600000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "23",
        "options": [
            2,
            1,
            2,
            23,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of neptune around sun is 2795200000 miles.It takes 1979 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take earth whose orbit is 93000000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "12",
        "options": [
            12,
            3799,
            2762,
            3096,
            2416
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of neptune around sun is 2795200000 miles.It takes 1979 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take saturn whose orbit is 886500000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "354",
        "options": [
            2282,
            354,
            2814,
            3304,
            2972
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of pluto around sun is 3670100000 miles.It takes 2977 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take venus whose orbit is 67200000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "7",
        "options": [
            5650,
            7,
            4014,
            4320,
            5477
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of neptune around sun is 2795200000 miles.It takes 1979 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take mercury whose orbit is 223700000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "3",
        "options": [
            2158,
            3248,
            3032,
            3,
            3043
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of saturn around sun is 886500000 miles.It takes 354 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take saturn whose orbit is 886500000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "354",
        "options": [
            249,
            24,
            354,
            94,
            89
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of uranus around sun is 1783700000 miles.It takes 1009 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take neptune whose orbit is 2795200000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "1979",
        "options": [
            915,
            941,
            1979,
            63,
            779
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of venus around sun is 67200000 miles.It takes 7 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take mars whose orbit is 141600000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "23",
        "options": [
            1,
            1,
            23,
            2,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of mercury around sun is 223700000 miles.It takes 3 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take uranus whose orbit is 1783700000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "1009",
        "options": [
            1,
            1,
            1009,
            1,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of saturn around sun is 886500000 miles.It takes 354 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take neptune whose orbit is 2795200000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "1979",
        "options": [
            1979,
            1,
            60,
            1,
            230
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of uranus around sun is 1783700000 miles.It takes 1009 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take uranus whose orbit is 1783700000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "1009",
        "options": [
            273,
            221,
            472,
            1009,
            586
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of earth around sun is 93000000 miles.It takes 12 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take mercury whose orbit is 223700000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "3",
        "options": [
            5,
            1,
            5,
            3,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of jupiter around sun is 483600000 miles.It takes 142 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take saturn whose orbit is 886500000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "354",
        "options": [
            51,
            354,
            42,
            82,
            56
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of pluto around sun is 3670100000 miles.It takes 2977 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take neptune whose orbit is 2795200000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "1979",
        "options": [
            3078,
            1979,
            3903,
            3783,
            4211
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of uranus around sun is 1783700000 miles.It takes 1009 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take saturn whose orbit is 886500000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "354",
        "options": [
            1280,
            354,
            1223,
            1511,
            1588
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of saturn around sun is 886500000 miles.It takes 354 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take neptune whose orbit is 2795200000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "1979",
        "options": [
            1979,
            60,
            206,
            281,
            25
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The orbit of venus around sun is 67200000 miles.It takes 7 earth months to orbit once around sun. How many days will it take neptune whose orbit is 2795200000 miles to rotate once around the sun?",
        "answer": "1979",
        "options": [
            3,
            4,
            3,
            3,
            1979
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 43 * 32. Which carpet shoul I buy from target?",
        "answer": "31*31",
        "options": [
            "69*44",
            "76*54",
            "75*35",
            "31*31",
            "60*53"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 45 * 50. Which carpet shoul I buy from amazon?",
        "answer": "43*31",
        "options": [
            "62*79",
            "72*68",
            "68*79",
            "76*89",
            "43*31"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 57 * 52. Which carpet shoul I buy from target?",
        "answer": "42*38",
        "options": [
            "42*38",
            "94*74",
            "103*105",
            "88*88",
            "104*69"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 58 * 53. Which carpet shoul I buy from target?",
        "answer": "39*38",
        "options": [
            "39*38",
            "84*74",
            "67*59",
            "73*88",
            "99*98"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 35 * 33. Which carpet shoul I buy from target?",
        "answer": "33*30",
        "options": [
            "44*49",
            "70*58",
            "49*62",
            "61*44",
            "33*30"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 38 * 53. Which carpet shoul I buy from target?",
        "answer": "31*37",
        "options": [
            "40*100",
            "69*103",
            "31*37",
            "74*91",
            "53*91"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 39 * 43. Which carpet shoul I buy from amazon?",
        "answer": "31*37",
        "options": [
            "55*59",
            "66*87",
            "31*37",
            "64*46",
            "47*73"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 45 * 51. Which carpet shoul I buy from walmart?",
        "answer": "30*37",
        "options": [
            "82*78",
            "74*104",
            "60*88",
            "30*37",
            "91*97"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 32 * 60. Which carpet shoul I buy from target?",
        "answer": "29*40",
        "options": [
            "50*119",
            "47*62",
            "55*109",
            "47*81",
            "29*40"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 40 * 44. Which carpet shoul I buy from amazon?",
        "answer": "39*23",
        "options": [
            "62*72",
            "59*81",
            "39*23",
            "50*49",
            "67*47"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 58 * 43. Which carpet shoul I buy from target?",
        "answer": "33*41",
        "options": [
            "33*41",
            "68*61",
            "101*74",
            "101*71",
            "64*54"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 51 * 55. Which carpet shoul I buy from walmart?",
        "answer": "30*29",
        "options": [
            "94*111",
            "62*97",
            "84*78",
            "30*29",
            "66*99"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 35 * 46. Which carpet shoul I buy from target?",
        "answer": "34*36",
        "options": [
            "34*36",
            "38*81",
            "55*68",
            "55*89",
            "40*83"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 45 * 49. Which carpet shoul I buy from flipkart?",
        "answer": "24*29",
        "options": [
            "77*81",
            "55*91",
            "55*98",
            "92*54",
            "24*29"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 38 * 59. Which carpet shoul I buy from target?",
        "answer": "32*35",
        "options": [
            "72*85",
            "71*81",
            "43*83",
            "32*35",
            "67*108"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 58 * 38. Which carpet shoul I buy from target?",
        "answer": "34*25",
        "options": [
            "34*25",
            "61*45",
            "78*56",
            "115*74",
            "113*60"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 38 * 57. Which carpet shoul I buy from flipkart?",
        "answer": "28*29",
        "options": [
            "66*107",
            "75*111",
            "42*108",
            "48*101",
            "28*29"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 49 * 56. Which carpet shoul I buy from target?",
        "answer": "32*52",
        "options": [
            "32*52",
            "55*90",
            "65*75",
            "52*110",
            "92*82"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 45 * 39. Which carpet shoul I buy from walmart?",
        "answer": "26*37",
        "options": [
            "87*52",
            "49*48",
            "26*37",
            "76*60",
            "83*74"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 53 * 41. Which carpet shoul I buy from walmart?",
        "answer": "49*21",
        "options": [
            "80*44",
            "49*21",
            "63*58",
            "89*51",
            "91*56"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 37 * 33. Which carpet shoul I buy from walmart?",
        "answer": "24*21",
        "options": [
            "49*52",
            "50*58",
            "40*59",
            "71*48",
            "24*21"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 38 * 38. Which carpet shoul I buy from target?",
        "answer": "29*20",
        "options": [
            "65*57",
            "74*67",
            "29*20",
            "60*56",
            "52*47"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 51 * 49. Which carpet shoul I buy from flipkart?",
        "answer": "36*27",
        "options": [
            "60*87",
            "36*27",
            "79*78",
            "63*52",
            "61*74"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 43 * 57. Which carpet shoul I buy from walmart?",
        "answer": "22*38",
        "options": [
            "22*38",
            "65*92",
            "72*106",
            "68*88",
            "46*94"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 44 * 59. Which carpet shoul I buy from flipkart?",
        "answer": "36*58",
        "options": [
            "36*58",
            "59*72",
            "73*102",
            "73*77",
            "62*99"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 39 * 46. Which carpet shoul I buy from target?",
        "answer": "20*34",
        "options": [
            "43*55",
            "20*34",
            "67*78",
            "75*60",
            "72*68"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 32 * 38. Which carpet shoul I buy from walmart?",
        "answer": "27*23",
        "options": [
            "55*64",
            "39*70",
            "48*63",
            "27*23",
            "59*73"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 49 * 32. Which carpet shoul I buy from target?",
        "answer": "34*20",
        "options": [
            "89*54",
            "58*65",
            "34*20",
            "62*44",
            "69*59"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 30 * 41. Which carpet shoul I buy from flipkart?",
        "answer": "20*26",
        "options": [
            "32*42",
            "44*63",
            "54*54",
            "49*81",
            "20*26"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 52 * 43. Which carpet shoul I buy from amazon?",
        "answer": "49*22",
        "options": [
            "93*47",
            "62*75",
            "76*59",
            "53*45",
            "49*22"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 43 * 48. Which carpet shoul I buy from flipkart?",
        "answer": "35*45",
        "options": [
            "66*83",
            "44*68",
            "67*51",
            "69*55",
            "35*45"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 43 * 40. Which carpet shoul I buy from walmart?",
        "answer": "42*34",
        "options": [
            "55*61",
            "66*81",
            "81*77",
            "42*34",
            "71*78"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 48 * 38. Which carpet shoul I buy from walmart?",
        "answer": "27*25",
        "options": [
            "60*46",
            "70*63",
            "27*25",
            "79*75",
            "50*62"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 52 * 52. Which carpet shoul I buy from target?",
        "answer": "43*51",
        "options": [
            "43*51",
            "53*96",
            "77*92",
            "72*75",
            "85*59"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 39 * 50. Which carpet shoul I buy from amazon?",
        "answer": "21*49",
        "options": [
            "44*62",
            "63*70",
            "21*49",
            "61*76",
            "66*70"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 58 * 46. Which carpet shoul I buy from flipkart?",
        "answer": "30*24",
        "options": [
            "30*24",
            "69*73",
            "111*71",
            "96*76",
            "113*70"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 37 * 50. Which carpet shoul I buy from target?",
        "answer": "26*47",
        "options": [
            "73*65",
            "41*69",
            "26*47",
            "38*66",
            "48*87"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 56 * 40. Which carpet shoul I buy from flipkart?",
        "answer": "51*20",
        "options": [
            "103*60",
            "104*60",
            "98*61",
            "98*61",
            "51*20"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 37 * 53. Which carpet shoul I buy from amazon?",
        "answer": "31*31",
        "options": [
            "62*88",
            "50*63",
            "68*94",
            "71*75",
            "31*31"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 31 * 52. Which carpet shoul I buy from walmart?",
        "answer": "21*45",
        "options": [
            "55*95",
            "59*64",
            "63*87",
            "49*74",
            "21*45"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 48 * 57. Which carpet shoul I buy from target?",
        "answer": "44*39",
        "options": [
            "67*76",
            "44*39",
            "52*63",
            "59*85",
            "77*67"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 57 * 48. Which carpet shoul I buy from target?",
        "answer": "37*31",
        "options": [
            "68*60",
            "37*31",
            "80*49",
            "92*52",
            "102*82"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 38 * 33. Which carpet shoul I buy from walmart?",
        "answer": "19*23",
        "options": [
            "55*50",
            "48*48",
            "60*57",
            "19*23",
            "48*41"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 35 * 54. Which carpet shoul I buy from flipkart?",
        "answer": "20*45",
        "options": [
            "59*89",
            "20*45",
            "70*108",
            "54*84",
            "41*109"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 50 * 57. Which carpet shoul I buy from walmart?",
        "answer": "35*44",
        "options": [
            "82*58",
            "35*44",
            "78*59",
            "66*107",
            "65*97"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 58 * 34. Which carpet shoul I buy from amazon?",
        "answer": "36*33",
        "options": [
            "101*42",
            "74*36",
            "36*33",
            "73*52",
            "68*51"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 42 * 53. Which carpet shoul I buy from flipkart?",
        "answer": "36*36",
        "options": [
            "36*36",
            "70*60",
            "62*83",
            "71*100",
            "43*86"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 32 * 50. Which carpet shoul I buy from walmart?",
        "answer": "17*36",
        "options": [
            "56*94",
            "47*63",
            "17*36",
            "45*66",
            "58*63"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 48 * 54. Which carpet shoul I buy from amazon?",
        "answer": "37*35",
        "options": [
            "61*68",
            "37*35",
            "80*64",
            "84*72",
            "69*88"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The size of my room is 32 * 32. Which carpet shoul I buy from flipkart?",
        "answer": "19*24",
        "options": [
            "19*24",
            "36*48",
            "46*39",
            "48*35",
            "36*39"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Harvey drives at a speed of 7 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Grey 's place which is 185 km away?",
        "answer": "26.43",
        "options": [
            "105.71",
            "52.86",
            "26.43",
            "132.14",
            "79.29"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Cade runs at a speed of 18 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Deandre 's place which is 151 km away?",
        "answer": "8.39",
        "options": [
            "25.17",
            "16.78",
            "25.17",
            "8.39",
            "16.78"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Anderson drives at a speed of 12 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Marc 's place which is 116 km away?",
        "answer": "9.67",
        "options": [
            "48.33",
            "38.67",
            "9.67",
            "38.67",
            "19.33"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Preston runs at a speed of 15 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Westin 's place which is 179 km away?",
        "answer": "11.93",
        "options": [
            "35.80",
            "11.93",
            "23.87",
            "23.87",
            "59.67"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Javier drives at a speed of 13 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Aden 's place which is 194 km away?",
        "answer": "14.92",
        "options": [
            "59.69",
            "59.69",
            "14.92",
            "44.77",
            "44.77"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Nash runs at a speed of 16 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Vivaan 's place which is 161 km away?",
        "answer": "10.06",
        "options": [
            "30.19",
            "20.12",
            "10.06",
            "20.12",
            "20.12"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Tobias runs at a speed of 15 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Alessandro 's place which is 169 km away?",
        "answer": "11.27",
        "options": [
            "33.80",
            "45.07",
            "56.33",
            "11.27",
            "56.33"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ezra walks at a speed of 20 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Roland 's place which is 147 km away?",
        "answer": "7.35",
        "options": [
            "22.05",
            "7.35",
            "29.40",
            "22.05",
            "14.70"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Donovan drives at a speed of 17 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Gatlin 's place which is 167 km away?",
        "answer": "9.82",
        "options": [
            "19.65",
            "39.29",
            "9.82",
            "39.29",
            "39.29"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Maximiliano walks at a speed of 11 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Van 's place which is 142 km away?",
        "answer": "12.91",
        "options": [
            "64.55",
            "64.55",
            "64.55",
            "12.91",
            "51.64"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Derek cycles at a speed of 15 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Coleman 's place which is 179 km away?",
        "answer": "11.93",
        "options": [
            "35.80",
            "23.87",
            "59.67",
            "11.93",
            "47.73"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ismael runs at a speed of 18 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Dillon 's place which is 177 km away?",
        "answer": "9.83",
        "options": [
            "29.50",
            "19.67",
            "39.33",
            "19.67",
            "9.83"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Oscar walks at a speed of 18 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Roger 's place which is 189 km away?",
        "answer": "10.50",
        "options": [
            "21.00",
            "10.50",
            "31.50",
            "52.50",
            "31.50"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Elliott runs at a speed of 11 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Blaze 's place which is 169 km away?",
        "answer": "15.36",
        "options": [
            "61.45",
            "76.82",
            "15.36",
            "61.45",
            "46.09"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Joshua runs at a speed of 7 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Casen 's place which is 112 km away?",
        "answer": "16.00",
        "options": [
            "80.00",
            "80.00",
            "48.00",
            "16.00",
            "80.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Josue runs at a speed of 12 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Julio 's place which is 183 km away?",
        "answer": "15.25",
        "options": [
            "30.50",
            "61.00",
            "61.00",
            "15.25",
            "76.25"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "David cycles at a speed of 8 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Zaid 's place which is 168 km away?",
        "answer": "21.00",
        "options": [
            "63.00",
            "63.00",
            "105.00",
            "21.00",
            "84.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Milo drives at a speed of 16 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Arturo 's place which is 165 km away?",
        "answer": "10.31",
        "options": [
            "41.25",
            "20.62",
            "10.31",
            "30.94",
            "20.62"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Nicholas cycles at a speed of 7 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Alessandro 's place which is 196 km away?",
        "answer": "28.00",
        "options": [
            "84.00",
            "28.00",
            "140.00",
            "112.00",
            "112.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Joaquin walks at a speed of 10 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Crosby 's place which is 150 km away?",
        "answer": "15.00",
        "options": [
            "30.00",
            "30.00",
            "75.00",
            "75.00",
            "15.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Emerson runs at a speed of 20 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Dennis 's place which is 182 km away?",
        "answer": "9.10",
        "options": [
            "36.40",
            "18.20",
            "9.10",
            "27.30",
            "45.50"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Patrick walks at a speed of 7 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Jad 's place which is 108 km away?",
        "answer": "15.43",
        "options": [
            "30.86",
            "61.71",
            "61.71",
            "46.29",
            "15.43"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Hayden drives at a speed of 8 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Imran 's place which is 189 km away?",
        "answer": "23.62",
        "options": [
            "70.88",
            "23.62",
            "94.50",
            "47.25",
            "70.88"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Otto runs at a speed of 19 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Terry 's place which is 131 km away?",
        "answer": "6.89",
        "options": [
            "34.47",
            "34.47",
            "27.58",
            "6.89",
            "34.47"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexis drives at a speed of 17 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Kendall 's place which is 159 km away?",
        "answer": "9.35",
        "options": [
            "46.76",
            "28.06",
            "37.41",
            "9.35",
            "18.71"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Finnegan runs at a speed of 13 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Leonard 's place which is 196 km away?",
        "answer": "15.08",
        "options": [
            "60.31",
            "75.38",
            "30.15",
            "45.23",
            "15.08"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Aidan drives at a speed of 12 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Callum 's place which is 140 km away?",
        "answer": "11.67",
        "options": [
            "35.00",
            "58.33",
            "23.33",
            "58.33",
            "11.67"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Dawson cycles at a speed of 12 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Eddie 's place which is 184 km away?",
        "answer": "15.33",
        "options": [
            "15.33",
            "61.33",
            "76.67",
            "61.33",
            "61.33"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Liam cycles at a speed of 19 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Abdullah 's place which is 137 km away?",
        "answer": "7.21",
        "options": [
            "14.42",
            "28.84",
            "7.21",
            "28.84",
            "36.05"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Weston drives at a speed of 15 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Vihaan 's place which is 189 km away?",
        "answer": "12.60",
        "options": [
            "37.80",
            "37.80",
            "37.80",
            "12.60",
            "50.40"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Rylan walks at a speed of 6 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Scott 's place which is 144 km away?",
        "answer": "24.00",
        "options": [
            "96.00",
            "120.00",
            "24.00",
            "72.00",
            "96.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jaxton walks at a speed of 12 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Jacoby 's place which is 164 km away?",
        "answer": "13.67",
        "options": [
            "27.33",
            "54.67",
            "41.00",
            "68.33",
            "13.67"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jeremiah cycles at a speed of 10 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Duncan 's place which is 139 km away?",
        "answer": "13.90",
        "options": [
            "13.90",
            "41.70",
            "55.60",
            "55.60",
            "55.60"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Shawn walks at a speed of 14 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Dorian 's place which is 104 km away?",
        "answer": "7.43",
        "options": [
            "29.71",
            "22.29",
            "22.29",
            "29.71",
            "7.43"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Gavin cycles at a speed of 17 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Judson 's place which is 141 km away?",
        "answer": "8.29",
        "options": [
            "16.59",
            "16.59",
            "24.88",
            "16.59",
            "8.29"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Pedro cycles at a speed of 14 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Brendan 's place which is 154 km away?",
        "answer": "11.00",
        "options": [
            "22.00",
            "22.00",
            "33.00",
            "55.00",
            "11.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Killian runs at a speed of 6 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Vincenzo 's place which is 110 km away?",
        "answer": "18.33",
        "options": [
            "91.67",
            "18.33",
            "73.33",
            "73.33",
            "36.67"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Luca drives at a speed of 10 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Zakai 's place which is 199 km away?",
        "answer": "19.90",
        "options": [
            "39.80",
            "79.60",
            "19.90",
            "39.80",
            "39.80"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jonathan drives at a speed of 8 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Westley 's place which is 192 km away?",
        "answer": "24.00",
        "options": [
            "96.00",
            "24.00",
            "72.00",
            "48.00",
            "96.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Fernando walks at a speed of 18 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Raylan 's place which is 110 km away?",
        "answer": "6.11",
        "options": [
            "6.11",
            "12.22",
            "30.56",
            "24.44",
            "30.56"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Atlas cycles at a speed of 13 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Casen 's place which is 152 km away?",
        "answer": "11.69",
        "options": [
            "23.38",
            "58.46",
            "35.08",
            "11.69",
            "46.77"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Kayden runs at a speed of 17 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Zev 's place which is 183 km away?",
        "answer": "10.76",
        "options": [
            "21.53",
            "53.82",
            "21.53",
            "43.06",
            "10.76"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jensen cycles at a speed of 18 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Jordy 's place which is 105 km away?",
        "answer": "5.83",
        "options": [
            "11.67",
            "29.17",
            "17.50",
            "5.83",
            "17.50"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jax cycles at a speed of 19 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Juelz 's place which is 197 km away?",
        "answer": "10.37",
        "options": [
            "10.37",
            "31.11",
            "20.74",
            "20.74",
            "31.11"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Cooper cycles at a speed of 9 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Nikolas 's place which is 179 km away?",
        "answer": "19.89",
        "options": [
            "19.89",
            "99.44",
            "79.56",
            "59.67",
            "99.44"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Erick cycles at a speed of 11 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Jericho 's place which is 154 km away?",
        "answer": "14.00",
        "options": [
            "70.00",
            "56.00",
            "14.00",
            "56.00",
            "42.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Mark runs at a speed of 17 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Bentlee 's place which is 118 km away?",
        "answer": "6.94",
        "options": [
            "20.82",
            "13.88",
            "6.94",
            "27.76",
            "34.71"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ezra cycles at a speed of 18 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Jerry 's place which is 123 km away?",
        "answer": "6.83",
        "options": [
            "27.33",
            "20.50",
            "6.83",
            "34.17",
            "34.17"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Abraham runs at a speed of 7 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Zaire 's place which is 170 km away?",
        "answer": "24.29",
        "options": [
            "72.86",
            "24.29",
            "97.14",
            "72.86",
            "121.43"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Kameron walks at a speed of 12 km/hr. How much time will it take him/her to travel Valentino 's place which is 146 km away?",
        "answer": "12.17",
        "options": [
            "24.33",
            "12.17",
            "48.67",
            "36.50",
            "24.33"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 19 watt charger charges a phone in 57 minutes. How much time will it take for a 28 watt charger to charge the same phone ?",
        "answer": 53,
        "options": [
            91,
            90,
            89,
            53,
            86
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 12 watt charger charges a airpods in 30 minutes. How much time will it take for a 30 watt charger to charge the same airpods ?",
        "answer": 17,
        "options": [
            74,
            17,
            78,
            95,
            34
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 7 watt charger charges a tablet in 43 minutes. How much time will it take for a 25 watt charger to charge the same tablet ?",
        "answer": 14,
        "options": [
            75,
            65,
            52,
            63,
            14
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 20 watt charger charges a phone in 46 minutes. How much time will it take for a 26 watt charger to charge the same phone ?",
        "answer": 12,
        "options": [
            94,
            96,
            79,
            94,
            12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 24 watt charger charges a powerbank in 18 minutes. How much time will it take for a 5 watt charger to charge the same powerbank ?",
        "answer": 33,
        "options": [
            11,
            17,
            8,
            33,
            15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 20 watt charger charges a airpods in 31 minutes. How much time will it take for a 15 watt charger to charge the same airpods ?",
        "answer": 62,
        "options": [
            4,
            15,
            62,
            7,
            16
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 25 watt charger charges a airpods in 25 minutes. How much time will it take for a 5 watt charger to charge the same airpods ?",
        "answer": 59,
        "options": [
            20,
            3,
            59,
            12,
            14
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 11 watt charger charges a powerbank in 50 minutes. How much time will it take for a 3 watt charger to charge the same powerbank ?",
        "answer": 58,
        "options": [
            33,
            58,
            30,
            26,
            28
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 8 watt charger charges a laptop in 13 minutes. How much time will it take for a 6 watt charger to charge the same laptop ?",
        "answer": 44,
        "options": [
            12,
            44,
            2,
            10,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 18 watt charger charges a airpods in 53 minutes. How much time will it take for a 7 watt charger to charge the same airpods ?",
        "answer": 70,
        "options": [
            32,
            45,
            43,
            70,
            12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 19 watt charger charges a laptop in 13 minutes. How much time will it take for a 11 watt charger to charge the same laptop ?",
        "answer": 62,
        "options": [
            10,
            62,
            10,
            6,
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 25 watt charger charges a tablet in 29 minutes. How much time will it take for a 27 watt charger to charge the same tablet ?",
        "answer": 20,
        "options": [
            70,
            32,
            87,
            85,
            20
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 22 watt charger charges a laptop in 39 minutes. How much time will it take for a 8 watt charger to charge the same laptop ?",
        "answer": 58,
        "options": [
            58,
            24,
            4,
            21,
            17
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 27 watt charger charges a powerbank in 28 minutes. How much time will it take for a 18 watt charger to charge the same powerbank ?",
        "answer": 65,
        "options": [
            7,
            19,
            11,
            1,
            65
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 10 watt charger charges a powerbank in 24 minutes. How much time will it take for a 14 watt charger to charge the same powerbank ?",
        "answer": 7,
        "options": [
            47,
            69,
            52,
            53,
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 15 watt charger charges a phone in 46 minutes. How much time will it take for a 6 watt charger to charge the same phone ?",
        "answer": 60,
        "options": [
            34,
            17,
            37,
            11,
            60
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 27 watt charger charges a powerbank in 42 minutes. How much time will it take for a 19 watt charger to charge the same powerbank ?",
        "answer": 57,
        "options": [
            13,
            33,
            38,
            36,
            57
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 5 watt charger charges a phone in 14 minutes. How much time will it take for a 12 watt charger to charge the same phone ?",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            16,
            41,
            41,
            9,
            85
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 21 watt charger charges a powerbank in 20 minutes. How much time will it take for a 18 watt charger to charge the same powerbank ?",
        "answer": 46,
        "options": [
            4,
            16,
            15,
            13,
            46
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 8 watt charger charges a airpods in 48 minutes. How much time will it take for a 7 watt charger to charge the same airpods ?",
        "answer": 68,
        "options": [
            39,
            68,
            9,
            10,
            24
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 13 watt charger charges a tablet in 18 minutes. How much time will it take for a 16 watt charger to charge the same tablet ?",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            75,
            6,
            61,
            19,
            19
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 13 watt charger charges a phone in 37 minutes. How much time will it take for a 6 watt charger to charge the same phone ?",
        "answer": 51,
        "options": [
            13,
            22,
            51,
            9,
            28
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 11 watt charger charges a powerbank in 11 minutes. How much time will it take for a 20 watt charger to charge the same powerbank ?",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            69,
            73,
            86,
            19,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 28 watt charger charges a airpods in 30 minutes. How much time will it take for a 21 watt charger to charge the same airpods ?",
        "answer": 64,
        "options": [
            27,
            17,
            22,
            64,
            26
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 28 watt charger charges a phone in 58 minutes. How much time will it take for a 28 watt charger to charge the same phone ?",
        "answer": 58,
        "options": [
            58,
            68,
            43,
            35,
            39
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 8 watt charger charges a powerbank in 40 minutes. How much time will it take for a 24 watt charger to charge the same powerbank ?",
        "answer": 23,
        "options": [
            44,
            59,
            89,
            69,
            23
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 14 watt charger charges a powerbank in 32 minutes. How much time will it take for a 26 watt charger to charge the same powerbank ?",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            94,
            77,
            88,
            2,
            60
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 11 watt charger charges a airpods in 11 minutes. How much time will it take for a 8 watt charger to charge the same airpods ?",
        "answer": 29,
        "options": [
            2,
            29,
            1,
            10,
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 24 watt charger charges a powerbank in 14 minutes. How much time will it take for a 23 watt charger to charge the same powerbank ?",
        "answer": 16,
        "options": [
            7,
            7,
            6,
            11,
            16
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 28 watt charger charges a airpods in 15 minutes. How much time will it take for a 28 watt charger to charge the same airpods ?",
        "answer": 15,
        "options": [
            16,
            33,
            15,
            37,
            31
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 27 watt charger charges a phone in 52 minutes. How much time will it take for a 21 watt charger to charge the same phone ?",
        "answer": 66,
        "options": [
            15,
            13,
            66,
            3,
            14
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 21 watt charger charges a airpods in 54 minutes. How much time will it take for a 28 watt charger to charge the same airpods ?",
        "answer": 19,
        "options": [
            86,
            19,
            72,
            91,
            83
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 21 watt charger charges a powerbank in 39 minutes. How much time will it take for a 19 watt charger to charge the same powerbank ?",
        "answer": 40,
        "options": [
            12,
            33,
            25,
            40,
            29
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 8 watt charger charges a airpods in 26 minutes. How much time will it take for a 27 watt charger to charge the same airpods ?",
        "answer": 11,
        "options": [
            72,
            100,
            75,
            63,
            11
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 25 watt charger charges a tablet in 44 minutes. How much time will it take for a 9 watt charger to charge the same tablet ?",
        "answer": 53,
        "options": [
            11,
            53,
            19,
            38,
            20
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 26 watt charger charges a tablet in 17 minutes. How much time will it take for a 22 watt charger to charge the same tablet ?",
        "answer": 29,
        "options": [
            29,
            15,
            11,
            14,
            13
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 12 watt charger charges a tablet in 58 minutes. How much time will it take for a 8 watt charger to charge the same tablet ?",
        "answer": 63,
        "options": [
            36,
            11,
            53,
            55,
            63
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 15 watt charger charges a laptop in 49 minutes. How much time will it take for a 23 watt charger to charge the same laptop ?",
        "answer": 20,
        "options": [
            50,
            59,
            20,
            94,
            85
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 22 watt charger charges a powerbank in 35 minutes. How much time will it take for a 28 watt charger to charge the same powerbank ?",
        "answer": 31,
        "options": [
            79,
            73,
            47,
            90,
            31
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 9 watt charger charges a phone in 11 minutes. How much time will it take for a 10 watt charger to charge the same phone ?",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            19,
            9,
            20,
            49,
            37
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 17 watt charger charges a powerbank in 32 minutes. How much time will it take for a 27 watt charger to charge the same powerbank ?",
        "answer": 27,
        "options": [
            93,
            41,
            49,
            77,
            27
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 24 watt charger charges a airpods in 58 minutes. How much time will it take for a 7 watt charger to charge the same airpods ?",
        "answer": 62,
        "options": [
            50,
            32,
            62,
            43,
            41
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 11 watt charger charges a phone in 25 minutes. How much time will it take for a 16 watt charger to charge the same phone ?",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            27,
            36,
            9,
            47,
            79
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 15 watt charger charges a phone in 10 minutes. How much time will it take for a 4 watt charger to charge the same phone ?",
        "answer": 61,
        "options": [
            61,
            3,
            9,
            3,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 28 watt charger charges a tablet in 39 minutes. How much time will it take for a 22 watt charger to charge the same tablet ?",
        "answer": 51,
        "options": [
            28,
            21,
            5,
            38,
            51
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 26 watt charger charges a airpods in 27 minutes. How much time will it take for a 7 watt charger to charge the same airpods ?",
        "answer": 31,
        "options": [
            31,
            26,
            13,
            24,
            26
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 23 watt charger charges a phone in 32 minutes. How much time will it take for a 11 watt charger to charge the same phone ?",
        "answer": 37,
        "options": [
            27,
            26,
            23,
            37,
            19
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 4 watt charger charges a powerbank in 27 minutes. How much time will it take for a 18 watt charger to charge the same powerbank ?",
        "answer": 24,
        "options": [
            52,
            24,
            28,
            55,
            90
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 30 watt charger charges a phone in 30 minutes. How much time will it take for a 19 watt charger to charge the same phone ?",
        "answer": 67,
        "options": [
            19,
            15,
            67,
            17,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 13 watt charger charges a phone in 34 minutes. How much time will it take for a 18 watt charger to charge the same phone ?",
        "answer": 28,
        "options": [
            28,
            56,
            35,
            97,
            81
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 27 watt charger charges a phone in 34 minutes. How much time will it take for a 24 watt charger to charge the same phone ?",
        "answer": 58,
        "options": [
            5,
            58,
            14,
            15,
            20
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 7 watt charger charges a airpods in 53 minutes. How much time will it take for a 28 watt charger to charge the same airpods ?",
        "answer": 47,
        "options": [
            60,
            95,
            47,
            72,
            66
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 13 watt charger charges a laptop in 52 minutes. How much time will it take for a 20 watt charger to charge the same laptop ?",
        "answer": 7,
        "options": [
            75,
            79,
            99,
            69,
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 22 watt charger charges a airpods in 30 minutes. How much time will it take for a 22 watt charger to charge the same airpods ?",
        "answer": 30,
        "options": [
            30,
            15,
            45,
            58,
            19
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 10 watt charger charges a phone in 17 minutes. How much time will it take for a 30 watt charger to charge the same phone ?",
        "answer": 15,
        "options": [
            99,
            15,
            71,
            28,
            56
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 23 watt charger charges a phone in 33 minutes. How much time will it take for a 3 watt charger to charge the same phone ?",
        "answer": 39,
        "options": [
            25,
            39,
            7,
            11,
            28
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 11 watt charger charges a laptop in 59 minutes. How much time will it take for a 20 watt charger to charge the same laptop ?",
        "answer": 25,
        "options": [
            72,
            78,
            25,
            93,
            93
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 12 watt charger charges a phone in 39 minutes. How much time will it take for a 14 watt charger to charge the same phone ?",
        "answer": 27,
        "options": [
            89,
            81,
            43,
            27,
            71
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 19 watt charger charges a powerbank in 21 minutes. How much time will it take for a 7 watt charger to charge the same powerbank ?",
        "answer": 47,
        "options": [
            10,
            6,
            18,
            19,
            47
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 19 watt charger charges a airpods in 26 minutes. How much time will it take for a 22 watt charger to charge the same airpods ?",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            81,
            59,
            65,
            2,
            44
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 24 watt charger charges a laptop in 29 minutes. How much time will it take for a 19 watt charger to charge the same laptop ?",
        "answer": 49,
        "options": [
            25,
            8,
            21,
            49,
            22
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 27 watt charger charges a laptop in 44 minutes. How much time will it take for a 11 watt charger to charge the same laptop ?",
        "answer": 54,
        "options": [
            29,
            54,
            35,
            12,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 21 watt charger charges a laptop in 35 minutes. How much time will it take for a 13 watt charger to charge the same laptop ?",
        "answer": 54,
        "options": [
            6,
            15,
            7,
            54,
            23
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 30 watt charger charges a powerbank in 34 minutes. How much time will it take for a 30 watt charger to charge the same powerbank ?",
        "answer": 34,
        "options": [
            28,
            40,
            54,
            38,
            34
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 6 watt charger charges a powerbank in 21 minutes. How much time will it take for a 17 watt charger to charge the same powerbank ?",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            54,
            10,
            71,
            64,
            62
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 11 watt charger charges a airpods in 33 minutes. How much time will it take for a 28 watt charger to charge the same airpods ?",
        "answer": 8,
        "options": [
            38,
            76,
            56,
            8,
            67
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 10 watt charger charges a tablet in 13 minutes. How much time will it take for a 18 watt charger to charge the same tablet ?",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            86,
            41,
            79,
            25,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 27 watt charger charges a airpods in 10 minutes. How much time will it take for a 16 watt charger to charge the same airpods ?",
        "answer": 11,
        "options": [
            11,
            2,
            6,
            9,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 5 watt charger charges a powerbank in 17 minutes. How much time will it take for a 2 watt charger to charge the same powerbank ?",
        "answer": 51,
        "options": [
            3,
            51,
            1,
            11,
            12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 7 watt charger charges a tablet in 58 minutes. How much time will it take for a 11 watt charger to charge the same tablet ?",
        "answer": 50,
        "options": [
            71,
            83,
            50,
            90,
            100
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 20 watt charger charges a powerbank in 30 minutes. How much time will it take for a 8 watt charger to charge the same powerbank ?",
        "answer": 34,
        "options": [
            1,
            15,
            26,
            16,
            34
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 6 watt charger charges a tablet in 36 minutes. How much time will it take for a 30 watt charger to charge the same tablet ?",
        "answer": 2,
        "options": [
            99,
            45,
            44,
            2,
            49
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 27 watt charger charges a tablet in 14 minutes. How much time will it take for a 20 watt charger to charge the same tablet ?",
        "answer": 53,
        "options": [
            11,
            53,
            13,
            9,
            13
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 18 watt charger charges a phone in 32 minutes. How much time will it take for a 23 watt charger to charge the same phone ?",
        "answer": 6,
        "options": [
            42,
            78,
            6,
            80,
            59
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 16 watt charger charges a airpods in 15 minutes. How much time will it take for a 16 watt charger to charge the same airpods ?",
        "answer": 15,
        "options": [
            70,
            20,
            37,
            15,
            33
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 13 watt charger charges a phone in 58 minutes. How much time will it take for a 14 watt charger to charge the same phone ?",
        "answer": 30,
        "options": [
            62,
            91,
            80,
            71,
            30
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 10 watt charger charges a phone in 48 minutes. How much time will it take for a 21 watt charger to charge the same phone ?",
        "answer": 15,
        "options": [
            60,
            91,
            62,
            15,
            78
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 24 watt charger charges a phone in 44 minutes. How much time will it take for a 17 watt charger to charge the same phone ?",
        "answer": 62,
        "options": [
            62,
            36,
            34,
            22,
            26
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 13 watt charger charges a airpods in 39 minutes. How much time will it take for a 7 watt charger to charge the same airpods ?",
        "answer": 63,
        "options": [
            63,
            26,
            4,
            9,
            36
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 20 watt charger charges a powerbank in 40 minutes. How much time will it take for a 11 watt charger to charge the same powerbank ?",
        "answer": 46,
        "options": [
            20,
            14,
            46,
            18,
            23
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 7 watt charger charges a laptop in 10 minutes. How much time will it take for a 11 watt charger to charge the same laptop ?",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            1,
            65,
            38,
            38,
            93
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 24 watt charger charges a powerbank in 16 minutes. How much time will it take for a 4 watt charger to charge the same powerbank ?",
        "answer": 47,
        "options": [
            11,
            47,
            5,
            9,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 7 watt charger charges a powerbank in 41 minutes. How much time will it take for a 16 watt charger to charge the same powerbank ?",
        "answer": 21,
        "options": [
            21,
            87,
            91,
            56,
            68
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 3 watt charger charges a tablet in 56 minutes. How much time will it take for a 6 watt charger to charge the same tablet ?",
        "answer": 53,
        "options": [
            53,
            76,
            78,
            95,
            64
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 21 watt charger charges a laptop in 23 minutes. How much time will it take for a 20 watt charger to charge the same laptop ?",
        "answer": 49,
        "options": [
            7,
            3,
            3,
            49,
            14
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 23 watt charger charges a airpods in 36 minutes. How much time will it take for a 9 watt charger to charge the same airpods ?",
        "answer": 47,
        "options": [
            17,
            26,
            15,
            10,
            47
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 23 watt charger charges a laptop in 23 minutes. How much time will it take for a 7 watt charger to charge the same laptop ?",
        "answer": 61,
        "options": [
            3,
            17,
            15,
            16,
            61
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 12 watt charger charges a powerbank in 32 minutes. How much time will it take for a 22 watt charger to charge the same powerbank ?",
        "answer": 31,
        "options": [
            93,
            51,
            57,
            31,
            99
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 20 watt charger charges a laptop in 29 minutes. How much time will it take for a 9 watt charger to charge the same laptop ?",
        "answer": 39,
        "options": [
            27,
            26,
            39,
            25,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 12 watt charger charges a airpods in 33 minutes. How much time will it take for a 3 watt charger to charge the same airpods ?",
        "answer": 62,
        "options": [
            3,
            15,
            62,
            1,
            24
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 30 watt charger charges a tablet in 41 minutes. How much time will it take for a 10 watt charger to charge the same tablet ?",
        "answer": 42,
        "options": [
            19,
            42,
            26,
            19,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 13 watt charger charges a laptop in 24 minutes. How much time will it take for a 14 watt charger to charge the same laptop ?",
        "answer": 20,
        "options": [
            35,
            63,
            43,
            20,
            94
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 29 watt charger charges a laptop in 45 minutes. How much time will it take for a 18 watt charger to charge the same laptop ?",
        "answer": 64,
        "options": [
            28,
            64,
            44,
            31,
            20
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 25 watt charger charges a tablet in 11 minutes. How much time will it take for a 11 watt charger to charge the same tablet ?",
        "answer": 67,
        "options": [
            67,
            6,
            2,
            10,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 25 watt charger charges a phone in 15 minutes. How much time will it take for a 4 watt charger to charge the same phone ?",
        "answer": 36,
        "options": [
            36,
            11,
            2,
            4,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 4 watt charger charges a laptop in 42 minutes. How much time will it take for a 22 watt charger to charge the same laptop ?",
        "answer": 26,
        "options": [
            87,
            71,
            59,
            26,
            67
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 14 watt charger charges a powerbank in 46 minutes. How much time will it take for a 10 watt charger to charge the same powerbank ?",
        "answer": 57,
        "options": [
            57,
            45,
            31,
            36,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 7 watt charger charges a powerbank in 33 minutes. How much time will it take for a 5 watt charger to charge the same powerbank ?",
        "answer": 45,
        "options": [
            9,
            7,
            45,
            14,
            29
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 3 watt charger charges a phone in 52 minutes. How much time will it take for a 19 watt charger to charge the same phone ?",
        "answer": 49,
        "options": [
            99,
            49,
            93,
            66,
            72
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A 24 watt charger charges a powerbank in 56 minutes. How much time will it take for a 20 watt charger to charge the same powerbank ?",
        "answer": 62,
        "options": [
            8,
            62,
            19,
            21,
            45
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 63, 38, 79. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "acute angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 41, 32, 107. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "obtuse angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 82, 43, 55. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "acute angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 82, 58, 40. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "acute angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 73, 57, 50. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "acute angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 57, 42, 81. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "acute angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 81, 48, 51. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "acute angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 63, 43, 74. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "acute angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 99, 48, 33. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "obtuse angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 97, 42, 41. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "obtuse angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 91, 53, 36. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "obtuse angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 57, 34, 89. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "acute angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 37, 44, 99. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "obtuse angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 57, 55, 68. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "acute angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 87, 60, 33. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "acute angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 96, 38, 46. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "obtuse angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 90, 49, 41. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "right angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 49, 47, 84. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "acute angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 82, 42, 56. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "acute angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 98, 57, 25. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "obtuse angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 67, 50, 63. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "acute angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 75, 41, 64. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "acute angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 79, 40, 61. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "acute angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 49, 52, 79. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "acute angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 38, 34, 108. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "obtuse angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 83, 46, 51. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "acute angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 97, 52, 31. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "obtuse angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 53, 46, 81. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "acute angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 71, 41, 68. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "acute angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 59, 30, 91. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "obtuse angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 60, 36, 84. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "acute angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 94, 51, 35. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "obtuse angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 62, 48, 70. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "acute angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 76, 57, 47. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "acute angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 77, 50, 53. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "acute angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 61, 43, 76. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "acute angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 42, 56, 82. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "acute angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 52, 37, 91. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "obtuse angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 96, 32, 52. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "obtuse angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 54, 34, 92. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "obtuse angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 78, 50, 52. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "acute angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 38, 31, 111. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "obtuse angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 59, 44, 77. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "acute angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 73, 30, 77. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "acute angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 99, 32, 49. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "obtuse angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 75, 41, 64. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "acute angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 32, 35, 113. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "obtuse angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 85, 40, 55. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "acute angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 84, 32, 64. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "acute angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The angles of an triangle are 84, 47, 49. What type of triangle is this one?",
        "answer": "acute angle triangle",
        "options": [
            "acute angle triangle,right angle triangle,obtuse angle triangle"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "There are 6 sides of a polygon. What type of polygon is this one?",
        "answer": "Hexagon",
        "options": [
            "Triangle,Rectangle,Pentagon,Hexagon,Heptagon,Octagon"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "There are 6 sides of a polygon. What type of polygon is this one?",
        "answer": "Hexagon",
        "options": [
            "Triangle,Rectangle,Pentagon,Hexagon,Heptagon,Octagon"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "There are 8 sides of a polygon. What type of polygon is this one?",
        "answer": "Octagon",
        "options": [
            "Triangle,Rectangle,Pentagon,Hexagon,Heptagon,Octagon"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "There are 6 sides of a polygon. What type of polygon is this one?",
        "answer": "Hexagon",
        "options": [
            "Triangle,Rectangle,Pentagon,Hexagon,Heptagon,Octagon"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "There are 8 sides of a polygon. What type of polygon is this one?",
        "answer": "Octagon",
        "options": [
            "Triangle,Rectangle,Pentagon,Hexagon,Heptagon,Octagon"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "There are 3 sides of a polygon. What type of polygon is this one?",
        "answer": "Traingle",
        "options": [
            "Triangle,Rectangle,Pentagon,Hexagon,Heptagon,Octagon"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "There are 8 sides of a polygon. What type of polygon is this one?",
        "answer": "Octagon",
        "options": [
            "Triangle,Rectangle,Pentagon,Hexagon,Heptagon,Octagon"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "There are 6 sides of a polygon. What type of polygon is this one?",
        "answer": "Hexagon",
        "options": [
            "Triangle,Rectangle,Pentagon,Hexagon,Heptagon,Octagon"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "There are 5 sides of a polygon. What type of polygon is this one?",
        "answer": "Pentagon",
        "options": [
            "Triangle,Rectangle,Pentagon,Hexagon,Heptagon,Octagon"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "There are 4 sides of a polygon. What type of polygon is this one?",
        "answer": "Rectangle",
        "options": [
            "Triangle,Rectangle,Pentagon,Hexagon,Heptagon,Octagon"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in wood ?",
        "answer": "3960",
        "options": [
            "185",
            "120",
            "148",
            "256",
            "3960"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in wood ?",
        "answer": "3960",
        "options": [
            "3960",
            "207",
            "272",
            "287",
            "331"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in wood ?",
        "answer": "3960",
        "options": [
            "213",
            "235",
            "140",
            "3960",
            "324"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in nickel ?",
        "answer": "6040",
        "options": [
            "136",
            "238",
            "6040",
            "102",
            "285"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in nylon ?",
        "answer": "2620",
        "options": [
            "134",
            "133",
            "2620",
            "205",
            "231"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in granite ?",
        "answer": "5950",
        "options": [
            "232",
            "5950",
            "177",
            "278",
            "174"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in glass light crown ?",
        "answer": "5100",
        "options": [
            "254",
            "276",
            "5100",
            "199",
            "135"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in gold ?",
        "answer": "3240",
        "options": [
            "257",
            "179",
            "3240",
            "288",
            "189"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in copper annealed ?",
        "answer": "4760",
        "options": [
            "307",
            "4760",
            "271",
            "136",
            "150"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in tantalium ?",
        "answer": "3350",
        "options": [
            "229",
            "3350",
            "262",
            "102",
            "282"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in drawn tungsten ?",
        "answer": "5410",
        "options": [
            "314",
            "106",
            "130",
            "5410",
            "205"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in magnesium annealed ?",
        "answer": "5770",
        "options": [
            "329",
            "288",
            "110",
            "5770",
            "188"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in iron electrolytic ?",
        "answer": "5950",
        "options": [
            "147",
            "320",
            "249",
            "284",
            "5950"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in lead rolled ?",
        "answer": "1960",
        "options": [
            "269",
            "1960",
            "148",
            "283",
            "233"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in drawn tungsten ?",
        "answer": "5410",
        "options": [
            "127",
            "204",
            "126",
            "5410",
            "142"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in Polystyrene ?",
        "answer": "2350",
        "options": [
            "251",
            "221",
            "2350",
            "305",
            "281"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in slate ?",
        "answer": "4510",
        "options": [
            "114",
            "326",
            "4510",
            "338",
            "122"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in titanium ?",
        "answer": "6070",
        "options": [
            "229",
            "171",
            "6070",
            "303",
            "196"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in tantalium ?",
        "answer": "3350",
        "options": [
            "313",
            "260",
            "160",
            "3350",
            "116"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in glass light crown ?",
        "answer": "5100",
        "options": [
            "134",
            "282",
            "5100",
            "179",
            "341"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in rubber neoprene ?",
        "answer": "1600",
        "options": [
            "180",
            "313",
            "320",
            "189",
            "1600"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in lucite ?",
        "answer": "2680",
        "options": [
            "238",
            "201",
            "129",
            "2680",
            "269"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in Bismut ?",
        "answer": "2180",
        "options": [
            "204",
            "2180",
            "245",
            "192",
            "144"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in Polyethylene ?",
        "answer": "1250",
        "options": [
            "1250",
            "278",
            "240",
            "225",
            "126"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in copper rolled ?",
        "answer": "5010",
        "options": [
            "256",
            "5010",
            "280",
            "147",
            "285"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in nylon ?",
        "answer": "2620",
        "options": [
            "2620",
            "152",
            "188",
            "336",
            "215"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in molybdenum ?",
        "answer": "6250",
        "options": [
            "128",
            "332",
            "201",
            "6250",
            "310"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in Beryllium ?",
        "answer": "12890",
        "options": [
            "329",
            "286",
            "305",
            "323",
            "12890"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in titanium ?",
        "answer": "6070",
        "options": [
            "332",
            "273",
            "226",
            "338",
            "6070"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in antimony ?",
        "answer": "3400",
        "options": [
            "302",
            "214",
            "251",
            "229",
            "3400"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in granite ?",
        "answer": "5950",
        "options": [
            "217",
            "283",
            "275",
            "165",
            "5950"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in silver ?",
        "answer": "3650",
        "options": [
            "3650",
            "138",
            "156",
            "136",
            "160"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in glass silicate flint ?",
        "answer": "3980",
        "options": [
            "105",
            "200",
            "118",
            "3980",
            "118"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in marbel ?",
        "answer": "3810",
        "options": [
            "263",
            "3810",
            "261",
            "139",
            "199"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in aluminium ?",
        "answer": "6420",
        "options": [
            "332",
            "212",
            "109",
            "6420",
            "248"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in glass ?",
        "answer": "5640",
        "options": [
            "166",
            "185",
            "326",
            "5640",
            "203"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in ivory ?",
        "answer": "3010",
        "options": [
            "107",
            "3010",
            "170",
            "184",
            "301"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in annealed tungsten ?",
        "answer": "5220",
        "options": [
            "277",
            "271",
            "111",
            "120",
            "5220"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in glass pyrex ?",
        "answer": "5640",
        "options": [
            "117",
            "163",
            "5640",
            "276",
            "153"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in copper rolled ?",
        "answer": "5010",
        "options": [
            "225",
            "5010",
            "166",
            "285",
            "272"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in Bismut ?",
        "answer": "2180",
        "options": [
            "100",
            "269",
            "273",
            "2180",
            "278"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in marbel ?",
        "answer": "3810",
        "options": [
            "130",
            "117",
            "185",
            "314",
            "3810"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in ivory ?",
        "answer": "3010",
        "options": [
            "133",
            "240",
            "3010",
            "132",
            "274"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in silver ?",
        "answer": "3650",
        "options": [
            "261",
            "240",
            "3650",
            "129",
            "316"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in lead annealed ?",
        "answer": "2160",
        "options": [
            "201",
            "177",
            "313",
            "182",
            "2160"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in iron electrolytic ?",
        "answer": "5950",
        "options": [
            "124",
            "272",
            "138",
            "5950",
            "109"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in Polystyrene ?",
        "answer": "2350",
        "options": [
            "211",
            "299",
            "2350",
            "254",
            "256"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in glass light crown ?",
        "answer": "5100",
        "options": [
            "163",
            "5100",
            "319",
            "181",
            "222"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in Polystyrene ?",
        "answer": "2350",
        "options": [
            "175",
            "301",
            "2350",
            "108",
            "101"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in copper rolled ?",
        "answer": "5010",
        "options": [
            "170",
            "5010",
            "212",
            "240",
            "166"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in lead rolled ?",
        "answer": "1960",
        "options": [
            "1960",
            "143",
            "145",
            "334",
            "227"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in annealed tungsten ?",
        "answer": "5220",
        "options": [
            "330",
            "329",
            "338",
            "222",
            "5220"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in molybdenum ?",
        "answer": "6250",
        "options": [
            "6250",
            "323",
            "113",
            "102",
            "227"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in manganese ?",
        "answer": "4660",
        "options": [
            "183",
            "327",
            "290",
            "239",
            "4660"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in monel ?",
        "answer": "5350",
        "options": [
            "110",
            "5350",
            "282",
            "322",
            "302"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in nylon ?",
        "answer": "2620",
        "options": [
            "130",
            "199",
            "248",
            "203",
            "2620"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in marbel ?",
        "answer": "3810",
        "options": [
            "178",
            "255",
            "3810",
            "101",
            "268"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in copper rolled ?",
        "answer": "5010",
        "options": [
            "164",
            "5010",
            "128",
            "307",
            "166"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in granite ?",
        "answer": "5950",
        "options": [
            "208",
            "209",
            "182",
            "5950",
            "142"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in Beryllium ?",
        "answer": "12890",
        "options": [
            "101",
            "201",
            "207",
            "124",
            "12890"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in stainless steel ?",
        "answer": "5790",
        "options": [
            "154",
            "169",
            "257",
            "5790",
            "180"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in silver ?",
        "answer": "3650",
        "options": [
            "3650",
            "212",
            "132",
            "196",
            "221"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in glass light crown ?",
        "answer": "5100",
        "options": [
            "5100",
            "339",
            "256",
            "175",
            "180"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in granite ?",
        "answer": "5950",
        "options": [
            "122",
            "242",
            "120",
            "5950",
            "108"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in iridium ?",
        "answer": "4790",
        "options": [
            "298",
            "196",
            "242",
            "4790",
            "109"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in copper rolled ?",
        "answer": "5010",
        "options": [
            "5010",
            "212",
            "161",
            "282",
            "261"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in tantalium ?",
        "answer": "3350",
        "options": [
            "185",
            "3350",
            "318",
            "183",
            "299"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in tungsten carbide ?",
        "answer": "6655",
        "options": [
            "200",
            "6655",
            "150",
            "290",
            "239"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in cadmium ?",
        "answer": "2780",
        "options": [
            "268",
            "173",
            "2780",
            "238",
            "295"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in glass ?",
        "answer": "5640",
        "options": [
            "5640",
            "298",
            "325",
            "205",
            "170"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in rubber butyl ?",
        "answer": "1830",
        "options": [
            "327",
            "202",
            "142",
            "299",
            "1830"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in iron cast ?",
        "answer": "4994",
        "options": [
            "118",
            "4994",
            "246",
            "143",
            "108"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in nickel ?",
        "answer": "6040",
        "options": [
            "6040",
            "324",
            "141",
            "281",
            "180"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in slate ?",
        "answer": "4510",
        "options": [
            "340",
            "4510",
            "194",
            "113",
            "277"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in lead annealed ?",
        "answer": "2160",
        "options": [
            "301",
            "149",
            "322",
            "336",
            "2160"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in Polyethylene ?",
        "answer": "1250",
        "options": [
            "169",
            "192",
            "1250",
            "101",
            "228"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in lead annealed ?",
        "answer": "2160",
        "options": [
            "241",
            "295",
            "135",
            "260",
            "2160"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in lucite ?",
        "answer": "2680",
        "options": [
            "263",
            "220",
            "2680",
            "221",
            "156"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in glass ?",
        "answer": "5640",
        "options": [
            "5640",
            "110",
            "224",
            "220",
            "327"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in slate ?",
        "answer": "4510",
        "options": [
            "289",
            "156",
            "309",
            "4510",
            "153"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in Brick ?",
        "answer": "4200",
        "options": [
            "188",
            "4200",
            "130",
            "264",
            "325"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in Beryllium ?",
        "answer": "12890",
        "options": [
            "197",
            "178",
            "275",
            "101",
            "12890"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in granite ?",
        "answer": "5950",
        "options": [
            "106",
            "190",
            "329",
            "5950",
            "211"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in drawn tungsten ?",
        "answer": "5410",
        "options": [
            "334",
            "217",
            "340",
            "5410",
            "317"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in iron electrolytic ?",
        "answer": "5950",
        "options": [
            "149",
            "237",
            "165",
            "5950",
            "280"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in iron electrolytic ?",
        "answer": "5950",
        "options": [
            "291",
            "283",
            "109",
            "5950",
            "156"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in Brick ?",
        "answer": "4200",
        "options": [
            "168",
            "332",
            "160",
            "191",
            "4200"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in Brass ?",
        "answer": "4700",
        "options": [
            "324",
            "179",
            "243",
            "287",
            "4700"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in glass ?",
        "answer": "5640",
        "options": [
            "207",
            "262",
            "143",
            "5640",
            "202"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in aluminium ?",
        "answer": "6420",
        "options": [
            "205",
            "265",
            "319",
            "236",
            "6420"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in tantalium ?",
        "answer": "3350",
        "options": [
            "100",
            "314",
            "3350",
            "298",
            "283"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in glass light crown ?",
        "answer": "5100",
        "options": [
            "158",
            "200",
            "112",
            "5100",
            "287"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in diamond ?",
        "answer": "12000",
        "options": [
            "12000",
            "259",
            "299",
            "269",
            "161"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in lucite ?",
        "answer": "2680",
        "options": [
            "175",
            "272",
            "2680",
            "246",
            "168"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in tantalium ?",
        "answer": "3350",
        "options": [
            "106",
            "267",
            "104",
            "145",
            "3350"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in rubber gum ?",
        "answer": "1550",
        "options": [
            "170",
            "133",
            "263",
            "1550",
            "329"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in marbel ?",
        "answer": "3810",
        "options": [
            "3810",
            "195",
            "185",
            "318",
            "240"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in nickel ?",
        "answer": "6040",
        "options": [
            "302",
            "198",
            "175",
            "6040",
            "213"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in tin rolled ?",
        "answer": "3320",
        "options": [
            "132",
            "310",
            "3320",
            "263",
            "102"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels faster in denser medium than air. What is the speed of sound in Polystyrene ?",
        "answer": "2350",
        "options": [
            "190",
            "2350",
            "272",
            "174",
            "207"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Eduardo is younger than Harry by 4 years. 7 years ago Harry was 30 years old. What is Eduardo 's age today?",
        "answer": 33,
        "options": [
            "55",
            "33",
            "56",
            "48",
            "52"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Pablo is younger than Crosby by 5 years. 10 years ago Crosby was 29 years old. What is Pablo 's age today?",
        "answer": 34,
        "options": [
            "49",
            "49",
            "64",
            "34",
            "54"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Kamden is younger than Morgan by 2 years. 7 years ago Morgan was 35 years old. What is Kamden 's age today?",
        "answer": 40,
        "options": [
            "51",
            "40",
            "53",
            "48",
            "62"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Luca is younger than Edison by 1 years. 15 years ago Edison was 31 years old. What is Luca 's age today?",
        "answer": 45,
        "options": [
            "49",
            "64",
            "45",
            "47",
            "62"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ivan is younger than Roy by 3 years. 8 years ago Roy was 35 years old. What is Ivan 's age today?",
        "answer": 40,
        "options": [
            "62",
            "40",
            "68",
            "57",
            "49"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Tyson is younger than Gatlin by 2 years. 6 years ago Gatlin was 33 years old. What is Tyson 's age today?",
        "answer": 37,
        "options": [
            "51",
            "45",
            "37",
            "51",
            "47"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Nicholas is younger than Turner by 3 years. 14 years ago Turner was 27 years old. What is Nicholas 's age today?",
        "answer": 38,
        "options": [
            "75",
            "38",
            "47",
            "50",
            "50"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Princeton is younger than Toby by 5 years. 11 years ago Toby was 32 years old. What is Princeton 's age today?",
        "answer": 38,
        "options": [
            "59",
            "53",
            "64",
            "38",
            "75"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Luciano is younger than Davion by 5 years. 15 years ago Davion was 28 years old. What is Luciano 's age today?",
        "answer": 38,
        "options": [
            "83",
            "58",
            "73",
            "38",
            "58"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Joshua is younger than Wilder by 3 years. 14 years ago Wilder was 26 years old. What is Joshua 's age today?",
        "answer": 37,
        "options": [
            "57",
            "63",
            "43",
            "37",
            "49"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Emiliano is younger than Duke by 3 years. 7 years ago Duke was 28 years old. What is Emiliano 's age today?",
        "answer": 32,
        "options": [
            "52",
            "45",
            "51",
            "32",
            "45"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alejandro is younger than Leighton by 2 years. 15 years ago Leighton was 33 years old. What is Alejandro 's age today?",
        "answer": 46,
        "options": [
            "46",
            "52",
            "54",
            "54",
            "54"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Justin is younger than Koa by 3 years. 15 years ago Koa was 27 years old. What is Justin 's age today?",
        "answer": 39,
        "options": [
            "48",
            "39",
            "48",
            "75",
            "63"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Fabian is younger than Gibson by 1 years. 8 years ago Gibson was 27 years old. What is Fabian 's age today?",
        "answer": 34,
        "options": [
            "54",
            "37",
            "52",
            "34",
            "38"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Henry is younger than Aryan by 3 years. 11 years ago Aryan was 29 years old. What is Henry 's age today?",
        "answer": 37,
        "options": [
            "68",
            "37",
            "49",
            "71",
            "68"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jensen is younger than Izaiah by 3 years. 5 years ago Izaiah was 33 years old. What is Jensen 's age today?",
        "answer": 35,
        "options": [
            "52",
            "51",
            "46",
            "35",
            "51"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Nikolai is younger than Dash by 4 years. 7 years ago Dash was 30 years old. What is Nikolai 's age today?",
        "answer": 33,
        "options": [
            "55",
            "33",
            "63",
            "52",
            "41"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Hank is younger than Leroy by 2 years. 12 years ago Leroy was 35 years old. What is Hank 's age today?",
        "answer": 45,
        "options": [
            "77",
            "65",
            "51",
            "61",
            "45"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Tyson is younger than Tadeo by 3 years. 10 years ago Tadeo was 28 years old. What is Tyson 's age today?",
        "answer": 35,
        "options": [
            "35",
            "57",
            "54",
            "47",
            "54"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Mark is younger than Azariah by 5 years. 7 years ago Azariah was 35 years old. What is Mark 's age today?",
        "answer": 37,
        "options": [
            "71",
            "59",
            "71",
            "37",
            "57"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Avery is younger than Westin by 1 years. 11 years ago Westin was 32 years old. What is Avery 's age today?",
        "answer": 42,
        "options": [
            "56",
            "55",
            "56",
            "42",
            "57"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Romeo is younger than Gustavo by 2 years. 12 years ago Gustavo was 30 years old. What is Romeo 's age today?",
        "answer": 40,
        "options": [
            "40",
            "46",
            "72",
            "44",
            "72"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Theo is younger than Nova by 2 years. 15 years ago Nova was 35 years old. What is Theo 's age today?",
        "answer": 48,
        "options": [
            "48",
            "71",
            "67",
            "86",
            "54"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Joaquin is younger than Ulises by 2 years. 7 years ago Ulises was 31 years old. What is Joaquin 's age today?",
        "answer": 36,
        "options": [
            "54",
            "49",
            "40",
            "36",
            "40"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Grayson is younger than Toby by 3 years. 15 years ago Toby was 30 years old. What is Grayson 's age today?",
        "answer": 42,
        "options": [
            "42",
            "69",
            "84",
            "78",
            "51"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Hayes is younger than Kendall by 5 years. 12 years ago Kendall was 29 years old. What is Hayes 's age today?",
        "answer": 36,
        "options": [
            "63",
            "80",
            "56",
            "36",
            "75"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "August is younger than Konnor by 4 years. 10 years ago Konnor was 31 years old. What is August 's age today?",
        "answer": 37,
        "options": [
            "65",
            "69",
            "55",
            "37",
            "63"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Knox is younger than Franco by 3 years. 6 years ago Franco was 34 years old. What is Knox 's age today?",
        "answer": 37,
        "options": [
            "58",
            "37",
            "46",
            "52",
            "55"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Hank is younger than Lance by 2 years. 6 years ago Lance was 30 years old. What is Hank 's age today?",
        "answer": 34,
        "options": [
            "42",
            "54",
            "34",
            "38",
            "50"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Damian is younger than Elon by 1 years. 7 years ago Elon was 26 years old. What is Damian 's age today?",
        "answer": 32,
        "options": [
            "35",
            "34",
            "50",
            "32",
            "48"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Micah is younger than Heath by 2 years. 15 years ago Heath was 31 years old. What is Micah 's age today?",
        "answer": 44,
        "options": [
            "52",
            "44",
            "67",
            "78",
            "82"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ayden is younger than Dakari by 2 years. 11 years ago Dakari was 33 years old. What is Ayden 's age today?",
        "answer": 42,
        "options": [
            "57",
            "59",
            "42",
            "61",
            "70"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Brian is younger than Layton by 5 years. 12 years ago Layton was 26 years old. What is Brian 's age today?",
        "answer": 33,
        "options": [
            "67",
            "48",
            "33",
            "67",
            "48"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jordan is younger than Harley by 4 years. 15 years ago Harley was 34 years old. What is Jordan 's age today?",
        "answer": 45,
        "options": [
            "45",
            "68",
            "91",
            "91",
            "53"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Joel is younger than Ulises by 5 years. 8 years ago Ulises was 31 years old. What is Joel 's age today?",
        "answer": 34,
        "options": [
            "52",
            "70",
            "60",
            "70",
            "34"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Chase is younger than Caspian by 3 years. 8 years ago Caspian was 31 years old. What is Chase 's age today?",
        "answer": 36,
        "options": [
            "36",
            "61",
            "48",
            "61",
            "42"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ricardo is younger than Reyansh by 3 years. 7 years ago Reyansh was 26 years old. What is Ricardo 's age today?",
        "answer": 30,
        "options": [
            "53",
            "46",
            "36",
            "30",
            "50"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Phillip is younger than Misael by 3 years. 11 years ago Misael was 33 years old. What is Phillip 's age today?",
        "answer": 41,
        "options": [
            "69",
            "58",
            "75",
            "41",
            "47"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Emanuel is younger than Mauricio by 2 years. 10 years ago Mauricio was 35 years old. What is Emanuel 's age today?",
        "answer": 43,
        "options": [
            "67",
            "71",
            "47",
            "43",
            "61"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Edward is younger than Maurice by 4 years. 9 years ago Maurice was 26 years old. What is Edward 's age today?",
        "answer": 31,
        "options": [
            "56",
            "56",
            "48",
            "47",
            "31"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Weston is younger than Mordechai by 4 years. 7 years ago Mordechai was 33 years old. What is Weston 's age today?",
        "answer": 36,
        "options": [
            "58",
            "36",
            "59",
            "52",
            "44"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Max is younger than Reginald by 5 years. 12 years ago Reginald was 27 years old. What is Max 's age today?",
        "answer": 34,
        "options": [
            "66",
            "34",
            "56",
            "78",
            "56"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Porter is younger than Alessandro by 3 years. 9 years ago Alessandro was 33 years old. What is Porter 's age today?",
        "answer": 39,
        "options": [
            "69",
            "39",
            "45",
            "54",
            "57"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jaxton is younger than Zavier by 3 years. 13 years ago Zavier was 25 years old. What is Jaxton 's age today?",
        "answer": 35,
        "options": [
            "57",
            "73",
            "35",
            "54",
            "73"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "William is younger than Mustafa by 2 years. 10 years ago Mustafa was 29 years old. What is William 's age today?",
        "answer": 37,
        "options": [
            "65",
            "37",
            "41",
            "45",
            "43"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ari is younger than Karsyn by 4 years. 15 years ago Karsyn was 27 years old. What is Ari 's age today?",
        "answer": 38,
        "options": [
            "76",
            "38",
            "46",
            "46",
            "46"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Brian is younger than Kyree by 3 years. 7 years ago Kyree was 30 years old. What is Brian 's age today?",
        "answer": 34,
        "options": [
            "34",
            "53",
            "40",
            "43",
            "40"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "August is younger than Mohammad by 3 years. 9 years ago Mohammad was 34 years old. What is August 's age today?",
        "answer": 40,
        "options": [
            "40",
            "58",
            "61",
            "49",
            "64"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Gunnar is younger than Layton by 2 years. 5 years ago Layton was 31 years old. What is Gunnar 's age today?",
        "answer": 34,
        "options": [
            "52",
            "48",
            "48",
            "34",
            "40"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Rhys is younger than Franco by 3 years. 13 years ago Franco was 33 years old. What is Rhys 's age today?",
        "answer": 43,
        "options": [
            "78",
            "52",
            "75",
            "75",
            "43"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 420 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 1680,
        "options": [
            "1680",
            2100,
            4200,
            2100,
            3360
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 322 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 1288,
        "options": [
            "1288",
            1610,
            1932,
            2898,
            1932
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 397 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 1588,
        "options": [
            1985,
            "1588",
            2779,
            3176,
            2382
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 565 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 2260,
        "options": [
            3390,
            5650,
            "2260",
            3390,
            5085
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 700 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 2800,
        "options": [
            "2800",
            4900,
            4900,
            4200,
            4200
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 668 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 2672,
        "options": [
            6680,
            6012,
            "2672",
            5344,
            6680
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 196 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 784,
        "options": [
            1568,
            "784",
            980,
            1176,
            1372
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 626 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 2504,
        "options": [
            3756,
            4382,
            4382,
            "2504",
            6260
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 552 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 2208,
        "options": [
            4416,
            3864,
            3864,
            "2208",
            2760
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 734 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 2936,
        "options": [
            "2936",
            5872,
            4404,
            5138,
            6606
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 856 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 3424,
        "options": [
            6848,
            7704,
            "3424",
            8560,
            5992
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 12 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 48,
        "options": [
            84,
            "48",
            108,
            108,
            60
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 534 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 2136,
        "options": [
            3204,
            5340,
            "2136",
            3204,
            3204
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 204 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 816,
        "options": [
            "816",
            1428,
            1632,
            1020,
            1632
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 176 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 704,
        "options": [
            1760,
            1760,
            1232,
            "704",
            1232
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 387 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 1548,
        "options": [
            1935,
            3870,
            3096,
            3096,
            "1548"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 354 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 1416,
        "options": [
            3186,
            1770,
            3540,
            2124,
            "1416"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 15 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 60,
        "options": [
            "60",
            150,
            75,
            150,
            105
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 551 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 2204,
        "options": [
            4959,
            4408,
            5510,
            4959,
            "2204"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 446 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 1784,
        "options": [
            4014,
            2230,
            4014,
            "1784",
            3122
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 266 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 1064,
        "options": [
            "1064",
            1596,
            1330,
            1596,
            2128
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 302 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 1208,
        "options": [
            1812,
            2114,
            2416,
            2114,
            "1208"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 955 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 3820,
        "options": [
            "3820",
            8595,
            7640,
            7640,
            9550
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 173 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 692,
        "options": [
            "692",
            1384,
            1730,
            1730,
            1557
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 740 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 2960,
        "options": [
            "2960",
            3700,
            6660,
            4440,
            5920
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 634 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 2536,
        "options": [
            "2536",
            3170,
            3804,
            6340,
            3170
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 350 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 1400,
        "options": [
            2100,
            2800,
            "1400",
            1750,
            1750
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 461 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 1844,
        "options": [
            3227,
            4149,
            2305,
            "1844",
            3688
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 231 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 924,
        "options": [
            2310,
            1848,
            1617,
            "924",
            1386
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 174 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 696,
        "options": [
            870,
            1392,
            "696",
            1740,
            1566
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 754 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 3016,
        "options": [
            5278,
            4524,
            6786,
            3770,
            "3016"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 693 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 2772,
        "options": [
            6237,
            6237,
            "2772",
            3465,
            6930
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 349 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 1396,
        "options": [
            2792,
            2792,
            3490,
            "1396",
            3490
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 334 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 1336,
        "options": [
            "1336",
            2338,
            2338,
            3340,
            2004
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 709 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 2836,
        "options": [
            "2836",
            4254,
            3545,
            7090,
            5672
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 215 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 860,
        "options": [
            1290,
            2150,
            2150,
            "860",
            1720
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 387 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 1548,
        "options": [
            3096,
            1935,
            "1548",
            2322,
            3870
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 945 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 3780,
        "options": [
            9450,
            4725,
            7560,
            "3780",
            6615
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 736 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 2944,
        "options": [
            5152,
            "2944",
            4416,
            5152,
            5888
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 848 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 3392,
        "options": [
            7632,
            8480,
            "3392",
            4240,
            5088
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 227 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 908,
        "options": [
            1816,
            "908",
            1589,
            2043,
            1135
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 803 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 3212,
        "options": [
            8030,
            8030,
            8030,
            "3212",
            6424
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 628 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 2512,
        "options": [
            5652,
            5652,
            "2512",
            3140,
            3768
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 756 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 3024,
        "options": [
            5292,
            "3024",
            6804,
            3780,
            7560
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 249 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 996,
        "options": [
            1992,
            2490,
            1992,
            "996",
            1992
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 397 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 1588,
        "options": [
            2382,
            3573,
            1985,
            1985,
            "1588"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 11 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 44,
        "options": [
            110,
            "44",
            110,
            66,
            66
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 268 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 1072,
        "options": [
            2412,
            2680,
            1340,
            "1072",
            2412
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 892 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 3568,
        "options": [
            8920,
            "3568",
            5352,
            4460,
            5352
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The side of an square is 733 . What is the perimeter of the square?",
        "answer": 2932,
        "options": [
            6597,
            5864,
            5864,
            "2932",
            5131
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "William is older than Noah by 3 years. 11 years ago Noah was 25 years old. What is William 's age today?",
        "answer": 39,
        "options": [
            "41",
            "39",
            "44",
            "55",
            "44"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "James is older than James by 5 years. 6 years ago James was 25 years old. What is James 's age today?",
        "answer": 36,
        "options": [
            "38",
            "27",
            "38",
            "33",
            "36"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Oliver is older than Noah by 4 years. 10 years ago Noah was 30 years old. What is Oliver 's age today?",
        "answer": 44,
        "options": [
            "46",
            "48",
            "32",
            "56",
            "44"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Liam is older than Oliver by 4 years. 15 years ago Oliver was 35 years old. What is Liam 's age today?",
        "answer": 54,
        "options": [
            "76",
            "54",
            "76",
            "42",
            "57"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Noah is older than William by 1 years. 6 years ago William was 29 years old. What is Noah 's age today?",
        "answer": 36,
        "options": [
            "45",
            "44",
            "32",
            "36",
            "32"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Noah is older than Benjamin by 3 years. 10 years ago Benjamin was 35 years old. What is Noah 's age today?",
        "answer": 48,
        "options": [
            "62",
            "62",
            "46",
            "48",
            "36"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Oliver is older than William by 1 years. 6 years ago William was 34 years old. What is Oliver 's age today?",
        "answer": 41,
        "options": [
            "39",
            "41",
            "49",
            "45",
            "50"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Oliver is older than Oliver by 2 years. 13 years ago Oliver was 34 years old. What is Oliver 's age today?",
        "answer": 49,
        "options": [
            "56",
            "49",
            "43",
            "58",
            "54"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Benjamin is older than Noah by 3 years. 9 years ago Noah was 31 years old. What is Benjamin 's age today?",
        "answer": 43,
        "options": [
            "49",
            "52",
            "43",
            "31",
            "52"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Oliver is older than James by 1 years. 5 years ago James was 26 years old. What is Oliver 's age today?",
        "answer": 32,
        "options": [
            "34",
            "30",
            "30",
            "32",
            "39"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Noah is older than Noah by 1 years. 7 years ago Noah was 29 years old. What is Noah 's age today?",
        "answer": 37,
        "options": [
            "37",
            "47",
            "34",
            "42",
            "49"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Oliver is older than Noah by 5 years. 14 years ago Noah was 27 years old. What is Oliver 's age today?",
        "answer": 46,
        "options": [
            "31",
            "36",
            "54",
            "46",
            "50"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Noah is older than Benjamin by 2 years. 12 years ago Benjamin was 30 years old. What is Noah 's age today?",
        "answer": 44,
        "options": [
            "40",
            "38",
            "36",
            "48",
            "44"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Noah is older than Oliver by 3 years. 9 years ago Oliver was 34 years old. What is Noah 's age today?",
        "answer": 46,
        "options": [
            "49",
            "46",
            "49",
            "49",
            "46"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "William is older than Liam by 3 years. 11 years ago Liam was 25 years old. What is William 's age today?",
        "answer": 39,
        "options": [
            "38",
            "41",
            "27",
            "38",
            "39"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "James is older than William by 1 years. 5 years ago William was 32 years old. What is James 's age today?",
        "answer": 38,
        "options": [
            "39",
            "39",
            "40",
            "38",
            "34"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Benjamin is older than James by 4 years. 7 years ago James was 29 years old. What is Benjamin 's age today?",
        "answer": 40,
        "options": [
            "35",
            "31",
            "38",
            "42",
            "40"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Benjamin is older than Liam by 1 years. 7 years ago Liam was 33 years old. What is Benjamin 's age today?",
        "answer": 41,
        "options": [
            "41",
            "44",
            "53",
            "46",
            "44"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "William is older than Liam by 1 years. 8 years ago Liam was 25 years old. What is William 's age today?",
        "answer": 34,
        "options": [
            "31",
            "48",
            "31",
            "34",
            "46"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Liam is older than Noah by 2 years. 5 years ago Noah was 31 years old. What is Liam 's age today?",
        "answer": 38,
        "options": [
            "40",
            "40",
            "37",
            "37",
            "38"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "James is older than James by 1 years. 5 years ago James was 32 years old. What is James 's age today?",
        "answer": 38,
        "options": [
            "40",
            "46",
            "35",
            "38",
            "34"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Noah is older than Noah by 3 years. 13 years ago Noah was 27 years old. What is Noah 's age today?",
        "answer": 43,
        "options": [
            "47",
            "43",
            "31",
            "47",
            "50"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Oliver is older than Noah by 3 years. 8 years ago Noah was 33 years old. What is Oliver 's age today?",
        "answer": 44,
        "options": [
            "48",
            "44",
            "38",
            "40",
            "32"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Liam is older than James by 3 years. 15 years ago James was 25 years old. What is Liam 's age today?",
        "answer": 43,
        "options": [
            "49",
            "43",
            "37",
            "67",
            "49"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Benjamin is older than Oliver by 4 years. 13 years ago Oliver was 30 years old. What is Benjamin 's age today?",
        "answer": 47,
        "options": [
            "35",
            "61",
            "61",
            "31",
            "47"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "James is older than Liam by 2 years. 6 years ago Liam was 35 years old. What is James 's age today?",
        "answer": 43,
        "options": [
            "47",
            "47",
            "43",
            "51",
            "49"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Oliver is older than Oliver by 5 years. 11 years ago Oliver was 32 years old. What is Oliver 's age today?",
        "answer": 48,
        "options": [
            "44",
            "48",
            "55",
            "55",
            "39"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Oliver is older than Noah by 3 years. 13 years ago Noah was 35 years old. What is Oliver 's age today?",
        "answer": 51,
        "options": [
            "45",
            "45",
            "45",
            "51",
            "58"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Oliver is older than William by 3 years. 8 years ago William was 33 years old. What is Oliver 's age today?",
        "answer": 44,
        "options": [
            "43",
            "44",
            "40",
            "35",
            "35"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "James is older than Liam by 3 years. 7 years ago Liam was 25 years old. What is James 's age today?",
        "answer": 35,
        "options": [
            "23",
            "33",
            "43",
            "35",
            "43"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "William is older than Oliver by 4 years. 11 years ago Oliver was 34 years old. What is William 's age today?",
        "answer": 49,
        "options": [
            "37",
            "49",
            "63",
            "37",
            "37"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "James is older than Oliver by 5 years. 10 years ago Oliver was 29 years old. What is James 's age today?",
        "answer": 44,
        "options": [
            "54",
            "44",
            "44",
            "54",
            "44"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Liam is older than James by 5 years. 5 years ago James was 29 years old. What is Liam 's age today?",
        "answer": 39,
        "options": [
            "34",
            "39",
            "34",
            "39",
            "34"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Noah is older than Benjamin by 4 years. 10 years ago Benjamin was 33 years old. What is Noah 's age today?",
        "answer": 47,
        "options": [
            "39",
            "55",
            "39",
            "49",
            "47"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Benjamin is older than Oliver by 1 years. 12 years ago Oliver was 25 years old. What is Benjamin 's age today?",
        "answer": 38,
        "options": [
            "60",
            "36",
            "60",
            "38",
            "59"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Noah is older than Benjamin by 3 years. 13 years ago Benjamin was 35 years old. What is Noah 's age today?",
        "answer": 51,
        "options": [
            "39",
            "65",
            "58",
            "51",
            "39"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Benjamin is older than Noah by 3 years. 8 years ago Noah was 30 years old. What is Benjamin 's age today?",
        "answer": 41,
        "options": [
            "35",
            "43",
            "29",
            "40",
            "41"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Benjamin is older than Benjamin by 3 years. 15 years ago Benjamin was 34 years old. What is Benjamin 's age today?",
        "answer": 52,
        "options": [
            "52",
            "46",
            "46",
            "43",
            "43"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Noah is older than Noah by 4 years. 12 years ago Noah was 30 years old. What is Noah 's age today?",
        "answer": 46,
        "options": [
            "50",
            "58",
            "46",
            "50",
            "42"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Liam is older than Oliver by 5 years. 12 years ago Oliver was 32 years old. What is Liam 's age today?",
        "answer": 49,
        "options": [
            "49",
            "39",
            "51",
            "63",
            "63"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Benjamin is older than James by 1 years. 14 years ago James was 25 years old. What is Benjamin 's age today?",
        "answer": 40,
        "options": [
            "38",
            "37",
            "40",
            "66",
            "37"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Oliver is older than Liam by 1 years. 13 years ago Liam was 29 years old. What is Oliver 's age today?",
        "answer": 43,
        "options": [
            "40",
            "40",
            "41",
            "43",
            "39"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "William is older than William by 3 years. 12 years ago William was 25 years old. What is William 's age today?",
        "answer": 40,
        "options": [
            "40",
            "52",
            "52",
            "52",
            "28"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Benjamin is older than Benjamin by 4 years. 13 years ago Benjamin was 25 years old. What is Benjamin 's age today?",
        "answer": 42,
        "options": [
            "52",
            "42",
            "56",
            "34",
            "47"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Oliver is older than Benjamin by 2 years. 6 years ago Benjamin was 29 years old. What is Oliver 's age today?",
        "answer": 37,
        "options": [
            "45",
            "37",
            "37",
            "39",
            "37"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Liam is older than Noah by 2 years. 11 years ago Noah was 35 years old. What is Liam 's age today?",
        "answer": 48,
        "options": [
            "53",
            "48",
            "42",
            "66",
            "66"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Benjamin is older than Oliver by 5 years. 7 years ago Oliver was 26 years old. What is Benjamin 's age today?",
        "answer": 38,
        "options": [
            "18",
            "35",
            "23",
            "42",
            "38"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "James is older than James by 1 years. 15 years ago James was 25 years old. What is James 's age today?",
        "answer": 41,
        "options": [
            "54",
            "39",
            "54",
            "67",
            "41"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Benjamin is older than Liam by 4 years. 13 years ago Liam was 34 years old. What is Benjamin 's age today?",
        "answer": 51,
        "options": [
            "51",
            "43",
            "35",
            "56",
            "69"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "William is older than Noah by 2 years. 14 years ago Noah was 29 years old. What is William 's age today?",
        "answer": 45,
        "options": [
            "51",
            "67",
            "45",
            "55",
            "65"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean height of the set of given human ? 10 47 2 5 43 28 32 15 41 4 41 30 10 8 37 1 2 26 40 28 32 10 10 10 17 28 39 8 13 31 22 47 38 3 41 15 3 14 8 22 ",
        "answer": "21.52",
        "options": [
            "64.56",
            "64.56",
            "107.60",
            "86.08",
            "21.52"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean length of the set of given cats ? 2 40 5 2 17 28 6 23 46 44 48 2 27 33 19 31 44 17 35 36 46 34 24 21 26 8 7 33 1 24 39 35 4 25 34 18 16 21 8 14 45 29 17 ",
        "answer": "24.05",
        "options": [
            "96.20",
            "96.20",
            "48.10",
            "72.15",
            "24.05"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean weight of the set of given kangaroos ? 46 39 35 7 50 21 16 16 14 27 6 28 44 7 36 13 32 50 10 44 17 28 3 36 46 31 4 30 48 37 48 17 1 3 26 37 36 27 44 38 15 23 6 2 2 5 46 21 34 ",
        "answer": "25.55",
        "options": [
            "102.20",
            "102.20",
            "76.65",
            "25.55",
            "76.65"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean length of the set of given cats ? 30 48 32 31 5 ",
        "answer": "29.20",
        "options": [
            "29.20",
            "87.60",
            "87.60",
            "87.60",
            "87.60"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean weight of the set of given elephants ? 49 35 2 7 9 49 25 37 1 ",
        "answer": "23.78",
        "options": [
            "23.78",
            "118.90",
            "118.90",
            "71.34",
            "118.90"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean height of the set of given martians ? 28 37 20 5 37 27 4 18 47 2 31 13 43 24 26 12 8 2 32 2 31 39 5 42 ",
        "answer": "22.29",
        "options": [
            "44.58",
            "89.16",
            "89.16",
            "22.29",
            "89.16"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean weight of the set of given tigers ? 16 22 15 27 20 12 23 25 25 8 50 48 8 46 14 32 25 38 14 ",
        "answer": "24.63",
        "options": [
            "123.15",
            "73.89",
            "73.89",
            "98.52",
            "24.63"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean area of the set of given elephants ? 15 7 36 15 29 36 6 30 3 41 6 40 50 6 13 4 35 9 5 22 50 16 14 46 20 38 35 29 15 1 11 ",
        "answer": "22.03",
        "options": [
            "88.12",
            "22.03",
            "88.12",
            "66.09",
            "44.06"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean size of the set of given cats ? 25 39 5 45 43 12 44 4 6 23 19 18 34 39 50 35 50 38 47 16 18 48 9 8 15 6 ",
        "answer": "26.77",
        "options": [
            "26.77",
            "107.08",
            "80.31",
            "53.54",
            "53.54"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean size of the set of given dogs ? 50 17 14 33 26 8 38 36 48 26 5 7 9 14 42 42 35 44 22 45 29 48 14 37 37 11 18 27 ",
        "answer": "27.93",
        "options": [
            "111.72",
            "55.86",
            "27.93",
            "111.72",
            "111.72"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean height of the set of given cats ? 26 13 20 18 13 4 17 45 23 4 38 33 18 12 26 19 4 13 ",
        "answer": "19.22",
        "options": [
            "19.22",
            "96.10",
            "38.44",
            "76.88",
            "38.44"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean weight of the set of given tigers ? 11 39 22 35 42 4 35 32 50 11 42 ",
        "answer": "29.36",
        "options": [
            "58.72",
            "146.80",
            "29.36",
            "146.80",
            "58.72"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean area of the set of given cats ? 36 30 39 41 17 26 1 3 48 12 2 31 13 34 48 39 15 23 10 21 48 43 5 5 2 33 31 26 10 14 34 50 40 21 14 4 18 ",
        "answer": "23.97",
        "options": [
            "47.94",
            "23.97",
            "95.88",
            "95.88",
            "71.91"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean weight of the set of given kangaroos ? 21 9 4 26 24 42 50 18 42 25 32 10 21 41 16 1 39 36 45 28 45 45 13 10 34 39 11 50 21 23 13 49 50 11 15 33 40 38 33 ",
        "answer": "28.28",
        "options": [
            "28.28",
            "84.84",
            "56.56",
            "113.12",
            "56.56"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean length of the set of given martians ? 33 47 21 9 13 26 42 36 17 46 14 9 27 24 19 15 10 18 21 17 4 2 1 50 33 33 18 23 39 25 38 49 14 29 20 23 22 12 20 44 29 10 ",
        "answer": "23.86",
        "options": [
            "71.58",
            "47.72",
            "47.72",
            "23.86",
            "119.30"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean size of the set of given human ? 45 45 49 18 10 8 34 46 33 30 46 32 39 34 4 7 33 15 ",
        "answer": "29.33",
        "options": [
            "146.65",
            "146.65",
            "117.32",
            "58.66",
            "29.33"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean area of the set of given elephants ? 17 34 49 1 10 46 20 13 49 12 40 13 49 5 9 43 30 45 46 34 44 41 1 1 27 ",
        "answer": "27.16",
        "options": [
            "108.64",
            "135.80",
            "27.16",
            "135.80",
            "81.48"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean weight of the set of given cats ? 14 1 48 16 28 41 26 22 ",
        "answer": "24.50",
        "options": [
            "98.00",
            "24.50",
            "122.50",
            "73.50",
            "98.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean size of the set of given human ? 29 18 27 10 38 20 41 2 43 16 28 18 18 17 48 35 34 2 22 44 43 49 29 14 25 13 ",
        "answer": "26.27",
        "options": [
            "52.54",
            "26.27",
            "105.08",
            "105.08",
            "105.08"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean weight of the set of given tigers ? 29 45 38 27 41 21 36 47 9 21 28 21 3 14 42 48 50 5 11 10 13 29 17 14 44 40 27 19 5 1 19 12 33 35 21 27 32 32 4 22 47 23 2 28 39 1 35 9 ",
        "answer": "24.50",
        "options": [
            "73.50",
            "98.00",
            "98.00",
            "24.50",
            "49.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean length of the set of given kangaroos ? 32 11 39 36 39 26 17 24 19 2 39 17 17 39 12 36 34 18 15 48 5 47 36 6 18 48 33 24 19 4 18 9 1 36 46 3 44 50 ",
        "answer": "25.45",
        "options": [
            "76.35",
            "25.45",
            "127.25",
            "127.25",
            "76.35"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean length of the set of given cats ? 44 16 42 20 45 31 3 7 8 11 20 44 16 18 11 25 33 19 43 34 22 21 37 44 22 1 20 5 37 29 24 14 3 36 34 12 22 44 19 47 21 27 ",
        "answer": "24.55",
        "options": [
            "122.75",
            "122.75",
            "49.10",
            "122.75",
            "24.55"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean size of the set of given tigers ? 15 23 21 42 11 19 32 33 24 24 4 30 16 46 33 41 41 ",
        "answer": "26.76",
        "options": [
            "133.80",
            "53.52",
            "26.76",
            "53.52",
            "107.04"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean height of the set of given tigers ? 33 36 46 29 33 37 42 23 45 46 46 46 47 28 36 40 27 15 20 12 33 44 33 46 33 1 37 3 38 39 34 30 26 34 47 13 33 27 14 26 3 15 21 33 41 2 34 ",
        "answer": "30.36",
        "options": [
            "121.44",
            "30.36",
            "60.72",
            "91.08",
            "151.80"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean height of the set of given dogs ? 6 27 45 40 7 26 38 39 42 42 48 20 43 31 17 2 50 30 46 1 2 ",
        "answer": "28.67",
        "options": [
            "28.67",
            "57.34",
            "86.01",
            "86.01",
            "114.68"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean height of the set of given tigers ? 16 45 39 11 30 2 13 39 32 14 25 21 37 9 48 5 21 49 10 45 16 33 37 5 ",
        "answer": "25.08",
        "options": [
            "75.24",
            "25.08",
            "75.24",
            "125.40",
            "125.40"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean height of the set of given kangaroos ? 45 40 28 17 9 33 24 45 9 27 37 46 21 47 1 46 50 1 9 34 19 32 11 24 46 42 16 19 24 ",
        "answer": "27.66",
        "options": [
            "110.64",
            "110.64",
            "110.64",
            "27.66",
            "82.98"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean size of the set of given human ? 23 43 18 48 46 9 17 1 3 3 10 49 29 45 ",
        "answer": "24.57",
        "options": [
            "49.14",
            "73.71",
            "24.57",
            "49.14",
            "98.28"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean length of the set of given human ? 21 12 48 16 3 38 30 48 11 4 20 26 9 31 31 17 3 13 50 11 7 1 33 42 14 11 19 8 4 37 22 39 20 9 6 24 15 43 27 30 20 23 2 18 28 42 24 ",
        "answer": "21.49",
        "options": [
            "85.96",
            "107.45",
            "64.47",
            "21.49",
            "64.47"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean weight of the set of given kangaroos ? 35 7 7 42 13 27 41 4 36 30 34 25 44 42 47 47 28 12 47 40 30 41 39 43 26 ",
        "answer": "31.48",
        "options": [
            "94.44",
            "31.48",
            "125.92",
            "125.92",
            "157.40"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean length of the set of given dogs ? 25 13 28 25 13 3 48 44 5 17 16 30 36 37 25 50 42 3 8 9 43 22 23 35 34 13 40 23 17 25 22 24 47 8 8 23 32 29 10 24 6 46 50 50 26 34 ",
        "answer": "25.89",
        "options": [
            "77.67",
            "25.89",
            "103.56",
            "103.56",
            "129.45"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean area of the set of given cats ? 49 4 31 39 34 21 50 8 20 11 25 22 5 21 23 40 26 21 15 47 41 11 17 22 28 45 21 49 26 45 ",
        "answer": "27.23",
        "options": [
            "81.69",
            "108.92",
            "81.69",
            "54.46",
            "27.23"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean weight of the set of given elephants ? 46 13 14 8 40 24 29 47 45 14 48 ",
        "answer": "29.82",
        "options": [
            "29.82",
            "149.10",
            "89.46",
            "119.28",
            "89.46"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean weight of the set of given martians ? 47 36 39 7 3 20 46 19 30 43 1 49 27 13 46 28 48 5 6 33 4 10 4 ",
        "answer": "24.52",
        "options": [
            "49.04",
            "73.56",
            "73.56",
            "98.08",
            "24.52"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean length of the set of given kangaroos ? 4 46 11 2 4 6 48 10 22 6 37 12 8 1 33 40 28 16 36 16 48 26 38 15 44 26 ",
        "answer": "22.42",
        "options": [
            "112.10",
            "22.42",
            "112.10",
            "112.10",
            "112.10"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean area of the set of given martians ? 8 23 48 12 11 50 24 16 11 10 48 2 7 19 47 10 9 3 28 7 13 20 18 8 34 40 41 40 31 31 12 38 ",
        "answer": "22.47",
        "options": [
            "89.88",
            "44.94",
            "89.88",
            "22.47",
            "44.94"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean size of the set of given elephants ? 21 25 28 41 37 3 27 12 7 49 40 17 25 36 25 19 45 3 16 36 42 30 22 17 49 25 5 47 3 47 34 44 43 2 47 16 37 15 10 19 42 31 ",
        "answer": "27.12",
        "options": [
            "81.36",
            "108.48",
            "135.60",
            "81.36",
            "27.12"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean area of the set of given cats ? 11 8 14 49 22 5 29 13 23 35 10 34 8 49 45 26 13 46 38 38 45 5 29 44 42 5 11 46 25 20 26 47 47 33 11 31 42 41 49 35 4 43 38 ",
        "answer": "28.72",
        "options": [
            "143.60",
            "28.72",
            "57.44",
            "114.88",
            "114.88"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean weight of the set of given tigers ? 25 11 13 18 45 33 30 6 37 43 13 6 23 6 25 16 17 11 20 47 7 41 3 1 31 39 29 11 40 2 ",
        "answer": "21.63",
        "options": [
            "43.26",
            "86.52",
            "43.26",
            "108.15",
            "21.63"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean weight of the set of given dogs ? 36 39 30 32 38 23 35 42 2 8 22 29 29 20 50 28 31 ",
        "answer": "29.06",
        "options": [
            "116.24",
            "58.12",
            "116.24",
            "87.18",
            "29.06"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean height of the set of given human ? 25 28 38 48 6 41 35 42 28 3 26 38 16 24 11 18 30 ",
        "answer": "26.88",
        "options": [
            "53.76",
            "53.76",
            "80.64",
            "26.88",
            "107.52"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean area of the set of given martians ? 40 5 14 12 34 15 24 7 18 15 11 42 5 11 20 26 43 22 30 45 44 50 22 25 42 39 11 32 45 28 33 36 9 ",
        "answer": "25.91",
        "options": [
            "103.64",
            "129.55",
            "25.91",
            "103.64",
            "77.73"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean area of the set of given cats ? 6 30 40 33 3 25 32 25 33 35 19 29 50 28 33 3 49 45 43 32 35 23 43 1 50 14 35 12 14 37 3 43 12 13 16 22 1 33 20 15 33 37 44 21 5 8 ",
        "answer": "25.72",
        "options": [
            "77.16",
            "51.44",
            "128.60",
            "25.72",
            "77.16"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean length of the set of given human ? 32 3 44 28 7 30 35 34 32 10 5 11 40 50 21 10 16 44 14 7 20 29 4 39 3 36 11 35 2 3 29 15 1 ",
        "answer": "21.21",
        "options": [
            "21.21",
            "42.42",
            "106.05",
            "42.42",
            "106.05"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean length of the set of given cats ? 2 8 5 40 23 3 39 26 41 44 35 22 36 49 49 26 26 17 15 33 43 43 29 18 33 13 7 12 ",
        "answer": "26.32",
        "options": [
            "52.64",
            "105.28",
            "52.64",
            "131.60",
            "26.32"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean area of the set of given dogs ? 11 37 39 15 25 26 42 17 49 47 5 7 23 45 14 37 7 15 3 12 46 13 18 30 19 10 2 37 15 31 20 34 4 ",
        "answer": "22.88",
        "options": [
            "22.88",
            "68.64",
            "45.76",
            "45.76",
            "114.40"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean size of the set of given cats ? 43 27 46 38 17 32 11 8 23 38 7 40 13 20 12 6 15 29 27 22 6 2 26 9 44 9 2 11 2 6 43 27 ",
        "answer": "20.66",
        "options": [
            "20.66",
            "82.64",
            "41.32",
            "82.64",
            "41.32"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean weight of the set of given dogs ? 25 16 26 6 40 14 5 35 37 14 30 27 7 4 46 27 13 37 40 34 39 26 6 35 5 21 20 8 22 17 37 23 15 47 16 30 9 12 12 14 10 45 7 13 32 41 8 46 35 ",
        "answer": "23.14",
        "options": [
            "115.70",
            "115.70",
            "92.56",
            "115.70",
            "23.14"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean size of the set of given martians ? 23 40 49 31 6 39 26 27 46 20 12 39 11 41 5 29 27 4 22 33 46 23 50 49 29 3 45 48 46 3 ",
        "answer": "29.07",
        "options": [
            "145.35",
            "29.07",
            "87.21",
            "58.14",
            "58.14"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the mean size of the set of given tigers ? 48 2 39 44 25 17 11 4 29 14 11 28 9 35 35 7 3 45 39 16 38 14 43 21 ",
        "answer": "24.04",
        "options": [
            "48.08",
            "96.16",
            "24.04",
            "120.20",
            "48.08"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median length of the set of given human ? 14 33 24 26 36 18 6 12 47 14 10 45 44 9 43 20 19 ",
        "answer": "20.00",
        "options": [
            "44.00",
            "20.00",
            "10.00",
            "26.00",
            "9.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median size of the set of given elephants ? 25 48 5 9 21 25 48 50 28 47 8 23 33 23 45 33 39 36 4 13 34 41 27 40 31 42 42 27 5 12 10 21 5 14 9 12 26 44 22 6 ",
        "answer": "25.50",
        "options": [
            "36.00",
            "33.00",
            "21.00",
            "25.50",
            "34.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median length of the set of given tigers ? 23 14 15 38 49 9 14 23 11 43 45 33 4 25 5 50 43 34 45 30 9 44 18 26 5 2 2 31 12 1 37 2 21 20 21 31 26 40 33 16 32 5 48 17 17 33 17 32 35 ",
        "answer": "23.00",
        "options": [
            "5.00",
            "32.00",
            "44.00",
            "17.00",
            "23.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median size of the set of given cats ? 5 33 14 40 26 36 13 48 26 23 18 30 3 32 24 42 15 24 20 ",
        "answer": "24.00",
        "options": [
            "23.00",
            "24.00",
            "42.00",
            "48.00",
            "48.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median area of the set of given martians ? 27 1 2 25 8 18 46 12 35 28 22 32 8 27 8 4 11 26 3 40 13 31 4 42 16 30 32 27 1 2 16 2 10 11 13 44 ",
        "answer": "16.00",
        "options": [
            "42.00",
            "16.00",
            "8.00",
            "35.00",
            "12.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median area of the set of given kangaroos ? 50 24 32 49 24 23 44 31 31 14 28 14 49 43 7 40 44 20 23 26 35 16 50 14 3 5 13 9 24 12 40 45 42 18 47 ",
        "answer": "26.00",
        "options": [
            "16.00",
            "20.00",
            "26.00",
            "31.00",
            "24.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median size of the set of given cats ? 6 16 15 12 27 8 13 20 38 16 11 20 1 9 36 42 9 37 40 42 36 33 23 7 3 48 2 18 20 49 16 10 44 11 46 38 39 4 ",
        "answer": "19.00",
        "options": [
            "19.00",
            "18.00",
            "33.00",
            "20.00",
            "33.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median size of the set of given tigers ? 10 18 20 13 26 44 12 40 32 13 13 ",
        "answer": "18.00",
        "options": [
            "26.00",
            "13.00",
            "18.00",
            "26.00",
            "13.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median weight of the set of given tigers ? 3 31 27 12 38 32 18 42 23 10 7 11 22 22 31 43 48 19 7 32 40 44 13 30 46 ",
        "answer": "27.00",
        "options": [
            "11.00",
            "31.00",
            "48.00",
            "27.00",
            "22.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median weight of the set of given tigers ? 9 50 27 16 49 36 20 18 21 28 32 38 2 10 19 40 8 18 12 31 41 20 31 28 1 48 8 37 20 4 42 ",
        "answer": "21.00",
        "options": [
            "21.00",
            "4.00",
            "1.00",
            "42.00",
            "9.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median weight of the set of given elephants ? 17 13 49 18 5 47 39 12 2 19 24 32 13 21 16 32 45 13 2 37 25 47 48 41 ",
        "answer": "22.50",
        "options": [
            "2.00",
            "19.00",
            "2.00",
            "47.00",
            "22.50"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median area of the set of given cats ? 25 43 22 21 24 5 15 5 28 28 19 12 42 46 23 11 43 30 29 25 27 13 44 7 38 8 22 42 48 11 16 ",
        "answer": "24.00",
        "options": [
            "24.00",
            "30.00",
            "22.00",
            "28.00",
            "42.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median length of the set of given tigers ? 31 50 19 35 24 20 23 41 ",
        "answer": "27.50",
        "options": [
            "20.00",
            "24.00",
            "27.50",
            "19.00",
            "35.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median size of the set of given kangaroos ? 39 14 23 11 8 20 39 2 32 44 26 43 28 ",
        "answer": "26.00",
        "options": [
            "26.00",
            "14.00",
            "32.00",
            "44.00",
            "44.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median size of the set of given tigers ? 23 32 25 33 6 49 14 20 17 7 26 12 26 31 30 26 5 20 ",
        "answer": "24.00",
        "options": [
            "49.00",
            "24.00",
            "31.00",
            "32.00",
            "49.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median length of the set of given human ? 16 35 36 45 21 18 3 27 22 29 43 1 28 31 48 12 21 35 44 47 50 41 41 12 38 45 14 29 48 32 50 6 44 42 47 11 37 42 2 41 17 22 38 44 39 25 19 21 34 ",
        "answer": "34.00",
        "options": [
            "6.00",
            "47.00",
            "50.00",
            "19.00",
            "34.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median size of the set of given dogs ? 32 6 19 26 2 46 29 3 8 12 26 22 16 35 9 23 16 3 22 15 35 42 29 7 45 5 49 10 43 16 12 18 40 21 41 31 8 10 43 7 32 31 ",
        "answer": "21.50",
        "options": [
            "35.00",
            "8.00",
            "12.00",
            "21.50",
            "29.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median area of the set of given tigers ? 5 18 33 22 33 23 23 29 40 48 38 43 6 29 47 32 35 24 28 38 41 39 33 9 4 43 37 26 14 24 48 2 2 39 29 41 3 37 27 30 16 38 16 14 22 26 10 27 ",
        "answer": "28.50",
        "options": [
            "48.00",
            "38.00",
            "14.00",
            "28.50",
            "38.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median size of the set of given elephants ? 25 12 10 28 6 29 37 1 20 18 6 43 14 46 13 29 27 34 28 2 24 40 47 17 2 29 42 15 43 9 39 17 39 32 15 32 7 22 34 4 48 ",
        "answer": "25.00",
        "options": [
            "24.00",
            "25.00",
            "34.00",
            "18.00",
            "28.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median weight of the set of given human ? 13 20 27 19 46 44 29 8 50 40 39 15 23 17 26 10 39 7 2 ",
        "answer": "23.00",
        "options": [
            "17.00",
            "26.00",
            "44.00",
            "23.00",
            "15.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median size of the set of given dogs ? 42 25 34 33 32 7 24 ",
        "answer": "32.00",
        "options": [
            "24.00",
            "7.00",
            "32.00",
            "7.00",
            "25.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median weight of the set of given tigers ? 50 35 33 13 23 36 11 ",
        "answer": "33.00",
        "options": [
            "33.00",
            "33.00",
            "13.00",
            "36.00",
            "33.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median size of the set of given human ? 17 49 3 9 27 49 46 36 22 14 20 50 25 25 50 3 7 46 9 9 41 41 26 32 47 11 26 24 18 25 26 38 45 23 39 3 44 23 22 21 17 46 ",
        "answer": "25.00",
        "options": [
            "23.00",
            "14.00",
            "23.00",
            "25.00",
            "14.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median size of the set of given cats ? 26 18 31 1 49 34 50 44 3 47 50 9 21 42 13 6 13 18 40 34 2 36 28 12 20 19 6 50 26 12 ",
        "answer": "23.50",
        "options": [
            "13.00",
            "23.50",
            "28.00",
            "34.00",
            "50.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median area of the set of given dogs ? 19 29 28 41 44 37 7 11 24 44 49 5 6 17 18 30 50 8 48 30 24 4 7 4 49 48 2 10 21 11 23 50 19 24 41 13 39 5 9 ",
        "answer": "23.00",
        "options": [
            "49.00",
            "23.00",
            "21.00",
            "9.00",
            "2.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median area of the set of given cats ? 16 22 20 42 37 48 16 8 ",
        "answer": "21.00",
        "options": [
            "48.00",
            "8.00",
            "8.00",
            "22.00",
            "21.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median weight of the set of given kangaroos ? 16 17 30 30 34 46 18 49 19 46 45 29 44 42 50 6 16 5 12 29 29 48 27 36 18 22 3 29 22 43 37 4 20 50 16 18 11 4 47 20 8 50 34 34 5 ",
        "answer": "29.00",
        "options": [
            "50.00",
            "43.00",
            "22.00",
            "49.00",
            "29.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median weight of the set of given tigers ? 17 43 14 19 41 28 20 11 6 37 40 22 40 19 39 25 38 ",
        "answer": "25.00",
        "options": [
            "37.00",
            "37.00",
            "25.00",
            "40.00",
            "40.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median height of the set of given cats ? 36 10 13 34 37 21 16 28 5 35 21 44 4 25 45 3 9 43 26 42 32 50 ",
        "answer": "27.00",
        "options": [
            "27.00",
            "50.00",
            "45.00",
            "21.00",
            "9.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median size of the set of given martians ? 32 40 16 37 48 41 28 37 42 17 2 22 41 30 3 13 48 3 1 29 19 29 37 49 27 18 25 42 29 21 41 ",
        "answer": "29.00",
        "options": [
            "37.00",
            "41.00",
            "41.00",
            "29.00",
            "48.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median length of the set of given cats ? 37 49 21 34 7 47 19 ",
        "answer": "34.00",
        "options": [
            "34.00",
            "34.00",
            "19.00",
            "21.00",
            "7.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median size of the set of given martians ? 6 22 22 32 29 ",
        "answer": "22.00",
        "options": [
            "22.00",
            "29.00",
            "22.00",
            "22.00",
            "22.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median weight of the set of given tigers ? 11 39 4 27 3 29 ",
        "answer": "19.00",
        "options": [
            "3.00",
            "39.00",
            "19.00",
            "3.00",
            "29.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median area of the set of given human ? 18 9 10 48 21 33 20 10 35 36 8 48 18 21 17 49 24 1 32 26 31 39 28 40 34 ",
        "answer": "26.00",
        "options": [
            "36.00",
            "18.00",
            "26.00",
            "10.00",
            "28.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median size of the set of given elephants ? 25 38 32 41 45 38 31 8 10 20 40 43 36 44 43 39 27 18 9 26 21 22 21 3 23 26 47 7 41 50 23 37 14 26 ",
        "answer": "26.50",
        "options": [
            "23.00",
            "36.00",
            "10.00",
            "26.50",
            "41.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median area of the set of given human ? 12 23 10 2 34 23 11 5 24 ",
        "answer": "12.00",
        "options": [
            "23.00",
            "2.00",
            "12.00",
            "5.00",
            "11.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median length of the set of given martians ? 24 40 17 42 44 30 35 40 30 20 46 2 11 36 30 33 26 10 45 9 13 39 ",
        "answer": "30.00",
        "options": [
            "17.00",
            "30.00",
            "30.00",
            "46.00",
            "17.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median weight of the set of given elephants ? 48 40 36 36 17 48 ",
        "answer": "38.00",
        "options": [
            "40.00",
            "17.00",
            "17.00",
            "40.00",
            "38.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median area of the set of given dogs ? 3 35 8 48 27 4 50 3 31 50 24 2 10 39 39 35 1 39 10 12 43 41 21 1 18 16 25 28 46 27 2 43 40 ",
        "answer": "27.00",
        "options": [
            "25.00",
            "25.00",
            "41.00",
            "43.00",
            "27.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median area of the set of given kangaroos ? 47 13 47 6 16 25 30 30 27 9 8 32 24 22 34 32 49 8 49 15 12 40 44 20 2 18 50 22 ",
        "answer": "24.50",
        "options": [
            "40.00",
            "6.00",
            "2.00",
            "49.00",
            "24.50"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median size of the set of given human ? 41 45 12 32 32 19 8 14 25 37 4 ",
        "answer": "25.00",
        "options": [
            "25.00",
            "25.00",
            "37.00",
            "8.00",
            "37.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median length of the set of given cats ? 13 17 46 36 7 1 4 31 16 46 36 6 31 48 25 6 45 46 10 49 5 48 19 42 25 31 16 12 37 37 1 11 50 19 19 8 19 46 26 29 21 30 17 24 28 29 36 4 49 ",
        "answer": "25.00",
        "options": [
            "10.00",
            "6.00",
            "25.00",
            "46.00",
            "25.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median size of the set of given dogs ? 22 46 31 19 30 41 41 47 34 15 17 44 48 50 15 6 45 7 27 33 9 13 3 27 18 6 24 50 12 48 31 18 4 ",
        "answer": "27.00",
        "options": [
            "46.00",
            "27.00",
            "22.00",
            "50.00",
            "18.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median area of the set of given cats ? 16 21 24 23 14 17 28 24 30 47 26 ",
        "answer": "24.00",
        "options": [
            "26.00",
            "24.00",
            "24.00",
            "17.00",
            "24.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median length of the set of given dogs ? 29 34 34 50 16 11 46 3 12 35 43 10 3 5 4 30 32 46 50 47 30 46 14 4 48 5 30 38 30 39 6 ",
        "answer": "30.00",
        "options": [
            "16.00",
            "5.00",
            "46.00",
            "46.00",
            "30.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median area of the set of given dogs ? 14 47 19 1 21 32 12 12 39 41 27 17 45 32 43 40 7 19 24 ",
        "answer": "24.00",
        "options": [
            "17.00",
            "24.00",
            "43.00",
            "14.00",
            "45.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median length of the set of given elephants ? 36 39 9 1 9 13 27 31 32 10 1 13 24 38 11 16 25 40 48 29 22 20 13 30 5 15 31 ",
        "answer": "22.00",
        "options": [
            "25.00",
            "31.00",
            "22.00",
            "25.00",
            "22.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median height of the set of given human ? 8 32 46 30 35 24 46 9 1 22 25 2 44 36 27 30 48 29 15 20 10 21 50 32 ",
        "answer": "28.00",
        "options": [
            "10.00",
            "24.00",
            "1.00",
            "25.00",
            "28.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median length of the set of given elephants ? 32 1 39 2 13 37 31 24 50 9 41 1 5 25 22 18 29 50 24 50 16 42 36 2 9 46 ",
        "answer": "24.50",
        "options": [
            "41.00",
            "13.00",
            "1.00",
            "24.50",
            "2.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the median weight of the set of given martians ? 30 36 48 27 36 41 50 9 14 26 49 17 47 48 21 29 36 29 17 1 8 25 46 35 16 40 40 24 35 15 48 14 18 47 ",
        "answer": "29.50",
        "options": [
            "14.00",
            "48.00",
            "48.00",
            "29.50",
            "48.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in titanium is 6070. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "12304",
            "343",
            "3706",
            "11602",
            "7569"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in Bismut is 2180. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "12294",
            "7983",
            "9888",
            "1852",
            "343"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in iron cast is 4994. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "343",
            "14360",
            "2141",
            "4400",
            "6713"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in nylon is 2620. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "2831",
            "5505",
            "343",
            "8187",
            "11777"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in copper annealed is 4760. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "2513",
            "14623",
            "7673",
            "2435",
            "343"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in iron electrolytic is 5950. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "2146",
            "1695",
            "14635",
            "343",
            "8571"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in aluminium is 6420. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "4966",
            "2583",
            "10477",
            "343",
            "7807"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in iron cast is 4994. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "12746",
            "5366",
            "9341",
            "343",
            "2886"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in wood is 3960. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "8158",
            "343",
            "7975",
            "7613",
            "10494"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in glass silicate flint is 3980. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "2465",
            "2749",
            "6361",
            "14124",
            "343"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in diamond is 12000. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "10945",
            "11835",
            "4906",
            "1262",
            "343"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in duralumin is 6320. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "343",
            "5436",
            "14322",
            "12592",
            "12730"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in wood is 3960. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "5235",
            "10730",
            "2104",
            "343",
            "4566"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in steel is 5940. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "4728",
            "13063",
            "4855",
            "9236",
            "343"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in monel is 5350. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "343",
            "12561",
            "6521",
            "14146",
            "6652"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in antimony is 3400. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "343",
            "948",
            "5173",
            "7847",
            "2889"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in platinum is 3260. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "343",
            "7175",
            "14394",
            "5437",
            "4182"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in steel is 5940. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "605",
            "11302",
            "1845",
            "343",
            "2287"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in nickel is 6040. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "3089",
            "14600",
            "8064",
            "343",
            "10927"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in Brick is 4200. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "1479",
            "1046",
            "13600",
            "4239",
            "343"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in glass is 5640. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "6707",
            "343",
            "12741",
            "5716",
            "5654"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in lead rolled is 1960. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "2043",
            "343",
            "8557",
            "1949",
            "12192"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in rubber gum is 1550. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "7633",
            "9064",
            "343",
            "6292",
            "2602"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in drawn tungsten is 5410. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "9034",
            "1381",
            "343",
            "6768",
            "3030"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in lucite is 2680. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "11979",
            "14134",
            "6100",
            "13871",
            "343"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in gold is 3240. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "14849",
            "8445",
            "2578",
            "13279",
            "343"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in iron cast is 4994. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "9453",
            "343",
            "13302",
            "11991",
            "1684"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in nylon is 2620. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "343",
            "3933",
            "673",
            "14457",
            "14380"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in gold is 3240. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "1437",
            "4426",
            "6764",
            "2547",
            "343"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in mercury is 1540. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "9699",
            "343",
            "6383",
            "13772",
            "9961"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in silver is 3650. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "3238",
            "13729",
            "5790",
            "343",
            "521"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in iron cast is 4994. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "14388",
            "8356",
            "3881",
            "8591",
            "343"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in nylon is 2620. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "817",
            "343",
            "12076",
            "10056",
            "5499"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in marbel is 3810. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "488",
            "343",
            "9914",
            "6896",
            "11740"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in stainless steel is 5790. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "9379",
            "542",
            "12226",
            "343",
            "12880"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in steel is 5940. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "10053",
            "5984",
            "7381",
            "9575",
            "343"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in water is 1496. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "10112",
            "7088",
            "10895",
            "343",
            "5468"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in manganese is 4660. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "6695",
            "14016",
            "343",
            "12412",
            "6608"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in glass pyrex is 5640. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "7404",
            "343",
            "4167",
            "429",
            "13962"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in Brick is 4200. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "13349",
            "6531",
            "2906",
            "5593",
            "343"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in glass light crown is 5100. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "13964",
            "6327",
            "1964",
            "343",
            "4110"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in tin rolled is 3320. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "504",
            "5365",
            "4033",
            "343",
            "10395"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in ivory is 3010. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "13501",
            "343",
            "2330",
            "7638",
            "8441"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in molybdenum is 6250. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "2809",
            "494",
            "10597",
            "4504",
            "343"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in constantan is 5177. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "975",
            "913",
            "4361",
            "1516",
            "343"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in aluminium is 6420. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "5647",
            "3232",
            "12226",
            "343",
            "2898"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in monel is 5350. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "14429",
            "5886",
            "8629",
            "343",
            "4319"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in glass is 5640. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "14934",
            "9351",
            "11095",
            "10000",
            "343"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in marbel is 3810. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "1142",
            "3793",
            "2177",
            "343",
            "8400"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in annealed tungsten is 5220. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "1009",
            "12873",
            "343",
            "389",
            "10152"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in iron electrolytic is 5950. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "343",
            "14975",
            "8791",
            "14732",
            "11338"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in silver is 3650. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "343",
            "3178",
            "6424",
            "1244",
            "8308"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in nylon is 2620. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "4725",
            "13225",
            "2048",
            "343",
            "9407"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in Polyethylene is 1250. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "7254",
            "1631",
            "343",
            "5726",
            "11927"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in rubber neoprene is 1600. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "11085",
            "8377",
            "14309",
            "343",
            "14123"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in antimony is 3400. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "343",
            "11242",
            "3858",
            "11844",
            "7230"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in iron electrolytic is 5950. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "10448",
            "3136",
            "1151",
            "4029",
            "343"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in nickel is 6040. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "343",
            "12804",
            "14327",
            "11952",
            "14632"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in glass silicate flint is 3980. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "343",
            "1797",
            "13103",
            "5250",
            "2366"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in rubber neoprene is 1600. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "11383",
            "14416",
            "343",
            "1937",
            "5697"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in manganese is 4660. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "3869",
            "3945",
            "14582",
            "343",
            "10371"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in titanium is 6070. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "8813",
            "1519",
            "7169",
            "1478",
            "343"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in manganese is 4660. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "343",
            "12314",
            "12285",
            "7883",
            "10560"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in platinum is 3260. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "4259",
            "8952",
            "4268",
            "343",
            "10621"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in slate is 4510. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "5834",
            "8592",
            "10659",
            "343",
            "14275"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in aluminium is 6420. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "13841",
            "343",
            "1411",
            "8998",
            "6412"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in mercury is 1540. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "6068",
            "343",
            "8393",
            "8221",
            "6967"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in glass is 5640. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "4500",
            "13129",
            "10895",
            "343",
            "647"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in tungsten carbide is 6655. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "14861",
            "9400",
            "5439",
            "343",
            "8119"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in lead annealed is 2160. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "343",
            "14893",
            "13761",
            "9037",
            "12820"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in zinc rolled is 4210. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "2998",
            "2150",
            "8598",
            "343",
            "9391"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in rubber neoprene is 1600. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "11432",
            "13121",
            "7826",
            "2578",
            "343"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in magnesium annealed is 5770. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "343",
            "4602",
            "8742",
            "9151",
            "7251"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in cork is 518. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "343",
            "6184",
            "13974",
            "10965",
            "4966"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in magnesium annealed is 5770. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "343",
            "12676",
            "12666",
            "7810",
            "8183"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in constantan is 5177. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "11457",
            "11283",
            "14515",
            "343",
            "7694"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in platinum is 3260. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "12989",
            "13871",
            "4712",
            "343",
            "2280"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in constantan is 5177. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "5891",
            "9000",
            "13380",
            "343",
            "4595"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in slate is 4510. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "343",
            "13545",
            "5494",
            "12830",
            "11997"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in nickel is 6040. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "8407",
            "13490",
            "343",
            "8511",
            "791"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in titanium is 6070. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "14421",
            "343",
            "5320",
            "14295",
            "11816"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in tantalium is 3350. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "343",
            "5338",
            "2197",
            "3192",
            "8260"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in iron electrolytic is 5950. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "9998",
            "343",
            "14747",
            "12909",
            "2532"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in aluminium is 6420. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "8110",
            "13237",
            "7763",
            "343",
            "489"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in aluminium is 6420. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "4235",
            "3874",
            "343",
            "13033",
            "14837"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in stainless steel is 5790. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "3760",
            "14716",
            "3680",
            "10803",
            "343"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in titanium is 6070. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "12392",
            "343",
            "5657",
            "5610",
            "10876"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in Bismut is 2180. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "2566",
            "343",
            "5219",
            "3875",
            "14984"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in wood is 3960. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "10255",
            "10407",
            "3054",
            "343",
            "11958"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in iridium is 4790. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "6663",
            "12504",
            "12240",
            "12443",
            "343"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in lead annealed is 2160. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "14458",
            "1605",
            "343",
            "2626",
            "14572"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in tungsten carbide is 6655. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "2956",
            "679",
            "10404",
            "7314",
            "343"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in Polystyrene is 2350. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "14825",
            "9231",
            "7483",
            "14828",
            "343"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in copper annealed is 4760. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "584",
            "343",
            "13427",
            "4402",
            "13255"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in tungsten carbide is 6655. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "3543",
            "343",
            "14856",
            "5123",
            "2516"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in duralumin is 6320. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "8864",
            "5305",
            "10734",
            "343",
            "6025"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in cork is 518. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "14148",
            "13363",
            "4150",
            "7955",
            "343"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in iridium is 4790. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "4040",
            "2228",
            "343",
            "12857",
            "1229"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in antimony is 3400. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "8007",
            "12185",
            "12776",
            "3509",
            "343"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sound travels slower in lighter medium than solids.The speed of sound in iron electrolytic is 5950. What is the speed of sound in air?",
        "answer": "343",
        "options": [
            "9350",
            "14228",
            "13639",
            "343",
            "12163"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Dawson consumes 630 calories per day. He/She is 1 years old. Sylas is 26 years old. How much calories should Sylas consume?",
        "answer": 1260,
        "options": [
            1260,
            176,
            224,
            361,
            189
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Lorenzo consumes 976 calories per day. He/She is 2 years old. Danny is 28 years old. How much calories should Danny consume?",
        "answer": 1952,
        "options": [
            508,
            1952,
            262,
            220,
            336
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Russell consumes 828 calories per day. He/She is 3 years old. Reginald is 26 years old. How much calories should Reginald consume?",
        "answer": 1656,
        "options": [
            177,
            1656,
            452,
            245,
            298
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Philip consumes 984 calories per day. He/She is 5 years old. Leroy is 24 years old. How much calories should Leroy consume?",
        "answer": 1968,
        "options": [
            232,
            373,
            1968,
            526,
            260
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Mohamed consumes 840 calories per day. He/She is 12 years old. Payton is 34 years old. How much calories should Payton consume?",
        "answer": 1680,
        "options": [
            241,
            201,
            298,
            432,
            1680
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Logan consumes 882 calories per day. He/She is 6 years old. Westin is 26 years old. How much calories should Westin consume?",
        "answer": 1764,
        "options": [
            247,
            197,
            477,
            1764,
            308
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Parker consumes 837 calories per day. He/She is 7 years old. Jamal is 26 years old. How much calories should Jamal consume?",
        "answer": 1674,
        "options": [
            1674,
            243,
            205,
            438,
            302
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Tate consumes 821 calories per day. He/She is 4 years old. Marcel is 34 years old. How much calories should Marcel consume?",
        "answer": 1642,
        "options": [
            459,
            1642,
            175,
            241,
            316
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jack consumes 815 calories per day. He/She is 9 years old. Tomas is 34 years old. How much calories should Tomas consume?",
        "answer": 1630,
        "options": [
            287,
            201,
            248,
            1630,
            436
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Isaac consumes 954 calories per day. He/She is 3 years old. Roger is 23 years old. How much calories should Roger consume?",
        "answer": 1908,
        "options": [
            260,
            239,
            344,
            492,
            1908
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Kyrie consumes 990 calories per day. He/She is 2 years old. Howard is 38 years old. How much calories should Howard consume?",
        "answer": 1980,
        "options": [
            354,
            294,
            532,
            209,
            1980
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Memphis consumes 540 calories per day. He/She is 3 years old. Raphael is 35 years old. How much calories should Raphael consume?",
        "answer": 1080,
        "options": [
            207,
            167,
            1080,
            127,
            287
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Arthur consumes 971 calories per day. He/She is 11 years old. Rayden is 23 years old. How much calories should Rayden consume?",
        "answer": 1942,
        "options": [
            352,
            210,
            1942,
            497,
            285
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Corbin consumes 597 calories per day. He/She is 15 years old. Dangelo is 21 years old. How much calories should Dangelo consume?",
        "answer": 1194,
        "options": [
            191,
            212,
            131,
            1194,
            348
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Lennox consumes 595 calories per day. He/She is 12 years old. Blaze is 29 years old. How much calories should Blaze consume?",
        "answer": 1190,
        "options": [
            223,
            180,
            150,
            309,
            1190
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Amari consumes 840 calories per day. He/She is 13 years old. Reyansh is 40 years old. How much calories should Reyansh consume?",
        "answer": 1680,
        "options": [
            205,
            1680,
            223,
            458,
            323
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Dallas consumes 857 calories per day. He/She is 12 years old. Aries is 31 years old. How much calories should Aries consume?",
        "answer": 1714,
        "options": [
            1714,
            255,
            445,
            311,
            192
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Cyrus consumes 812 calories per day. He/She is 1 years old. Alvin is 26 years old. How much calories should Alvin consume?",
        "answer": 1624,
        "options": [
            1624,
            225,
            313,
            182,
            445
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ronald consumes 955 calories per day. He/She is 8 years old. Darwin is 37 years old. How much calories should Darwin consume?",
        "answer": 1910,
        "options": [
            492,
            233,
            352,
            269,
            1910
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jonas consumes 962 calories per day. He/She is 10 years old. Raul is 34 years old. How much calories should Raul consume?",
        "answer": 1924,
        "options": [
            522,
            276,
            340,
            1924,
            209
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jeremy consumes 547 calories per day. He/She is 6 years old. Dillon is 36 years old. How much calories should Dillon consume?",
        "answer": 1094,
        "options": [
            184,
            317,
            1094,
            220,
            136
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jaylen consumes 537 calories per day. He/She is 14 years old. Alessandro is 36 years old. How much calories should Alessandro consume?",
        "answer": 1074,
        "options": [
            195,
            161,
            1074,
            129,
            316
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jeremiah consumes 845 calories per day. He/She is 12 years old. Damari is 28 years old. How much calories should Damari consume?",
        "answer": 1690,
        "options": [
            1690,
            230,
            445,
            201,
            324
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Gavin consumes 744 calories per day. He/She is 14 years old. Keaton is 31 years old. How much calories should Keaton consume?",
        "answer": 1488,
        "options": [
            279,
            399,
            1488,
            198,
            202
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Gunner consumes 727 calories per day. He/She is 2 years old. Baker is 35 years old. How much calories should Baker consume?",
        "answer": 1454,
        "options": [
            1454,
            168,
            379,
            208,
            255
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Gunner consumes 926 calories per day. He/She is 11 years old. Langston is 27 years old. How much calories should Langston consume?",
        "answer": 1852,
        "options": [
            204,
            1852,
            278,
            500,
            345
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Kyler consumes 856 calories per day. He/She is 10 years old. Sonny is 39 years old. How much calories should Sonny consume?",
        "answer": 1712,
        "options": [
            297,
            210,
            475,
            231,
            1712
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Nehemiah consumes 864 calories per day. He/She is 2 years old. Axl is 20 years old. How much calories should Axl consume?",
        "answer": 1728,
        "options": [
            208,
            335,
            450,
            1728,
            226
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Nehemiah consumes 972 calories per day. He/She is 6 years old. Salvador is 29 years old. How much calories should Salvador consume?",
        "answer": 1944,
        "options": [
            213,
            273,
            1944,
            370,
            506
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Hugo consumes 716 calories per day. He/She is 4 years old. Dominik is 25 years old. How much calories should Dominik consume?",
        "answer": 1432,
        "options": [
            384,
            1432,
            172,
            204,
            263
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Elliott consumes 589 calories per day. He/She is 15 years old. Franco is 26 years old. How much calories should Franco consume?",
        "answer": 1178,
        "options": [
            244,
            324,
            132,
            186,
            1178
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sergio consumes 746 calories per day. He/She is 12 years old. Mustafa is 24 years old. How much calories should Mustafa consume?",
        "answer": 1492,
        "options": [
            197,
            277,
            181,
            407,
            1492
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Liam consumes 514 calories per day. He/She is 12 years old. Jedidiah is 34 years old. How much calories should Jedidiah consume?",
        "answer": 1028,
        "options": [
            1028,
            173,
            300,
            220,
            124
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Kian consumes 846 calories per day. He/She is 5 years old. Boone is 21 years old. How much calories should Boone consume?",
        "answer": 1692,
        "options": [
            328,
            1692,
            179,
            241,
            447
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Matteo consumes 822 calories per day. He/She is 15 years old. Duncan is 28 years old. How much calories should Duncan consume?",
        "answer": 1644,
        "options": [
            178,
            225,
            1644,
            297,
            431
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Emmanuel consumes 797 calories per day. He/She is 5 years old. Coen is 28 years old. How much calories should Coen consume?",
        "answer": 1594,
        "options": [
            1594,
            240,
            276,
            443,
            207
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jaxon consumes 682 calories per day. He/She is 15 years old. Quentin is 37 years old. How much calories should Quentin consume?",
        "answer": 1364,
        "options": [
            385,
            181,
            1364,
            248,
            183
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Seth consumes 573 calories per day. He/She is 10 years old. Sam is 29 years old. How much calories should Sam consume?",
        "answer": 1146,
        "options": [
            1146,
            224,
            179,
            150,
            319
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Abraham consumes 863 calories per day. He/She is 13 years old. Sutton is 24 years old. How much calories should Sutton consume?",
        "answer": 1726,
        "options": [
            225,
            453,
            209,
            308,
            1726
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Shane consumes 847 calories per day. He/She is 1 years old. Braylon is 27 years old. How much calories should Braylon consume?",
        "answer": 1694,
        "options": [
            244,
            323,
            1694,
            470,
            213
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jax consumes 560 calories per day. He/She is 2 years old. Brysen is 40 years old. How much calories should Brysen consume?",
        "answer": 1120,
        "options": [
            197,
            183,
            1120,
            161,
            297
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Xavier consumes 925 calories per day. He/She is 7 years old. Bentlee is 22 years old. How much calories should Bentlee consume?",
        "answer": 1850,
        "options": [
            508,
            216,
            318,
            254,
            1850
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Abel consumes 626 calories per day. He/She is 7 years old. Layne is 21 years old. How much calories should Layne consume?",
        "answer": 1252,
        "options": [
            335,
            164,
            203,
            1252,
            258
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Roman consumes 724 calories per day. He/She is 9 years old. Mekhi is 24 years old. How much calories should Mekhi consume?",
        "answer": 1448,
        "options": [
            1448,
            287,
            378,
            198,
            188
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Lukas consumes 793 calories per day. He/She is 7 years old. Kabir is 33 years old. How much calories should Kabir consume?",
        "answer": 1586,
        "options": [
            440,
            191,
            1586,
            212,
            283
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Edgar consumes 948 calories per day. He/She is 1 years old. Gary is 40 years old. How much calories should Gary consume?",
        "answer": 1896,
        "options": [
            1896,
            501,
            328,
            252,
            204
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Daxton consumes 904 calories per day. He/She is 1 years old. Edison is 33 years old. How much calories should Edison consume?",
        "answer": 1808,
        "options": [
            490,
            1808,
            271,
            196,
            346
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Troy consumes 990 calories per day. He/She is 9 years old. Harlan is 29 years old. How much calories should Harlan consume?",
        "answer": 1980,
        "options": [
            259,
            224,
            543,
            344,
            1980
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Bradley consumes 545 calories per day. He/She is 7 years old. Terrance is 31 years old. How much calories should Terrance consume?",
        "answer": 1090,
        "options": [
            296,
            1090,
            185,
            120,
            224
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Daniel consumes 807 calories per day. He/She is 12 years old. Elon is 39 years old. How much calories should Elon consume?",
        "answer": 1614,
        "options": [
            417,
            1614,
            206,
            291,
            244
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Porter consumes 608 calories per day. He/She is 15 years old. Azariah is 36 years old. How much calories should Azariah consume?",
        "answer": 1216,
        "options": [
            225,
            132,
            1216,
            343,
            170
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Milo consumes 937 calories per day. He/She is 8 years old. Hugh is 27 years old. How much calories should Hugh consume?",
        "answer": 1874,
        "options": [
            360,
            1874,
            205,
            479,
            283
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Deacon consumes 999 calories per day. He/She is 7 years old. Fox is 20 years old. How much calories should Fox consume?",
        "answer": 1998,
        "options": [
            378,
            1998,
            224,
            549,
            282
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Holden consumes 917 calories per day. He/She is 9 years old. Roland is 30 years old. How much calories should Roland consume?",
        "answer": 1834,
        "options": [
            342,
            193,
            1834,
            267,
            481
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Cameron consumes 517 calories per day. He/She is 14 years old. Ralph is 26 years old. How much calories should Ralph consume?",
        "answer": 1034,
        "options": [
            196,
            113,
            273,
            1034,
            160
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Nolan consumes 916 calories per day. He/She is 14 years old. Kamdyn is 35 years old. How much calories should Kamdyn consume?",
        "answer": 1832,
        "options": [
            229,
            327,
            1832,
            479,
            247
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Kyson consumes 533 calories per day. He/She is 6 years old. Jeremias is 21 years old. How much calories should Jeremias consume?",
        "answer": 1066,
        "options": [
            194,
            117,
            148,
            1066,
            286
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Kai consumes 662 calories per day. He/She is 9 years old. Leandro is 20 years old. How much calories should Leandro consume?",
        "answer": 1324,
        "options": [
            191,
            177,
            354,
            259,
            1324
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Christian consumes 999 calories per day. He/She is 5 years old. Colten is 22 years old. How much calories should Colten consume?",
        "answer": 1998,
        "options": [
            1998,
            540,
            283,
            345,
            240
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sullivan consumes 987 calories per day. He/She is 6 years old. Graysen is 28 years old. How much calories should Graysen consume?",
        "answer": 1974,
        "options": [
            220,
            371,
            277,
            1974,
            542
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Adrian consumes 538 calories per day. He/She is 14 years old. Zaid is 31 years old. How much calories should Zaid consume?",
        "answer": 1076,
        "options": [
            169,
            1076,
            282,
            192,
            142
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Allen consumes 856 calories per day. He/She is 12 years old. Kylen is 38 years old. How much calories should Kylen consume?",
        "answer": 1712,
        "options": [
            218,
            467,
            305,
            255,
            1712
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jensen consumes 780 calories per day. He/She is 15 years old. Landyn is 20 years old. How much calories should Landyn consume?",
        "answer": 1560,
        "options": [
            1560,
            216,
            175,
            435,
            282
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Graham consumes 676 calories per day. He/She is 14 years old. Torin is 28 years old. How much calories should Torin consume?",
        "answer": 1352,
        "options": [
            147,
            212,
            349,
            1352,
            238
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Kyson consumes 560 calories per day. He/She is 13 years old. Ishaan is 31 years old. How much calories should Ishaan consume?",
        "answer": 1120,
        "options": [
            228,
            150,
            178,
            305,
            1120
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Mathias consumes 617 calories per day. He/She is 15 years old. Keanu is 22 years old. How much calories should Keanu consume?",
        "answer": 1234,
        "options": [
            232,
            1234,
            148,
            169,
            356
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sullivan consumes 910 calories per day. He/She is 1 years old. Koda is 40 years old. How much calories should Koda consume?",
        "answer": 1820,
        "options": [
            470,
            277,
            221,
            1820,
            343
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Vincent consumes 953 calories per day. He/She is 12 years old. Salvador is 31 years old. How much calories should Salvador consume?",
        "answer": 1906,
        "options": [
            514,
            1906,
            277,
            358,
            214
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Spencer consumes 890 calories per day. He/She is 10 years old. Aden is 25 years old. How much calories should Aden consume?",
        "answer": 1780,
        "options": [
            215,
            269,
            459,
            344,
            1780
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Quinn consumes 700 calories per day. He/She is 1 years old. Eliseo is 39 years old. How much calories should Eliseo consume?",
        "answer": 1400,
        "options": [
            172,
            383,
            1400,
            265,
            221
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Kairo consumes 653 calories per day. He/She is 3 years old. Ryland is 35 years old. How much calories should Ryland consume?",
        "answer": 1306,
        "options": [
            161,
            375,
            1306,
            264,
            194
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Timothy consumes 524 calories per day. He/She is 15 years old. Raul is 25 years old. How much calories should Raul consume?",
        "answer": 1048,
        "options": [
            162,
            195,
            282,
            1048,
            141
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jensen consumes 546 calories per day. He/She is 15 years old. Alessandro is 35 years old. How much calories should Alessandro consume?",
        "answer": 1092,
        "options": [
            184,
            149,
            298,
            204,
            1092
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "George consumes 843 calories per day. He/She is 14 years old. Jasiah is 37 years old. How much calories should Jasiah consume?",
        "answer": 1686,
        "options": [
            213,
            301,
            468,
            229,
            1686
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Santiago consumes 837 calories per day. He/She is 10 years old. Achilles is 30 years old. How much calories should Achilles consume?",
        "answer": 1674,
        "options": [
            231,
            1674,
            435,
            293,
            201
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Hector consumes 852 calories per day. He/She is 12 years old. Braden is 22 years old. How much calories should Braden consume?",
        "answer": 1704,
        "options": [
            240,
            471,
            313,
            190,
            1704
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jax consumes 889 calories per day. He/She is 12 years old. Mohammed is 26 years old. How much calories should Mohammed consume?",
        "answer": 1778,
        "options": [
            1778,
            214,
            233,
            307,
            455
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sterling consumes 714 calories per day. He/She is 4 years old. Thaddeus is 21 years old. How much calories should Thaddeus consume?",
        "answer": 1428,
        "options": [
            262,
            388,
            191,
            224,
            1428
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander consumes 823 calories per day. He/She is 13 years old. Santino is 24 years old. How much calories should Santino consume?",
        "answer": 1646,
        "options": [
            1646,
            297,
            194,
            243,
            461
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Declan consumes 689 calories per day. He/She is 2 years old. Jefferson is 39 years old. How much calories should Jefferson consume?",
        "answer": 1378,
        "options": [
            278,
            176,
            190,
            375,
            1378
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Mateo consumes 846 calories per day. He/She is 11 years old. Brecken is 24 years old. How much calories should Brecken consume?",
        "answer": 1692,
        "options": [
            1692,
            301,
            197,
            226,
            442
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Erik consumes 945 calories per day. He/She is 11 years old. Kylen is 26 years old. How much calories should Kylen consume?",
        "answer": 1890,
        "options": [
            515,
            1890,
            220,
            328,
            254
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sterling consumes 892 calories per day. He/She is 1 years old. Musa is 40 years old. How much calories should Musa consume?",
        "answer": 1784,
        "options": [
            266,
            1784,
            226,
            335,
            472
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Cole consumes 782 calories per day. He/She is 10 years old. Bowie is 37 years old. How much calories should Bowie consume?",
        "answer": 1564,
        "options": [
            310,
            411,
            196,
            213,
            1564
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jayceon consumes 967 calories per day. He/She is 14 years old. Mustafa is 38 years old. How much calories should Mustafa consume?",
        "answer": 1934,
        "options": [
            253,
            239,
            1934,
            351,
            514
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Noah consumes 527 calories per day. He/She is 15 years old. Jaxx is 24 years old. How much calories should Jaxx consume?",
        "answer": 1054,
        "options": [
            147,
            1054,
            166,
            210,
            273
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Derek consumes 712 calories per day. He/She is 9 years old. Van is 34 years old. How much calories should Van consume?",
        "answer": 1424,
        "options": [
            372,
            225,
            171,
            253,
            1424
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Reed consumes 947 calories per day. He/She is 1 years old. Blaze is 20 years old. How much calories should Blaze consume?",
        "answer": 1894,
        "options": [
            217,
            260,
            336,
            1894,
            491
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alan consumes 715 calories per day. He/She is 8 years old. Alexzander is 26 years old. How much calories should Alexzander consume?",
        "answer": 1430,
        "options": [
            367,
            1430,
            186,
            209,
            256
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Gunner consumes 999 calories per day. He/She is 4 years old. Wells is 27 years old. How much calories should Wells consume?",
        "answer": 1998,
        "options": [
            261,
            531,
            375,
            223,
            1998
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Easton consumes 984 calories per day. He/She is 7 years old. Reyansh is 28 years old. How much calories should Reyansh consume?",
        "answer": 1968,
        "options": [
            1968,
            350,
            538,
            260,
            234
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "John consumes 691 calories per day. He/She is 10 years old. Skylar is 23 years old. How much calories should Skylar consume?",
        "answer": 1382,
        "options": [
            162,
            1382,
            259,
            388,
            221
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Gideon consumes 554 calories per day. He/She is 6 years old. Landyn is 29 years old. How much calories should Landyn consume?",
        "answer": 1108,
        "options": [
            124,
            1108,
            292,
            186,
            229
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alijah consumes 697 calories per day. He/She is 10 years old. Wesson is 39 years old. How much calories should Wesson consume?",
        "answer": 1394,
        "options": [
            1394,
            218,
            276,
            361,
            153
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Paul consumes 720 calories per day. He/She is 13 years old. Denver is 29 years old. How much calories should Denver consume?",
        "answer": 1440,
        "options": [
            403,
            171,
            1440,
            280,
            213
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Parker consumes 634 calories per day. He/She is 9 years old. Kamdyn is 26 years old. How much calories should Kamdyn consume?",
        "answer": 1268,
        "options": [
            191,
            1268,
            233,
            345,
            139
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Dalton consumes 648 calories per day. He/She is 4 years old. Lucian is 27 years old. How much calories should Lucian consume?",
        "answer": 1296,
        "options": [
            171,
            200,
            1296,
            340,
            258
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "August consumes 599 calories per day. He/She is 15 years old. Thatcher is 26 years old. How much calories should Thatcher consume?",
        "answer": 1198,
        "options": [
            141,
            225,
            1198,
            185,
            332
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jase consumes 915 calories per day. He/She is 9 years old. Ahmir is 21 years old. How much calories should Ahmir consume?",
        "answer": 1830,
        "options": [
            1830,
            339,
            228,
            266,
            494
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Roman consumes 695 calories per day. He/She is 5 years old. Thatcher is 24 years old. How much calories should Thatcher consume?",
        "answer": 1390,
        "options": [
            1390,
            203,
            161,
            386,
            262
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Travis consumes 669 calories per day. He/She is 2 years old. Keith is 25 years old. How much calories should Keith consume?",
        "answer": 1338,
        "options": [
            371,
            252,
            207,
            148,
            1338
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Adam consumes 556 calories per day. He/She is 15 years old. Brentley is 39 years old. How much calories should Brentley consume?",
        "answer": 1112,
        "options": [
            1112,
            163,
            146,
            197,
            294
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Hector consumes 869 calories per day. He/She is 11 years old. Brixton is 27 years old. How much calories should Brixton consume?",
        "answer": 1738,
        "options": [
            333,
            1738,
            183,
            241,
            452
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Arthur consumes 987 calories per day. He/She is 4 years old. Reign is 27 years old. How much calories should Reign consume?",
        "answer": 1974,
        "options": [
            247,
            353,
            270,
            541,
            1974
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Bowen consumes 687 calories per day. He/She is 9 years old. Kristian is 32 years old. How much calories should Kristian consume?",
        "answer": 1374,
        "options": [
            265,
            187,
            1374,
            220,
            380
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Blake consumes 762 calories per day. He/She is 4 years old. Gary is 24 years old. How much calories should Gary consume?",
        "answer": 1524,
        "options": [
            399,
            170,
            1524,
            264,
            224
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Bodhi consumes 938 calories per day. He/She is 5 years old. Landyn is 22 years old. How much calories should Landyn consume?",
        "answer": 1876,
        "options": [
            348,
            519,
            220,
            251,
            1876
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Dalton consumes 583 calories per day. He/She is 3 years old. Mekhi is 36 years old. How much calories should Mekhi consume?",
        "answer": 1166,
        "options": [
            333,
            1166,
            154,
            168,
            210
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jax consumes 961 calories per day. He/She is 14 years old. Flynn is 32 years old. How much calories should Flynn consume?",
        "answer": 1922,
        "options": [
            237,
            497,
            276,
            1922,
            347
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Henry consumes 636 calories per day. He/She is 9 years old. Callum is 28 years old. How much calories should Callum consume?",
        "answer": 1272,
        "options": [
            196,
            331,
            145,
            239,
            1272
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Victor consumes 547 calories per day. He/She is 6 years old. Torin is 36 years old. How much calories should Torin consume?",
        "answer": 1094,
        "options": [
            152,
            178,
            284,
            209,
            1094
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Leo consumes 700 calories per day. He/She is 6 years old. Van is 31 years old. How much calories should Van consume?",
        "answer": 1400,
        "options": [
            251,
            176,
            1400,
            190,
            389
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Carlos consumes 781 calories per day. He/She is 12 years old. Jamie is 40 years old. How much calories should Jamie consume?",
        "answer": 1562,
        "options": [
            234,
            202,
            1562,
            405,
            293
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Zachary consumes 610 calories per day. He/She is 8 years old. Kaysen is 35 years old. How much calories should Kaysen consume?",
        "answer": 1220,
        "options": [
            244,
            166,
            1220,
            322,
            144
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Legend consumes 753 calories per day. He/She is 12 years old. Alden is 37 years old. How much calories should Alden consume?",
        "answer": 1506,
        "options": [
            238,
            291,
            191,
            411,
            1506
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Kaleb consumes 987 calories per day. He/She is 13 years old. Wesson is 40 years old. How much calories should Wesson consume?",
        "answer": 1974,
        "options": [
            277,
            530,
            1974,
            342,
            238
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Zayn consumes 836 calories per day. He/She is 12 years old. Rodney is 20 years old. How much calories should Rodney consume?",
        "answer": 1672,
        "options": [
            455,
            1672,
            319,
            221,
            191
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Leland consumes 656 calories per day. He/She is 5 years old. Ameer is 39 years old. How much calories should Ameer consume?",
        "answer": 1312,
        "options": [
            155,
            249,
            1312,
            349,
            209
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jackson consumes 566 calories per day. He/She is 11 years old. Maison is 29 years old. How much calories should Maison consume?",
        "answer": 1132,
        "options": [
            329,
            126,
            224,
            1132,
            164
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Barrett consumes 767 calories per day. He/She is 14 years old. Mekhi is 35 years old. How much calories should Mekhi consume?",
        "answer": 1534,
        "options": [
            281,
            187,
            209,
            1534,
            432
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Caiden consumes 540 calories per day. He/She is 15 years old. Raphael is 25 years old. How much calories should Raphael consume?",
        "answer": 1080,
        "options": [
            206,
            157,
            1080,
            296,
            127
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Malik consumes 543 calories per day. He/She is 5 years old. Castiel is 35 years old. How much calories should Castiel consume?",
        "answer": 1086,
        "options": [
            162,
            206,
            307,
            1086,
            135
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Lennox consumes 841 calories per day. He/She is 11 years old. Valentino is 26 years old. How much calories should Valentino consume?",
        "answer": 1682,
        "options": [
            234,
            445,
            309,
            189,
            1682
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Matthew consumes 516 calories per day. He/She is 4 years old. Zain is 40 years old. How much calories should Zain consume?",
        "answer": 1032,
        "options": [
            153,
            185,
            273,
            1032,
            138
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jasper consumes 503 calories per day. He/She is 5 years old. Koa is 33 years old. How much calories should Koa consume?",
        "answer": 1006,
        "options": [
            1006,
            216,
            125,
            272,
            143
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Oakley consumes 740 calories per day. He/She is 2 years old. Franco is 20 years old. How much calories should Franco consume?",
        "answer": 1480,
        "options": [
            281,
            395,
            1480,
            188,
            224
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Beau consumes 721 calories per day. He/She is 14 years old. Markus is 34 years old. How much calories should Markus consume?",
        "answer": 1442,
        "options": [
            219,
            285,
            392,
            181,
            1442
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Eric consumes 799 calories per day. He/She is 2 years old. Darren is 22 years old. How much calories should Darren consume?",
        "answer": 1598,
        "options": [
            430,
            1598,
            213,
            176,
            277
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Collin consumes 765 calories per day. He/She is 2 years old. Lian is 38 years old. How much calories should Lian consume?",
        "answer": 1530,
        "options": [
            1530,
            430,
            230,
            298,
            190
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jayceon consumes 972 calories per day. He/She is 6 years old. Louie is 27 years old. How much calories should Louie consume?",
        "answer": 1944,
        "options": [
            337,
            289,
            497,
            225,
            1944
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Cruz consumes 696 calories per day. He/She is 4 years old. Azariah is 32 years old. How much calories should Azariah consume?",
        "answer": 1392,
        "options": [
            171,
            215,
            242,
            366,
            1392
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Messiah consumes 796 calories per day. He/She is 1 years old. Issac is 22 years old. How much calories should Issac consume?",
        "answer": 1592,
        "options": [
            1592,
            277,
            201,
            433,
            210
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Blake consumes 823 calories per day. He/She is 14 years old. Emmitt is 20 years old. How much calories should Emmitt consume?",
        "answer": 1646,
        "options": [
            243,
            1646,
            195,
            295,
            438
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Timothy consumes 733 calories per day. He/She is 5 years old. Terrell is 38 years old. How much calories should Terrell consume?",
        "answer": 1466,
        "options": [
            1466,
            260,
            392,
            193,
            160
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Seth consumes 773 calories per day. He/She is 6 years old. Kole is 30 years old. How much calories should Kole consume?",
        "answer": 1546,
        "options": [
            279,
            230,
            186,
            1546,
            422
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Nathan consumes 893 calories per day. He/She is 2 years old. Azariah is 38 years old. How much calories should Azariah consume?",
        "answer": 1786,
        "options": [
            479,
            213,
            325,
            1786,
            237
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Kairo consumes 547 calories per day. He/She is 13 years old. Carl is 26 years old. How much calories should Carl consume?",
        "answer": 1094,
        "options": [
            184,
            142,
            319,
            227,
            1094
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Zaiden consumes 967 calories per day. He/She is 14 years old. Leighton is 25 years old. How much calories should Leighton consume?",
        "answer": 1934,
        "options": [
            206,
            1934,
            286,
            516,
            347
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Odin consumes 593 calories per day. He/She is 11 years old. Maximo is 37 years old. How much calories should Maximo consume?",
        "answer": 1186,
        "options": [
            162,
            1186,
            227,
            157,
            324
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Lawson consumes 894 calories per day. He/She is 12 years old. Brysen is 29 years old. How much calories should Brysen consume?",
        "answer": 1788,
        "options": [
            260,
            320,
            462,
            1788,
            223
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Damon consumes 665 calories per day. He/She is 2 years old. Lewis is 39 years old. How much calories should Lewis consume?",
        "answer": 1330,
        "options": [
            168,
            1330,
            199,
            247,
            348
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sterling consumes 841 calories per day. He/She is 13 years old. Kamryn is 27 years old. How much calories should Kamryn consume?",
        "answer": 1682,
        "options": [
            330,
            430,
            236,
            1682,
            205
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Victor consumes 849 calories per day. He/She is 9 years old. Julio is 26 years old. How much calories should Julio consume?",
        "answer": 1698,
        "options": [
            1698,
            447,
            250,
            195,
            294
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Lincoln consumes 745 calories per day. He/She is 14 years old. Vihaan is 21 years old. How much calories should Vihaan consume?",
        "answer": 1490,
        "options": [
            271,
            159,
            399,
            221,
            1490
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Aiden consumes 520 calories per day. He/She is 1 years old. Cullen is 22 years old. How much calories should Cullen consume?",
        "answer": 1040,
        "options": [
            139,
            194,
            1040,
            145,
            291
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Allen consumes 527 calories per day. He/She is 1 years old. Joziah is 29 years old. How much calories should Joziah consume?",
        "answer": 1054,
        "options": [
            168,
            288,
            217,
            1054,
            148
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Leonel consumes 577 calories per day. He/She is 9 years old. Briar is 29 years old. How much calories should Briar consume?",
        "answer": 1154,
        "options": [
            194,
            229,
            320,
            1154,
            156
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Franklin consumes 958 calories per day. He/She is 9 years old. Kamari is 21 years old. How much calories should Kamari consume?",
        "answer": 1916,
        "options": [
            263,
            1916,
            516,
            229,
            363
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Paul consumes 610 calories per day. He/She is 10 years old. Mauricio is 33 years old. How much calories should Mauricio consume?",
        "answer": 1220,
        "options": [
            245,
            151,
            353,
            193,
            1220
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ruben consumes 636 calories per day. He/She is 8 years old. Kelvin is 27 years old. How much calories should Kelvin consume?",
        "answer": 1272,
        "options": [
            185,
            1272,
            166,
            358,
            237
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexis consumes 669 calories per day. He/She is 2 years old. Tatum is 20 years old. How much calories should Tatum consume?",
        "answer": 1338,
        "options": [
            187,
            1338,
            254,
            166,
            367
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Eduardo consumes 986 calories per day. He/She is 2 years old. Jamari is 36 years old. How much calories should Jamari consume?",
        "answer": 1972,
        "options": [
            343,
            1972,
            262,
            247,
            537
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Aaron consumes 699 calories per day. He/She is 1 years old. Brodie is 39 years old. How much calories should Brodie consume?",
        "answer": 1398,
        "options": [
            1398,
            187,
            200,
            365,
            265
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Charles consumes 584 calories per day. He/She is 9 years old. Decker is 40 years old. How much calories should Decker consume?",
        "answer": 1168,
        "options": [
            337,
            223,
            172,
            147,
            1168
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Maddox consumes 689 calories per day. He/She is 1 years old. Boden is 34 years old. How much calories should Boden consume?",
        "answer": 1378,
        "options": [
            258,
            189,
            1378,
            177,
            385
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Memphis consumes 942 calories per day. He/She is 12 years old. Dominik is 33 years old. How much calories should Dominik consume?",
        "answer": 1884,
        "options": [
            1884,
            507,
            247,
            332,
            198
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Anthony consumes 863 calories per day. He/She is 12 years old. Yusuf is 20 years old. How much calories should Yusuf consume?",
        "answer": 1726,
        "options": [
            297,
            448,
            236,
            215,
            1726
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Isaac consumes 895 calories per day. He/She is 8 years old. Brayan is 20 years old. How much calories should Brayan consume?",
        "answer": 1790,
        "options": [
            221,
            347,
            1790,
            477,
            252
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ari consumes 904 calories per day. He/She is 6 years old. Gannon is 30 years old. How much calories should Gannon consume?",
        "answer": 1808,
        "options": [
            246,
            468,
            1808,
            338,
            222
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Kingston consumes 579 calories per day. He/She is 14 years old. Maxton is 27 years old. How much calories should Maxton consume?",
        "answer": 1158,
        "options": [
            223,
            187,
            1158,
            318,
            154
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Abraham consumes 771 calories per day. He/She is 3 years old. Jericho is 33 years old. How much calories should Jericho consume?",
        "answer": 1542,
        "options": [
            1542,
            175,
            267,
            237,
            434
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Harvey consumes 665 calories per day. He/She is 1 years old. Alexzander is 33 years old. How much calories should Alexzander consume?",
        "answer": 1330,
        "options": [
            176,
            1330,
            259,
            207,
            380
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alijah consumes 821 calories per day. He/She is 1 years old. Arian is 35 years old. How much calories should Arian consume?",
        "answer": 1642,
        "options": [
            315,
            443,
            1642,
            210,
            230
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Declan consumes 857 calories per day. He/She is 13 years old. Issac is 36 years old. How much calories should Issac consume?",
        "answer": 1714,
        "options": [
            1714,
            242,
            312,
            476,
            198
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Axel consumes 725 calories per day. He/She is 10 years old. Leroy is 20 years old. How much calories should Leroy consume?",
        "answer": 1450,
        "options": [
            1450,
            214,
            176,
            394,
            281
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Beau consumes 825 calories per day. He/She is 9 years old. Finnley is 32 years old. How much calories should Finnley consume?",
        "answer": 1650,
        "options": [
            225,
            197,
            1650,
            444,
            293
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Rocco consumes 881 calories per day. He/She is 1 years old. Yusuf is 22 years old. How much calories should Yusuf consume?",
        "answer": 1762,
        "options": [
            1762,
            187,
            486,
            319,
            265
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Tucker consumes 730 calories per day. He/She is 12 years old. Mauricio is 38 years old. How much calories should Mauricio consume?",
        "answer": 1460,
        "options": [
            415,
            157,
            206,
            272,
            1460
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Emmanuel consumes 898 calories per day. He/She is 2 years old. Bishop is 38 years old. How much calories should Bishop consume?",
        "answer": 1796,
        "options": [
            489,
            1796,
            225,
            313,
            262
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Carson consumes 811 calories per day. He/She is 4 years old. Vance is 24 years old. How much calories should Vance consume?",
        "answer": 1622,
        "options": [
            311,
            187,
            1622,
            221,
            448
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Kingston consumes 844 calories per day. He/She is 6 years old. Shepherd is 26 years old. How much calories should Shepherd consume?",
        "answer": 1688,
        "options": [
            229,
            183,
            309,
            447,
            1688
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Devin consumes 771 calories per day. He/She is 13 years old. Houston is 28 years old. How much calories should Houston consume?",
        "answer": 1542,
        "options": [
            268,
            397,
            201,
            1542,
            211
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Nathaniel consumes 961 calories per day. He/She is 14 years old. Bodie is 40 years old. How much calories should Bodie consume?",
        "answer": 1922,
        "options": [
            268,
            240,
            1922,
            497,
            350
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sergio consumes 786 calories per day. He/She is 15 years old. Ares is 33 years old. How much calories should Ares consume?",
        "answer": 1572,
        "options": [
            415,
            305,
            173,
            227,
            1572
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Titus consumes 808 calories per day. He/She is 1 years old. Langston is 30 years old. How much calories should Langston consume?",
        "answer": 1616,
        "options": [
            290,
            1616,
            434,
            196,
            237
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Carlos consumes 754 calories per day. He/She is 4 years old. Colten is 40 years old. How much calories should Colten consume?",
        "answer": 1508,
        "options": [
            181,
            1508,
            212,
            301,
            402
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Roman consumes 690 calories per day. He/She is 8 years old. Genesis is 20 years old. How much calories should Genesis consume?",
        "answer": 1380,
        "options": [
            182,
            355,
            208,
            246,
            1380
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Grady consumes 899 calories per day. He/She is 11 years old. Carl is 25 years old. How much calories should Carl consume?",
        "answer": 1798,
        "options": [
            1798,
            255,
            202,
            489,
            331
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Everett consumes 531 calories per day. He/She is 1 years old. Draven is 20 years old. How much calories should Draven consume?",
        "answer": 1062,
        "options": [
            210,
            126,
            167,
            1062,
            285
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Kade consumes 773 calories per day. He/She is 9 years old. Brock is 32 years old. How much calories should Brock consume?",
        "answer": 1546,
        "options": [
            294,
            197,
            420,
            205,
            1546
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sergio consumes 776 calories per day. He/She is 13 years old. Camdyn is 23 years old. How much calories should Camdyn consume?",
        "answer": 1552,
        "options": [
            229,
            1552,
            196,
            406,
            294
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ezra consumes 558 calories per day. He/She is 10 years old. Quentin is 31 years old. How much calories should Quentin consume?",
        "answer": 1116,
        "options": [
            145,
            1116,
            299,
            197,
            181
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Paul consumes 939 calories per day. He/She is 5 years old. Yehuda is 37 years old. How much calories should Yehuda consume?",
        "answer": 1878,
        "options": [
            256,
            234,
            504,
            1878,
            330
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Drake consumes 743 calories per day. He/She is 15 years old. Cannon is 27 years old. How much calories should Cannon consume?",
        "answer": 1486,
        "options": [
            223,
            1486,
            174,
            391,
            294
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Manuel consumes 530 calories per day. He/She is 10 years old. Crew is 40 years old. How much calories should Crew consume?",
        "answer": 1060,
        "options": [
            132,
            222,
            1060,
            287,
            154
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Emmanuel consumes 916 calories per day. He/She is 5 years old. Cristiano is 32 years old. How much calories should Cristiano consume?",
        "answer": 1832,
        "options": [
            500,
            336,
            196,
            245,
            1832
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Elliott consumes 551 calories per day. He/She is 10 years old. Leonidas is 26 years old. How much calories should Leonidas consume?",
        "answer": 1102,
        "options": [
            155,
            309,
            1102,
            180,
            228
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Donovan consumes 788 calories per day. He/She is 13 years old. Jakob is 32 years old. How much calories should Jakob consume?",
        "answer": 1576,
        "options": [
            437,
            297,
            1576,
            184,
            209
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Thomas consumes 588 calories per day. He/She is 14 years old. Gerald is 24 years old. How much calories should Gerald consume?",
        "answer": 1176,
        "options": [
            1176,
            219,
            170,
            337,
            158
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sullivan consumes 793 calories per day. He/She is 13 years old. Mauricio is 22 years old. How much calories should Mauricio consume?",
        "answer": 1586,
        "options": [
            306,
            1586,
            168,
            217,
            407
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Brady consumes 954 calories per day. He/She is 9 years old. Dennis is 23 years old. How much calories should Dennis consume?",
        "answer": 1908,
        "options": [
            1908,
            511,
            205,
            268,
            351
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Edgar consumes 510 calories per day. He/She is 6 years old. Rey is 39 years old. How much calories should Rey consume?",
        "answer": 1020,
        "options": [
            137,
            193,
            133,
            270,
            1020
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Weston consumes 918 calories per day. He/She is 5 years old. Conrad is 33 years old. How much calories should Conrad consume?",
        "answer": 1836,
        "options": [
            333,
            478,
            217,
            242,
            1836
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Frederick consumes 849 calories per day. He/She is 11 years old. Kellan is 38 years old. How much calories should Kellan consume?",
        "answer": 1698,
        "options": [
            231,
            1698,
            326,
            440,
            184
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Trevor consumes 727 calories per day. He/She is 7 years old. Gatlin is 20 years old. How much calories should Gatlin consume?",
        "answer": 1454,
        "options": [
            1454,
            264,
            185,
            405,
            211
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Riley consumes 749 calories per day. He/She is 4 years old. Alberto is 29 years old. How much calories should Alberto consume?",
        "answer": 1498,
        "options": [
            396,
            289,
            167,
            203,
            1498
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Kai consumes 512 calories per day. He/She is 13 years old. Kingsley is 22 years old. How much calories should Kingsley consume?",
        "answer": 1024,
        "options": [
            139,
            1024,
            129,
            266,
            220
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Quinn consumes 901 calories per day. He/She is 10 years old. Ricky is 27 years old. How much calories should Ricky consume?",
        "answer": 1802,
        "options": [
            479,
            312,
            273,
            1802,
            225
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Elian consumes 681 calories per day. He/She is 3 years old. Leroy is 30 years old. How much calories should Leroy consume?",
        "answer": 1362,
        "options": [
            1362,
            181,
            351,
            248,
            182
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Shawn consumes 829 calories per day. He/She is 1 years old. Kelvin is 28 years old. How much calories should Kelvin consume?",
        "answer": 1658,
        "options": [
            1658,
            436,
            185,
            307,
            229
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Brady consumes 537 calories per day. He/She is 12 years old. Mathew is 34 years old. How much calories should Mathew consume?",
        "answer": 1074,
        "options": [
            153,
            281,
            214,
            1074,
            153
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Kason consumes 504 calories per day. He/She is 13 years old. Zechariah is 24 years old. How much calories should Zechariah consume?",
        "answer": 1008,
        "options": [
            281,
            164,
            145,
            179,
            1008
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jordan consumes 896 calories per day. He/She is 8 years old. Lucian is 30 years old. How much calories should Lucian consume?",
        "answer": 1792,
        "options": [
            471,
            339,
            198,
            1792,
            257
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Milan consumes 608 calories per day. He/She is 12 years old. Heath is 36 years old. How much calories should Heath consume?",
        "answer": 1216,
        "options": [
            171,
            1216,
            251,
            322,
            197
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Greyson consumes 672 calories per day. He/She is 3 years old. Johan is 26 years old. How much calories should Johan consume?",
        "answer": 1344,
        "options": [
            363,
            236,
            167,
            1344,
            200
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Nehemiah consumes 978 calories per day. He/She is 13 years old. Darren is 28 years old. How much calories should Darren consume?",
        "answer": 1956,
        "options": [
            347,
            285,
            224,
            1956,
            527
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sterling consumes 695 calories per day. He/She is 2 years old. Magnus is 28 years old. How much calories should Magnus consume?",
        "answer": 1390,
        "options": [
            162,
            1390,
            250,
            390,
            184
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Julian consumes 796 calories per day. He/She is 15 years old. Tadeo is 33 years old. How much calories should Tadeo consume?",
        "answer": 1592,
        "options": [
            224,
            299,
            430,
            1592,
            209
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Francis consumes 692 calories per day. He/She is 6 years old. Madden is 34 years old. How much calories should Madden consume?",
        "answer": 1384,
        "options": [
            1384,
            240,
            377,
            155,
            208
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Asher consumes 550 calories per day. He/She is 13 years old. Ulises is 29 years old. How much calories should Ulises consume?",
        "answer": 1100,
        "options": [
            157,
            1100,
            124,
            291,
            223
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Silas consumes 500 calories per day. He/She is 14 years old. Darwin is 29 years old. How much calories should Darwin consume?",
        "answer": 1000,
        "options": [
            137,
            152,
            1000,
            269,
            180
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Hector consumes 649 calories per day. He/She is 4 years old. Ronnie is 40 years old. How much calories should Ronnie consume?",
        "answer": 1298,
        "options": [
            258,
            1298,
            206,
            368,
            150
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Armani consumes 676 calories per day. He/She is 4 years old. Tomas is 27 years old. How much calories should Tomas consume?",
        "answer": 1352,
        "options": [
            1352,
            168,
            364,
            184,
            264
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Zander consumes 836 calories per day. He/She is 14 years old. Castiel is 29 years old. How much calories should Castiel consume?",
        "answer": 1672,
        "options": [
            322,
            220,
            209,
            464,
            1672
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Legend consumes 727 calories per day. He/She is 9 years old. Kye is 29 years old. How much calories should Kye consume?",
        "answer": 1454,
        "options": [
            200,
            175,
            278,
            1454,
            408
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Cristian consumes 854 calories per day. He/She is 10 years old. Alvaro is 39 years old. How much calories should Alvaro consume?",
        "answer": 1708,
        "options": [
            444,
            235,
            193,
            1708,
            324
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ricardo consumes 700 calories per day. He/She is 9 years old. Willie is 24 years old. How much calories should Willie consume?",
        "answer": 1400,
        "options": [
            223,
            256,
            362,
            173,
            1400
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Edward consumes 780 calories per day. He/She is 9 years old. Elisha is 33 years old. How much calories should Elisha consume?",
        "answer": 1560,
        "options": [
            178,
            286,
            211,
            434,
            1560
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Raymond consumes 578 calories per day. He/She is 14 years old. Lachlan is 32 years old. How much calories should Lachlan consume?",
        "answer": 1156,
        "options": [
            188,
            224,
            319,
            1156,
            147
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ricardo consumes 641 calories per day. He/She is 1 years old. Jesiah is 21 years old. How much calories should Jesiah consume?",
        "answer": 1282,
        "options": [
            181,
            345,
            253,
            1282,
            143
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Barrett consumes 679 calories per day. He/She is 13 years old. Jamie is 21 years old. How much calories should Jamie consume?",
        "answer": 1358,
        "options": [
            383,
            1358,
            262,
            159,
            211
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jesse consumes 796 calories per day. He/She is 7 years old. Cairo is 28 years old. How much calories should Cairo consume?",
        "answer": 1592,
        "options": [
            1592,
            216,
            284,
            181,
            434
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jack consumes 947 calories per day. He/She is 12 years old. Isaias is 37 years old. How much calories should Isaias consume?",
        "answer": 1894,
        "options": [
            489,
            204,
            358,
            263,
            1894
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Andre consumes 518 calories per day. He/She is 7 years old. Tadeo is 27 years old. How much calories should Tadeo consume?",
        "answer": 1036,
        "options": [
            1036,
            153,
            289,
            176,
            221
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Corey consumes 925 calories per day. He/She is 10 years old. Kamryn is 34 years old. How much calories should Kamryn consume?",
        "answer": 1850,
        "options": [
            1850,
            325,
            510,
            270,
            213
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Maximilian consumes 542 calories per day. He/She is 12 years old. Harley is 28 years old. How much calories should Harley consume?",
        "answer": 1084,
        "options": [
            227,
            132,
            1084,
            172,
            301
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jose consumes 700 calories per day. He/She is 6 years old. Abdullah is 23 years old. How much calories should Abdullah consume?",
        "answer": 1400,
        "options": [
            179,
            1400,
            200,
            362,
            274
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Zander consumes 776 calories per day. He/She is 12 years old. Madden is 29 years old. How much calories should Madden consume?",
        "answer": 1552,
        "options": [
            170,
            276,
            242,
            1552,
            429
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Warren consumes 739 calories per day. He/She is 4 years old. Aldo is 30 years old. How much calories should Aldo consume?",
        "answer": 1478,
        "options": [
            1478,
            163,
            257,
            403,
            228
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jaden consumes 952 calories per day. He/She is 12 years old. Willie is 38 years old. How much calories should Willie consume?",
        "answer": 1904,
        "options": [
            331,
            222,
            494,
            275,
            1904
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Vincent consumes 684 calories per day. He/She is 11 years old. Jerry is 24 years old. How much calories should Jerry consume?",
        "answer": 1368,
        "options": [
            1368,
            177,
            273,
            354,
            209
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Remington consumes 576 calories per day. He/She is 12 years old. Ariel is 21 years old. How much calories should Ariel consume?",
        "answer": 1152,
        "options": [
            239,
            1152,
            158,
            147,
            307
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "William consumes 913 calories per day. He/She is 7 years old. Scott is 28 years old. How much calories should Scott consume?",
        "answer": 1826,
        "options": [
            195,
            1826,
            488,
            273,
            321
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Conor consumes 956 calories per day. He/She is 15 years old. Ben is 27 years old. How much calories should Ben consume?",
        "answer": 1912,
        "options": [
            505,
            337,
            205,
            1912,
            266
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Kyson consumes 894 calories per day. He/She is 5 years old. Koda is 24 years old. How much calories should Koda consume?",
        "answer": 1788,
        "options": [
            262,
            484,
            346,
            1788,
            191
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Johnny consumes 967 calories per day. He/She is 2 years old. Alfred is 22 years old. How much calories should Alfred consume?",
        "answer": 1934,
        "options": [
            1934,
            357,
            279,
            225,
            520
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Victor consumes 530 calories per day. He/She is 1 years old. Cason is 34 years old. How much calories should Cason consume?",
        "answer": 1060,
        "options": [
            1060,
            153,
            218,
            179,
            298
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Malachi consumes 824 calories per day. He/She is 6 years old. Dustin is 30 years old. How much calories should Dustin consume?",
        "answer": 1648,
        "options": [
            438,
            179,
            219,
            317,
            1648
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Warren consumes 612 calories per day. He/She is 10 years old. Gus is 32 years old. How much calories should Gus consume?",
        "answer": 1224,
        "options": [
            219,
            336,
            1224,
            182,
            140
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Elian consumes 564 calories per day. He/She is 15 years old. Isaias is 35 years old. How much calories should Isaias consume?",
        "answer": 1128,
        "options": [
            155,
            137,
            314,
            217,
            1128
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ryan consumes 840 calories per day. He/She is 13 years old. Rene is 20 years old. How much calories should Rene consume?",
        "answer": 1680,
        "options": [
            451,
            256,
            1680,
            193,
            328
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Lorenzo consumes 892 calories per day. He/She is 12 years old. Alessandro is 21 years old. How much calories should Alessandro consume?",
        "answer": 1784,
        "options": [
            479,
            208,
            266,
            338,
            1784
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Elliot consumes 612 calories per day. He/She is 13 years old. Abdullah is 24 years old. How much calories should Abdullah consume?",
        "answer": 1224,
        "options": [
            137,
            1224,
            184,
            347,
            242
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jaxon consumes 769 calories per day. He/She is 1 years old. Clay is 37 years old. How much calories should Clay consume?",
        "answer": 1538,
        "options": [
            1538,
            292,
            199,
            207,
            423
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Leonardo consumes 892 calories per day. He/She is 14 years old. Jerry is 38 years old. How much calories should Jerry consume?",
        "answer": 1784,
        "options": [
            343,
            1784,
            235,
            198,
            470
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Enzo consumes 758 calories per day. He/She is 1 years old. Zev is 26 years old. How much calories should Zev consume?",
        "answer": 1516,
        "options": [
            424,
            228,
            272,
            1516,
            197
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Rocco consumes 718 calories per day. He/She is 5 years old. Raylan is 32 years old. How much calories should Raylan consume?",
        "answer": 1436,
        "options": [
            194,
            285,
            1436,
            398,
            165
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Kolton consumes 633 calories per day. He/She is 15 years old. Kyree is 31 years old. How much calories should Kyree consume?",
        "answer": 1266,
        "options": [
            1266,
            351,
            191,
            256,
            145
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Raiden consumes 654 calories per day. He/She is 7 years old. Reece is 37 years old. How much calories should Reece consume?",
        "answer": 1308,
        "options": [
            370,
            1308,
            236,
            161,
            177
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Julius consumes 792 calories per day. He/She is 11 years old. Sonny is 27 years old. How much calories should Sonny consume?",
        "answer": 1584,
        "options": [
            1584,
            427,
            209,
            172,
            286
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Shawn and Aries are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Shawn consumes 2376 calories per day whereas Aries consumes 2082 calories per day. Shawn is more weight than Aries.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Jonathan and Emmitt are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Jonathan consumes 2873 calories per day whereas Emmitt consumes 1607 calories per day. Jonathan is stronger than Emmitt.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Moises and Harper are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Moises consumes 2597 calories per day whereas Harper consumes 1590 calories per day. Moises is more weight than Harper.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Landon and Ernesto are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Landon consumes 2590 calories per day whereas Ernesto consumes 2386 calories per day. Landon is bulkier than Ernesto.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Philip and Ares are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Philip consumes 2905 calories per day whereas Ares consumes 2165 calories per day. Philip is stronger than Ares.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Leon and Nickolas are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Leon consumes 1713 calories per day whereas Nickolas consumes 2736 calories per day. Leon is bulkier than Nickolas.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Dominick and Vivaan are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Dominick consumes 2482 calories per day whereas Vivaan consumes 2328 calories per day. Dominick is bulkier than Vivaan.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both River and Bridger are of same age. Both do same physical activity. River consumes 2413 calories per day whereas Bridger consumes 2339 calories per day. River is heavier than Bridger.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Abel and Louie are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Abel consumes 1580 calories per day whereas Louie consumes 2305 calories per day. Abel is more weight than Louie.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Daxton and Lionel are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Daxton consumes 2952 calories per day whereas Lionel consumes 2334 calories per day. Daxton is stronger than Lionel.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Oscar and Sutton are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Oscar consumes 2525 calories per day whereas Sutton consumes 2194 calories per day. Oscar is stronger than Sutton.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Adonis and Davis are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Adonis consumes 2329 calories per day whereas Davis consumes 2713 calories per day. Adonis is heavier than Davis.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Clark and Westley are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Clark consumes 1835 calories per day whereas Westley consumes 1529 calories per day. Clark is bulkier than Westley.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Robert and Samir are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Robert consumes 2399 calories per day whereas Samir consumes 2685 calories per day. Robert is heavier than Samir.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Alexis and Mohammad are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Alexis consumes 1638 calories per day whereas Mohammad consumes 2402 calories per day. Alexis is more weight than Mohammad.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Clark and Kristopher are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Clark consumes 1547 calories per day whereas Kristopher consumes 2283 calories per day. Clark is bulkier than Kristopher.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Rodrigo and Apollo are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Rodrigo consumes 2787 calories per day whereas Apollo consumes 1591 calories per day. Rodrigo is heavier than Apollo.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Sawyer and Cain are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Sawyer consumes 1771 calories per day whereas Cain consumes 2622 calories per day. Sawyer is bulkier than Cain.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Enrique and Allan are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Enrique consumes 2213 calories per day whereas Allan consumes 1976 calories per day. Enrique is stronger than Allan.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Jayden and Chris are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Jayden consumes 1664 calories per day whereas Chris consumes 1550 calories per day. Jayden is more weight than Chris.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Alijah and Kelvin are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Alijah consumes 2607 calories per day whereas Kelvin consumes 1971 calories per day. Alijah is stronger than Kelvin.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Sage and Zechariah are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Sage consumes 2453 calories per day whereas Zechariah consumes 2720 calories per day. Sage is more weight than Zechariah.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Leland and Brett are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Leland consumes 1686 calories per day whereas Brett consumes 1894 calories per day. Leland is stronger than Brett.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Ashton and Maison are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Ashton consumes 2143 calories per day whereas Maison consumes 2020 calories per day. Ashton is heavier than Maison.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Jayce and Nova are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Jayce consumes 2351 calories per day whereas Nova consumes 2935 calories per day. Jayce is heavier than Nova.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Augustus and Wayne are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Augustus consumes 2567 calories per day whereas Wayne consumes 1865 calories per day. Augustus is more weight than Wayne.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Isaac and Kyree are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Isaac consumes 2385 calories per day whereas Kyree consumes 2953 calories per day. Isaac is more weight than Kyree.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Joaquin and Vivaan are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Joaquin consumes 2333 calories per day whereas Vivaan consumes 1736 calories per day. Joaquin is bulkier than Vivaan.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Edwin and Callen are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Edwin consumes 2551 calories per day whereas Callen consumes 2548 calories per day. Edwin is stronger than Callen.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Matthew and Brock are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Matthew consumes 1906 calories per day whereas Brock consumes 1922 calories per day. Matthew is heavier than Brock.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Barrett and Deshawn are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Barrett consumes 2228 calories per day whereas Deshawn consumes 2603 calories per day. Barrett is bulkier than Deshawn.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Arlo and Zaid are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Arlo consumes 2144 calories per day whereas Zaid consumes 2710 calories per day. Arlo is bulkier than Zaid.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Deacon and Brayan are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Deacon consumes 1793 calories per day whereas Brayan consumes 2620 calories per day. Deacon is more weight than Brayan.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Knox and Colby are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Knox consumes 1652 calories per day whereas Colby consumes 2964 calories per day. Knox is more weight than Colby.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Lukas and Lyle are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Lukas consumes 2634 calories per day whereas Lyle consumes 1701 calories per day. Lukas is bulkier than Lyle.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Esteban and Sincere are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Esteban consumes 2374 calories per day whereas Sincere consumes 1582 calories per day. Esteban is stronger than Sincere.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Kieran and Ignacio are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Kieran consumes 2472 calories per day whereas Ignacio consumes 2885 calories per day. Kieran is more weight than Ignacio.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Arjun and Misael are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Arjun consumes 2224 calories per day whereas Misael consumes 1602 calories per day. Arjun is heavier than Misael.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Frederick and Bridger are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Frederick consumes 2448 calories per day whereas Bridger consumes 1987 calories per day. Frederick is more weight than Bridger.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Kendrick and Thatcher are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Kendrick consumes 1744 calories per day whereas Thatcher consumes 2416 calories per day. Kendrick is bulkier than Thatcher.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Tucker and Izaiah are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Tucker consumes 2247 calories per day whereas Izaiah consumes 2895 calories per day. Tucker is stronger than Izaiah.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Wyatt and Duke are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Wyatt consumes 1798 calories per day whereas Duke consumes 2137 calories per day. Wyatt is more weight than Duke.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Oakley and Juelz are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Oakley consumes 2857 calories per day whereas Juelz consumes 2270 calories per day. Oakley is heavier than Juelz.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Rhett and Kobe are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Rhett consumes 2462 calories per day whereas Kobe consumes 2358 calories per day. Rhett is bulkier than Kobe.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Maxwell and Kaysen are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Maxwell consumes 2658 calories per day whereas Kaysen consumes 2564 calories per day. Maxwell is stronger than Kaysen.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Kyler and Lachlan are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Kyler consumes 1520 calories per day whereas Lachlan consumes 1500 calories per day. Kyler is heavier than Lachlan.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Walter and Marlon are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Walter consumes 1915 calories per day whereas Marlon consumes 2409 calories per day. Walter is bulkier than Marlon.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Walker and Coen are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Walker consumes 1916 calories per day whereas Coen consumes 2221 calories per day. Walker is more weight than Coen.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Steven and Westley are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Steven consumes 2456 calories per day whereas Westley consumes 2662 calories per day. Steven is stronger than Westley.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Gregory and Lochlan are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Gregory consumes 2061 calories per day whereas Lochlan consumes 2956 calories per day. Gregory is bulkier than Lochlan.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both George and Conrad are of same age. Both do same physical activity. George consumes 2813 calories per day whereas Conrad consumes 1823 calories per day. George is more weight than Conrad.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Benjamin and Hamza are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Benjamin consumes 2940 calories per day whereas Hamza consumes 1863 calories per day. Benjamin is stronger than Hamza.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Marshall and Marcelo are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Marshall consumes 2009 calories per day whereas Marcelo consumes 2311 calories per day. Marshall is more weight than Marcelo.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Zachary and Randall are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Zachary consumes 1678 calories per day whereas Randall consumes 1870 calories per day. Zachary is heavier than Randall.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Ricardo and Terrence are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Ricardo consumes 2837 calories per day whereas Terrence consumes 2482 calories per day. Ricardo is heavier than Terrence.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Hendrix and Maxton are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Hendrix consumes 2437 calories per day whereas Maxton consumes 2174 calories per day. Hendrix is bulkier than Maxton.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Silas and Bryant are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Silas consumes 2412 calories per day whereas Bryant consumes 1795 calories per day. Silas is stronger than Bryant.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Matteo and Jacoby are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Matteo consumes 2215 calories per day whereas Jacoby consumes 2546 calories per day. Matteo is stronger than Jacoby.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Jayden and Kannon are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Jayden consumes 2905 calories per day whereas Kannon consumes 1535 calories per day. Jayden is bulkier than Kannon.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Vincent and Tatum are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Vincent consumes 2958 calories per day whereas Tatum consumes 2885 calories per day. Vincent is heavier than Tatum.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Deacon and Baylor are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Deacon consumes 2973 calories per day whereas Baylor consumes 2410 calories per day. Deacon is stronger than Baylor.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Sergio and Salvador are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Sergio consumes 2140 calories per day whereas Salvador consumes 2148 calories per day. Sergio is stronger than Salvador.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Johnathan and Samir are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Johnathan consumes 1940 calories per day whereas Samir consumes 1639 calories per day. Johnathan is stronger than Samir.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Zane and Darian are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Zane consumes 2134 calories per day whereas Darian consumes 1594 calories per day. Zane is bulkier than Darian.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Lawrence and Saint are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Lawrence consumes 2875 calories per day whereas Saint consumes 2158 calories per day. Lawrence is bulkier than Saint.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Harvey and Achilles are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Harvey consumes 2920 calories per day whereas Achilles consumes 2368 calories per day. Harvey is bulkier than Achilles.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Kaden and Aldo are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Kaden consumes 2959 calories per day whereas Aldo consumes 2641 calories per day. Kaden is bulkier than Aldo.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Nolan and Camilo are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Nolan consumes 2802 calories per day whereas Camilo consumes 1553 calories per day. Nolan is heavier than Camilo.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Kaiden and Coen are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Kaiden consumes 2523 calories per day whereas Coen consumes 1898 calories per day. Kaiden is heavier than Coen.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Isaac and Cairo are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Isaac consumes 2677 calories per day whereas Cairo consumes 2704 calories per day. Isaac is stronger than Cairo.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Hunter and Kohen are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Hunter consumes 2268 calories per day whereas Kohen consumes 2233 calories per day. Hunter is heavier than Kohen.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Khalil and Tommy are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Khalil consumes 1755 calories per day whereas Tommy consumes 1851 calories per day. Khalil is heavier than Tommy.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both King and London are of same age. Both do same physical activity. King consumes 1899 calories per day whereas London consumes 1542 calories per day. King is bulkier than London.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Garrett and Wilson are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Garrett consumes 1631 calories per day whereas Wilson consumes 2587 calories per day. Garrett is stronger than Wilson.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Iker and Valentin are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Iker consumes 2408 calories per day whereas Valentin consumes 2533 calories per day. Iker is bulkier than Valentin.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Diego and Ben are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Diego consumes 2009 calories per day whereas Ben consumes 2002 calories per day. Diego is bulkier than Ben.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Grady and Rex are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Grady consumes 1670 calories per day whereas Rex consumes 1849 calories per day. Grady is stronger than Rex.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Brycen and Mekhi are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Brycen consumes 2877 calories per day whereas Mekhi consumes 2026 calories per day. Brycen is heavier than Mekhi.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Kason and Davian are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Kason consumes 1932 calories per day whereas Davian consumes 1510 calories per day. Kason is heavier than Davian.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Gianni and Zyaire are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Gianni consumes 2009 calories per day whereas Zyaire consumes 2983 calories per day. Gianni is stronger than Zyaire.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Pablo and Trenton are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Pablo consumes 1687 calories per day whereas Trenton consumes 2029 calories per day. Pablo is bulkier than Trenton.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Maximilian and Karsyn are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Maximilian consumes 1740 calories per day whereas Karsyn consumes 1589 calories per day. Maximilian is more weight than Karsyn.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Rowan and Howard are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Rowan consumes 1636 calories per day whereas Howard consumes 2769 calories per day. Rowan is bulkier than Howard.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Shawn and Ahmad are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Shawn consumes 2483 calories per day whereas Ahmad consumes 2384 calories per day. Shawn is more weight than Ahmad.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Bennett and Nelson are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Bennett consumes 1750 calories per day whereas Nelson consumes 2214 calories per day. Bennett is stronger than Nelson.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Martin and Makai are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Martin consumes 2855 calories per day whereas Makai consumes 2836 calories per day. Martin is stronger than Makai.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Nathan and Trent are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Nathan consumes 2075 calories per day whereas Trent consumes 2869 calories per day. Nathan is stronger than Trent.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Paul and Davis are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Paul consumes 2759 calories per day whereas Davis consumes 2457 calories per day. Paul is stronger than Davis.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Cesar and Reginald are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Cesar consumes 1799 calories per day whereas Reginald consumes 2082 calories per day. Cesar is bulkier than Reginald.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Christian and Kingsley are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Christian consumes 2350 calories per day whereas Kingsley consumes 1865 calories per day. Christian is more weight than Kingsley.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Kyler and Anakin are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Kyler consumes 1860 calories per day whereas Anakin consumes 2194 calories per day. Kyler is bulkier than Anakin.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Marshall and Harold are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Marshall consumes 2336 calories per day whereas Harold consumes 1858 calories per day. Marshall is stronger than Harold.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Joseph and Howard are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Joseph consumes 2644 calories per day whereas Howard consumes 2175 calories per day. Joseph is bulkier than Howard.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Johnathan and Salvador are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Johnathan consumes 1637 calories per day whereas Salvador consumes 2803 calories per day. Johnathan is heavier than Salvador.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Malcolm and Zaid are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Malcolm consumes 1704 calories per day whereas Zaid consumes 2467 calories per day. Malcolm is stronger than Zaid.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Corbin and Bode are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Corbin consumes 2215 calories per day whereas Bode consumes 2824 calories per day. Corbin is bulkier than Bode.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Eli and Mustafa are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Eli consumes 2954 calories per day whereas Mustafa consumes 1505 calories per day. Eli is heavier than Mustafa.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Marcus and Ahmed are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Marcus consumes 2461 calories per day whereas Ahmed consumes 2571 calories per day. Marcus is more weight than Ahmed.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Elliott and Ahmir are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Elliott consumes 1763 calories per day whereas Ahmir consumes 1831 calories per day. Elliott is stronger than Ahmir.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Justin and Amos are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Justin consumes 1977 calories per day whereas Amos consumes 2571 calories per day. Justin is heavier than Amos.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Javier and Zechariah are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Javier consumes 2391 calories per day whereas Zechariah consumes 2249 calories per day. Javier is bulkier than Zechariah.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Cody and Emory are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Cody consumes 2148 calories per day whereas Emory consumes 1863 calories per day. Cody is more weight than Emory.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Porter and Mohammed are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Porter consumes 2799 calories per day whereas Mohammed consumes 2430 calories per day. Porter is heavier than Mohammed.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Shane and Ramon are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Shane consumes 2096 calories per day whereas Ramon consumes 2525 calories per day. Shane is more weight than Ramon.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Eden and Lian are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Eden consumes 1886 calories per day whereas Lian consumes 2025 calories per day. Eden is stronger than Lian.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Aidan and Keagan are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Aidan consumes 2034 calories per day whereas Keagan consumes 1998 calories per day. Aidan is heavier than Keagan.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Levi and Madden are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Levi consumes 2432 calories per day whereas Madden consumes 1633 calories per day. Levi is stronger than Madden.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Elliott and Amos are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Elliott consumes 2575 calories per day whereas Amos consumes 2143 calories per day. Elliott is stronger than Amos.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Kevin and Ernest are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Kevin consumes 2628 calories per day whereas Ernest consumes 2282 calories per day. Kevin is stronger than Ernest.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Adam and Ben are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Adam consumes 2554 calories per day whereas Ben consumes 1845 calories per day. Adam is more weight than Ben.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Kayden and Kody are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Kayden consumes 2385 calories per day whereas Kody consumes 2885 calories per day. Kayden is bulkier than Kody.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Drew and Tripp are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Drew consumes 2173 calories per day whereas Tripp consumes 2831 calories per day. Drew is stronger than Tripp.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Kevin and Alvin are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Kevin consumes 2859 calories per day whereas Alvin consumes 2787 calories per day. Kevin is bulkier than Alvin.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Aidan and Camilo are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Aidan consumes 2332 calories per day whereas Camilo consumes 1743 calories per day. Aidan is bulkier than Camilo.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Nicolas and Ford are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Nicolas consumes 1818 calories per day whereas Ford consumes 1537 calories per day. Nicolas is bulkier than Ford.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Marcus and Ulises are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Marcus consumes 2415 calories per day whereas Ulises consumes 2145 calories per day. Marcus is heavier than Ulises.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Johnathan and Saul are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Johnathan consumes 2945 calories per day whereas Saul consumes 1501 calories per day. Johnathan is more weight than Saul.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Tobias and Alden are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Tobias consumes 2936 calories per day whereas Alden consumes 2121 calories per day. Tobias is more weight than Alden.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Cody and Issac are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Cody consumes 2781 calories per day whereas Issac consumes 1573 calories per day. Cody is stronger than Issac.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Jesus and Jordy are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Jesus consumes 2130 calories per day whereas Jordy consumes 2743 calories per day. Jesus is bulkier than Jordy.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Enrique and Dariel are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Enrique consumes 2749 calories per day whereas Dariel consumes 1527 calories per day. Enrique is bulkier than Dariel.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Kaden and Crosby are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Kaden consumes 2486 calories per day whereas Crosby consumes 2190 calories per day. Kaden is heavier than Crosby.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Declan and Ariel are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Declan consumes 1735 calories per day whereas Ariel consumes 2577 calories per day. Declan is heavier than Ariel.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Jaiden and Douglas are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Jaiden consumes 1673 calories per day whereas Douglas consumes 2542 calories per day. Jaiden is more weight than Douglas.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Elias and Davian are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Elias consumes 2863 calories per day whereas Davian consumes 1821 calories per day. Elias is stronger than Davian.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Aiden and Mitchell are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Aiden consumes 2688 calories per day whereas Mitchell consumes 1624 calories per day. Aiden is heavier than Mitchell.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Oliver and Kabir are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Oliver consumes 2202 calories per day whereas Kabir consumes 2155 calories per day. Oliver is heavier than Kabir.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Harvey and Idris are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Harvey consumes 2861 calories per day whereas Idris consumes 2923 calories per day. Harvey is more weight than Idris.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Zander and Anakin are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Zander consumes 2073 calories per day whereas Anakin consumes 1615 calories per day. Zander is heavier than Anakin.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Nasir and Ahmir are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Nasir consumes 1576 calories per day whereas Ahmir consumes 2573 calories per day. Nasir is bulkier than Ahmir.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Oscar and Trey are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Oscar consumes 2160 calories per day whereas Trey consumes 1785 calories per day. Oscar is more weight than Trey.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Bodhi and Castiel are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Bodhi consumes 2109 calories per day whereas Castiel consumes 2430 calories per day. Bodhi is bulkier than Castiel.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Erick and Roland are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Erick consumes 2339 calories per day whereas Roland consumes 1962 calories per day. Erick is stronger than Roland.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Avery and Callum are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Avery consumes 2220 calories per day whereas Callum consumes 2572 calories per day. Avery is bulkier than Callum.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Derek and Gustavo are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Derek consumes 2804 calories per day whereas Gustavo consumes 2665 calories per day. Derek is bulkier than Gustavo.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Atlas and Yusuf are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Atlas consumes 2689 calories per day whereas Yusuf consumes 2072 calories per day. Atlas is heavier than Yusuf.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Dante and Westin are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Dante consumes 1635 calories per day whereas Westin consumes 2888 calories per day. Dante is stronger than Westin.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Luke and Marc are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Luke consumes 2974 calories per day whereas Marc consumes 1516 calories per day. Luke is heavier than Marc.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Riley and Boston are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Riley consumes 2639 calories per day whereas Boston consumes 2751 calories per day. Riley is more weight than Boston.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Kieran and Tadeo are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Kieran consumes 2859 calories per day whereas Tadeo consumes 2619 calories per day. Kieran is heavier than Tadeo.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Donovan and Idris are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Donovan consumes 2492 calories per day whereas Idris consumes 2547 calories per day. Donovan is heavier than Idris.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Bennett and Ulises are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Bennett consumes 2571 calories per day whereas Ulises consumes 1944 calories per day. Bennett is heavier than Ulises.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Remington and Dominik are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Remington consumes 1907 calories per day whereas Dominik consumes 2267 calories per day. Remington is stronger than Dominik.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Luis and Chad are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Luis consumes 1532 calories per day whereas Chad consumes 1670 calories per day. Luis is heavier than Chad.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Luka and Vicente are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Luka consumes 1538 calories per day whereas Vicente consumes 2033 calories per day. Luka is bulkier than Vicente.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Malcolm and Demetrius are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Malcolm consumes 2569 calories per day whereas Demetrius consumes 1760 calories per day. Malcolm is stronger than Demetrius.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Noel and Orlando are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Noel consumes 2449 calories per day whereas Orlando consumes 2239 calories per day. Noel is more weight than Orlando.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Carlos and Dustin are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Carlos consumes 2569 calories per day whereas Dustin consumes 2995 calories per day. Carlos is heavier than Dustin.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Jaxton and Valentino are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Jaxton consumes 2992 calories per day whereas Valentino consumes 1873 calories per day. Jaxton is more weight than Valentino.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Richard and Sutton are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Richard consumes 2815 calories per day whereas Sutton consumes 1781 calories per day. Richard is stronger than Sutton.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Jayden and Emery are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Jayden consumes 2277 calories per day whereas Emery consumes 1615 calories per day. Jayden is heavier than Emery.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Braxton and Casen are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Braxton consumes 1723 calories per day whereas Casen consumes 2657 calories per day. Braxton is bulkier than Casen.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Andy and Ahmad are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Andy consumes 2161 calories per day whereas Ahmad consumes 1545 calories per day. Andy is stronger than Ahmad.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Jorge and Jerome are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Jorge consumes 2879 calories per day whereas Jerome consumes 2481 calories per day. Jorge is stronger than Jerome.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Dax and Elon are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Dax consumes 1970 calories per day whereas Elon consumes 2806 calories per day. Dax is more weight than Elon.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Cayden and Keenan are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Cayden consumes 2623 calories per day whereas Keenan consumes 1543 calories per day. Cayden is heavier than Keenan.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Ronan and Lennon are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Ronan consumes 2610 calories per day whereas Lennon consumes 2606 calories per day. Ronan is heavier than Lennon.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Steven and Brentley are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Steven consumes 2272 calories per day whereas Brentley consumes 2293 calories per day. Steven is stronger than Brentley.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Princeton and Denver are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Princeton consumes 2889 calories per day whereas Denver consumes 2780 calories per day. Princeton is more weight than Denver.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Samuel and Darian are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Samuel consumes 2949 calories per day whereas Darian consumes 2653 calories per day. Samuel is more weight than Darian.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Corbin and Quinton are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Corbin consumes 2945 calories per day whereas Quinton consumes 2947 calories per day. Corbin is more weight than Quinton.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Paxton and Yahir are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Paxton consumes 1966 calories per day whereas Yahir consumes 1970 calories per day. Paxton is more weight than Yahir.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Sterling and Brendan are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Sterling consumes 2944 calories per day whereas Brendan consumes 1676 calories per day. Sterling is bulkier than Brendan.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Barrett and Dangelo are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Barrett consumes 2931 calories per day whereas Dangelo consumes 2851 calories per day. Barrett is more weight than Dangelo.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Rhys and Elisha are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Rhys consumes 2210 calories per day whereas Elisha consumes 2754 calories per day. Rhys is heavier than Elisha.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Remy and Harlan are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Remy consumes 2847 calories per day whereas Harlan consumes 2415 calories per day. Remy is stronger than Harlan.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Owen and Koda are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Owen consumes 2577 calories per day whereas Koda consumes 1797 calories per day. Owen is bulkier than Koda.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Declan and Lance are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Declan consumes 2837 calories per day whereas Lance consumes 1908 calories per day. Declan is bulkier than Lance.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Augustus and Reign are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Augustus consumes 2028 calories per day whereas Reign consumes 2379 calories per day. Augustus is more weight than Reign.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Cooper and Trenton are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Cooper consumes 2347 calories per day whereas Trenton consumes 2218 calories per day. Cooper is stronger than Trenton.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Roberto and Vincenzo are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Roberto consumes 1533 calories per day whereas Vincenzo consumes 2442 calories per day. Roberto is heavier than Vincenzo.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Devin and Devon are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Devin consumes 2144 calories per day whereas Devon consumes 2035 calories per day. Devin is stronger than Devon.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Nash and Titan are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Nash consumes 2568 calories per day whereas Titan consumes 2785 calories per day. Nash is heavier than Titan.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Ronan and Lucca are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Ronan consumes 2210 calories per day whereas Lucca consumes 2845 calories per day. Ronan is heavier than Lucca.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Kaden and Alessandro are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Kaden consumes 2011 calories per day whereas Alessandro consumes 1718 calories per day. Kaden is heavier than Alessandro.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Jonah and Kace are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Jonah consumes 2111 calories per day whereas Kace consumes 2497 calories per day. Jonah is stronger than Kace.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Leonardo and Valentino are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Leonardo consumes 2889 calories per day whereas Valentino consumes 2253 calories per day. Leonardo is heavier than Valentino.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Colt and Keagan are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Colt consumes 2614 calories per day whereas Keagan consumes 1926 calories per day. Colt is bulkier than Keagan.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Carter and Titan are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Carter consumes 2087 calories per day whereas Titan consumes 2281 calories per day. Carter is bulkier than Titan.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Malcolm and Kylo are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Malcolm consumes 2554 calories per day whereas Kylo consumes 1544 calories per day. Malcolm is more weight than Kylo.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Ismael and Baker are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Ismael consumes 2539 calories per day whereas Baker consumes 2670 calories per day. Ismael is bulkier than Baker.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Legend and Wells are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Legend consumes 2034 calories per day whereas Wells consumes 1712 calories per day. Legend is stronger than Wells.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Amari and Salvatore are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Amari consumes 2245 calories per day whereas Salvatore consumes 1669 calories per day. Amari is more weight than Salvatore.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Ismael and Fox are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Ismael consumes 2066 calories per day whereas Fox consumes 1556 calories per day. Ismael is bulkier than Fox.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Noel and Kamari are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Noel consumes 2371 calories per day whereas Kamari consumes 1847 calories per day. Noel is stronger than Kamari.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Jaylen and Ford are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Jaylen consumes 1573 calories per day whereas Ford consumes 1951 calories per day. Jaylen is stronger than Ford.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Eric and Brentley are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Eric consumes 1701 calories per day whereas Brentley consumes 1570 calories per day. Eric is bulkier than Brentley.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Charles and Wilder are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Charles consumes 2102 calories per day whereas Wilder consumes 2462 calories per day. Charles is heavier than Wilder.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Milo and Reuben are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Milo consumes 2924 calories per day whereas Reuben consumes 2620 calories per day. Milo is heavier than Reuben.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Diego and Vance are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Diego consumes 1865 calories per day whereas Vance consumes 1995 calories per day. Diego is more weight than Vance.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Maximiliano and Cristiano are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Maximiliano consumes 1969 calories per day whereas Cristiano consumes 2129 calories per day. Maximiliano is more weight than Cristiano.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Christian and Cedric are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Christian consumes 2355 calories per day whereas Cedric consumes 1970 calories per day. Christian is stronger than Cedric.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Zayden and Vincenzo are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Zayden consumes 1811 calories per day whereas Vincenzo consumes 2456 calories per day. Zayden is stronger than Vincenzo.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Sebastian and Dwayne are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Sebastian consumes 1757 calories per day whereas Dwayne consumes 2458 calories per day. Sebastian is heavier than Dwayne.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Aiden and Julien are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Aiden consumes 1760 calories per day whereas Julien consumes 1665 calories per day. Aiden is stronger than Julien.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Benson and Lucca are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Benson consumes 1598 calories per day whereas Lucca consumes 1685 calories per day. Benson is more weight than Lucca.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Hank and Trent are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Hank consumes 1878 calories per day whereas Trent consumes 2761 calories per day. Hank is bulkier than Trent.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Zayne and Reginald are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Zayne consumes 2346 calories per day whereas Reginald consumes 2140 calories per day. Zayne is heavier than Reginald.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Jaxon and Keenan are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Jaxon consumes 1592 calories per day whereas Keenan consumes 1777 calories per day. Jaxon is stronger than Keenan.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Stephen and Jordy are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Stephen consumes 1816 calories per day whereas Jordy consumes 2682 calories per day. Stephen is heavier than Jordy.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Andre and Jerome are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Andre consumes 2292 calories per day whereas Jerome consumes 2482 calories per day. Andre is more weight than Jerome.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Damian and Dustin are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Damian consumes 1908 calories per day whereas Dustin consumes 2341 calories per day. Damian is more weight than Dustin.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Zayn and Jadiel are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Zayn consumes 1981 calories per day whereas Jadiel consumes 1613 calories per day. Zayn is heavier than Jadiel.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Nikolai and Casey are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Nikolai consumes 1508 calories per day whereas Casey consumes 2356 calories per day. Nikolai is bulkier than Casey.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Gunner and Mustafa are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Gunner consumes 2636 calories per day whereas Mustafa consumes 2403 calories per day. Gunner is heavier than Mustafa.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Omari and Shepherd are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Omari consumes 1866 calories per day whereas Shepherd consumes 2838 calories per day. Omari is more weight than Shepherd.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Damien and Julien are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Damien consumes 2297 calories per day whereas Julien consumes 2301 calories per day. Damien is bulkier than Julien.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Jay and Carmelo are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Jay consumes 2681 calories per day whereas Carmelo consumes 2228 calories per day. Jay is heavier than Carmelo.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Cesar and Aydin are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Cesar consumes 1747 calories per day whereas Aydin consumes 1884 calories per day. Cesar is heavier than Aydin.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Royce and Baylor are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Royce consumes 2007 calories per day whereas Baylor consumes 2093 calories per day. Royce is bulkier than Baylor.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Kade and Ahmad are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Kade consumes 2614 calories per day whereas Ahmad consumes 1971 calories per day. Kade is stronger than Ahmad.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Ellis and Cain are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Ellis consumes 2023 calories per day whereas Cain consumes 2477 calories per day. Ellis is more weight than Cain.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Killian and Wilder are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Killian consumes 2663 calories per day whereas Wilder consumes 2756 calories per day. Killian is heavier than Wilder.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Angelo and Reuben are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Angelo consumes 2300 calories per day whereas Reuben consumes 2753 calories per day. Angelo is more weight than Reuben.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Alexander and Kannon are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Alexander consumes 1894 calories per day whereas Kannon consumes 2792 calories per day. Alexander is more weight than Kannon.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Brantley and Louie are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Brantley consumes 2622 calories per day whereas Louie consumes 1922 calories per day. Brantley is heavier than Louie.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Moses and Noe are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Moses consumes 2813 calories per day whereas Noe consumes 1777 calories per day. Moses is more weight than Noe.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Isaac and Alfredo are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Isaac consumes 1941 calories per day whereas Alfredo consumes 2080 calories per day. Isaac is stronger than Alfredo.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Greyson and Briggs are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Greyson consumes 2942 calories per day whereas Briggs consumes 1987 calories per day. Greyson is bulkier than Briggs.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Alex and Niko are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Alex consumes 2359 calories per day whereas Niko consumes 2021 calories per day. Alex is bulkier than Niko.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Michael and Tristen are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Michael consumes 2973 calories per day whereas Tristen consumes 2239 calories per day. Michael is heavier than Tristen.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Remy and Aldo are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Remy consumes 2106 calories per day whereas Aldo consumes 2521 calories per day. Remy is stronger than Aldo.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Allen and Jakob are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Allen consumes 2356 calories per day whereas Jakob consumes 2043 calories per day. Allen is heavier than Jakob.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Kingston and Camilo are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Kingston consumes 1873 calories per day whereas Camilo consumes 2950 calories per day. Kingston is stronger than Camilo.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Maddox and Juelz are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Maddox consumes 1558 calories per day whereas Juelz consumes 2317 calories per day. Maddox is heavier than Juelz.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Cooper and Hezekiah are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Cooper consumes 1844 calories per day whereas Hezekiah consumes 2505 calories per day. Cooper is bulkier than Hezekiah.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Carlos and Alfonso are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Carlos consumes 2964 calories per day whereas Alfonso consumes 2641 calories per day. Carlos is stronger than Alfonso.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Deacon and Nickolas are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Deacon consumes 2549 calories per day whereas Nickolas consumes 1577 calories per day. Deacon is more weight than Nickolas.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Bradley and Abdullah are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Bradley consumes 2739 calories per day whereas Abdullah consumes 2569 calories per day. Bradley is more weight than Abdullah.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Ruben and Van are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Ruben consumes 2119 calories per day whereas Van consumes 2127 calories per day. Ruben is heavier than Van.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Marco and Maxton are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Marco consumes 2356 calories per day whereas Maxton consumes 1593 calories per day. Marco is bulkier than Maxton.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Jackson and Gustavo are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Jackson consumes 2520 calories per day whereas Gustavo consumes 2615 calories per day. Jackson is more weight than Gustavo.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Jase and Korbin are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Jase consumes 2562 calories per day whereas Korbin consumes 2629 calories per day. Jase is bulkier than Korbin.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Adan and Huxley are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Adan consumes 1993 calories per day whereas Huxley consumes 2099 calories per day. Adan is bulkier than Huxley.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Francisco and Rodney are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Francisco consumes 2462 calories per day whereas Rodney consumes 2005 calories per day. Francisco is more weight than Rodney.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Gavin and Baker are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Gavin consumes 2007 calories per day whereas Baker consumes 1811 calories per day. Gavin is stronger than Baker.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Marco and Cory are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Marco consumes 2100 calories per day whereas Cory consumes 2351 calories per day. Marco is more weight than Cory.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Justin and Yehuda are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Justin consumes 2827 calories per day whereas Yehuda consumes 2848 calories per day. Justin is heavier than Yehuda.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Maverick and Cassius are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Maverick consumes 2487 calories per day whereas Cassius consumes 1756 calories per day. Maverick is stronger than Cassius.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Harrison and Decker are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Harrison consumes 2840 calories per day whereas Decker consumes 2035 calories per day. Harrison is bulkier than Decker.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Tucker and Terry are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Tucker consumes 2309 calories per day whereas Terry consumes 1982 calories per day. Tucker is bulkier than Terry.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Ronald and Saint are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Ronald consumes 2306 calories per day whereas Saint consumes 2194 calories per day. Ronald is heavier than Saint.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Maximiliano and Lennon are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Maximiliano consumes 2460 calories per day whereas Lennon consumes 2642 calories per day. Maximiliano is stronger than Lennon.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Grayson and Izaiah are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Grayson consumes 2915 calories per day whereas Izaiah consumes 1851 calories per day. Grayson is heavier than Izaiah.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Rhett and Braylon are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Rhett consumes 2105 calories per day whereas Braylon consumes 2582 calories per day. Rhett is heavier than Braylon.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Beau and Camilo are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Beau consumes 2956 calories per day whereas Camilo consumes 2382 calories per day. Beau is bulkier than Camilo.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Connor and Yahir are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Connor consumes 2926 calories per day whereas Yahir consumes 2687 calories per day. Connor is heavier than Yahir.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Parker and Zyaire are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Parker consumes 2484 calories per day whereas Zyaire consumes 1690 calories per day. Parker is bulkier than Zyaire.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Juan and Sincere are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Juan consumes 1686 calories per day whereas Sincere consumes 2464 calories per day. Juan is heavier than Sincere.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Carlos and Sam are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Carlos consumes 2252 calories per day whereas Sam consumes 2277 calories per day. Carlos is stronger than Sam.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 129 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2048 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 118,
        "options": [
            51,
            68,
            118,
            42,
            92
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 131 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 128 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 124,
        "options": [
            124,
            16,
            155,
            25,
            220
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 298 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2048 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 287,
        "options": [
            482,
            287,
            363,
            392,
            504
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 331 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 64 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 325,
        "options": [
            325,
            391,
            117,
            355,
            269
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 188 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 16 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 184,
        "options": [
            75,
            184,
            85,
            4,
            29
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 101 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 256 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 93,
        "options": [
            93,
            112,
            44,
            183,
            59
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 31 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 8 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 28,
        "options": [
            20,
            1,
            28,
            31,
            44
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 127 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 126,
        "options": [
            125,
            101,
            63,
            106,
            126
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 59 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 256 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 51,
        "options": [
            51,
            61,
            49,
            28,
            29
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 327 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 512 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 318,
        "options": [
            251,
            318,
            247,
            189,
            105
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 304 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 128 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 297,
        "options": [
            27,
            40,
            36,
            297,
            124
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 74 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 8 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 71,
        "options": [
            30,
            91,
            57,
            71,
            30
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 227 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2048 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 216,
        "options": [
            364,
            202,
            22,
            278,
            216
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 282 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 16 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 278,
        "options": [
            208,
            442,
            298,
            278,
            209
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 242 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 128 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 235,
        "options": [
            64,
            235,
            162,
            62,
            318
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 51 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 64 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 45,
        "options": [
            39,
            12,
            45,
            16,
            69
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 49 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 8 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 46,
        "options": [
            58,
            46,
            62,
            62,
            19
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 192 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 1024 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 182,
        "options": [
            224,
            182,
            23,
            99,
            59
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 19 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 8 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 16,
        "options": [
            23,
            15,
            16,
            12,
            15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 170 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 256 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 162,
        "options": [
            220,
            162,
            304,
            208,
            205
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 199 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 8 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 196,
        "options": [
            86,
            377,
            196,
            327,
            386
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 145 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 144,
        "options": [
            242,
            247,
            15,
            144,
            77
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 234 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 128 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 227,
        "options": [
            208,
            68,
            227,
            429,
            176
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 192 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 256 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 184,
        "options": [
            61,
            135,
            184,
            258,
            329
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 27 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 8 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 24,
        "options": [
            24,
            39,
            5,
            37,
            15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 170 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 8 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 167,
        "options": [
            119,
            213,
            194,
            53,
            167
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 123 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 8 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 120,
        "options": [
            46,
            182,
            55,
            111,
            120
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 139 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 1024 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 129,
        "options": [
            125,
            140,
            160,
            3,
            129
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 180 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2048 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 169,
        "options": [
            141,
            99,
            308,
            122,
            169
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 14 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 32 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 9,
        "options": [
            10,
            9,
            2,
            5,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 152 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 128 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 145,
        "options": [
            238,
            145,
            247,
            185,
            54
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 139 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 32 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 134,
        "options": [
            247,
            171,
            134,
            221,
            84
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 98 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2048 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 87,
        "options": [
            10,
            137,
            52,
            87,
            98
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 329 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 328,
        "options": [
            118,
            283,
            328,
            128,
            141
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 230 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 512 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 221,
        "options": [
            145,
            323,
            259,
            153,
            221
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 54 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 8 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 51,
        "options": [
            5,
            4,
            27,
            51,
            69
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 312 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 4 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 310,
        "options": [
            350,
            507,
            335,
            310,
            242
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 277 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2048 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 266,
        "options": [
            266,
            27,
            321,
            113,
            387
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 349 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 64 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 343,
        "options": [
            323,
            116,
            544,
            343,
            11
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 181 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 16 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 177,
        "options": [
            4,
            210,
            253,
            244,
            177
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 73 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 8 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 70,
        "options": [
            70,
            19,
            40,
            22,
            117
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 63 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 512 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 54,
        "options": [
            49,
            54,
            85,
            2,
            42
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 347 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 1024 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 337,
        "options": [
            38,
            337,
            89,
            186,
            114
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 117 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 128 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 110,
        "options": [
            140,
            180,
            92,
            89,
            110
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 222 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 128 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 215,
        "options": [
            41,
            383,
            274,
            20,
            215
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 298 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 512 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 289,
        "options": [
            206,
            313,
            501,
            289,
            528
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 281 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 32 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 276,
        "options": [
            276,
            376,
            422,
            20,
            164
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 99 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 16 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 95,
        "options": [
            169,
            140,
            95,
            61,
            18
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 237 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 512 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 228,
        "options": [
            228,
            227,
            137,
            339,
            304
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 187 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 256 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 179,
        "options": [
            256,
            49,
            254,
            179,
            71
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 314 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 16 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 310,
        "options": [
            574,
            310,
            86,
            486,
            102
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 253 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 512 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 244,
        "options": [
            383,
            437,
            265,
            34,
            244
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 211 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 1024 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 201,
        "options": [
            68,
            322,
            133,
            106,
            201
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 35 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 32 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 30,
        "options": [
            30,
            29,
            44,
            11,
            60
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 132 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 131,
        "options": [
            33,
            170,
            235,
            216,
            131
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 107 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2048 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 96,
        "options": [
            132,
            96,
            76,
            146,
            39
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 309 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 32 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 304,
        "options": [
            605,
            304,
            540,
            379,
            462
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 341 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2048 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 330,
        "options": [
            330,
            432,
            622,
            91,
            303
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 251 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2048 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 240,
        "options": [
            335,
            65,
            99,
            428,
            240
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 77 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2048 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 66,
        "options": [
            124,
            128,
            66,
            1,
            57
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 342 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 256 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 334,
        "options": [
            579,
            100,
            334,
            346,
            462
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 118 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 128 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 111,
        "options": [
            30,
            190,
            123,
            184,
            111
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 155 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2048 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 144,
        "options": [
            120,
            47,
            64,
            144,
            11
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 47 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 4 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 45,
        "options": [
            81,
            45,
            8,
            11,
            65
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 93 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 1024 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 83,
        "options": [
            20,
            83,
            125,
            48,
            144
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 333 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 256 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 325,
        "options": [
            536,
            474,
            325,
            349,
            126
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 261 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 128 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 254,
        "options": [
            269,
            178,
            254,
            291,
            200
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 202 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 4 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 200,
        "options": [
            380,
            123,
            371,
            2,
            200
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 93 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2048 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 82,
        "options": [
            157,
            130,
            7,
            22,
            82
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 178 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 512 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 169,
        "options": [
            165,
            208,
            131,
            247,
            169
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 102 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 64 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 96,
        "options": [
            84,
            39,
            99,
            131,
            96
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 162 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 128 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 155,
        "options": [
            37,
            178,
            33,
            268,
            155
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 307 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2048 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 296,
        "options": [
            255,
            124,
            447,
            326,
            296
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 92 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 512 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 83,
        "options": [
            61,
            123,
            150,
            83,
            70
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 298 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 297,
        "options": [
            85,
            219,
            297,
            149,
            163
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 314 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 1024 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 304,
        "options": [
            400,
            521,
            416,
            304,
            223
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 105 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 16 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 101,
        "options": [
            101,
            74,
            141,
            201,
            73
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 247 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 16 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 243,
        "options": [
            276,
            139,
            283,
            26,
            243
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 74 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 8 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 71,
        "options": [
            88,
            18,
            15,
            86,
            71
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 309 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 64 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 303,
        "options": [
            178,
            198,
            435,
            303,
            345
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 270 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 256 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 262,
        "options": [
            186,
            504,
            262,
            455,
            372
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 171 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 1024 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 161,
        "options": [
            54,
            251,
            98,
            161,
            299
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 255 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 1024 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 245,
        "options": [
            224,
            298,
            245,
            203,
            16
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 273 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 8 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 270,
        "options": [
            270,
            181,
            370,
            284,
            85
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 302 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 1024 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 292,
        "options": [
            520,
            73,
            292,
            393,
            285
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 277 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 1024 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 267,
        "options": [
            495,
            474,
            427,
            267,
            188
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 206 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 1024 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 196,
        "options": [
            378,
            196,
            190,
            254,
            232
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 212 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 64 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 206,
        "options": [
            277,
            57,
            185,
            167,
            206
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 140 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 4 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 138,
        "options": [
            265,
            138,
            56,
            127,
            89
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 86 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 32 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 81,
        "options": [
            79,
            36,
            18,
            81,
            70
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 88 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 32 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 83,
        "options": [
            65,
            120,
            31,
            75,
            83
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 160 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 159,
        "options": [
            87,
            177,
            159,
            222,
            139
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 290 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 32 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 285,
        "options": [
            537,
            285,
            19,
            541,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 175 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 174,
        "options": [
            174,
            62,
            70,
            104,
            33
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 348 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 512 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 339,
        "options": [
            537,
            193,
            84,
            211,
            339
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 237 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 8 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 234,
        "options": [
            400,
            284,
            420,
            234,
            170
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 132 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 8 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 129,
        "options": [
            94,
            89,
            129,
            228,
            195
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 325 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 1024 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 315,
        "options": [
            225,
            318,
            585,
            315,
            207
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 167 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2048 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 156,
        "options": [
            88,
            156,
            210,
            28,
            98
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 46 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 32 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 41,
        "options": [
            60,
            80,
            41,
            44,
            17
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 12 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2048 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 1,
        "options": [
            1,
            1,
            2,
            1,
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 118 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 32 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 113,
        "options": [
            113,
            92,
            68,
            16,
            16
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 71 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 8 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 68,
        "options": [
            118,
            54,
            5,
            118,
            68
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 119 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 64 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 113,
        "options": [
            113,
            30,
            219,
            26,
            136
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 229 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 128 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 222,
        "options": [
            250,
            133,
            222,
            128,
            387
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 145 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 144,
        "options": [
            144,
            241,
            192,
            281,
            283
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 319 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 128 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 312,
        "options": [
            312,
            532,
            77,
            245,
            199
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 158 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 4 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 156,
        "options": [
            156,
            299,
            246,
            258,
            23
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 207 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 16 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 203,
        "options": [
            127,
            28,
            203,
            171,
            68
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 266 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 4 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 264,
        "options": [
            122,
            240,
            205,
            264,
            198
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 27 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 1024 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 17,
        "options": [
            4,
            9,
            16,
            17,
            26
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 339 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 8 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 336,
        "options": [
            235,
            382,
            336,
            306,
            568
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 280 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 4 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 278,
        "options": [
            98,
            100,
            489,
            178,
            278
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 292 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 256 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 284,
        "options": [
            553,
            84,
            123,
            337,
            284
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 282 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 4 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 280,
        "options": [
            140,
            507,
            280,
            265,
            252
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 237 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 64 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 231,
        "options": [
            450,
            66,
            195,
            231,
            319
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 25 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 4 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 23,
        "options": [
            42,
            46,
            32,
            23,
            30
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 104 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2048 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 93,
        "options": [
            41,
            151,
            93,
            56,
            53
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 243 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 64 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 237,
        "options": [
            153,
            362,
            237,
            345,
            146
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 348 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 16 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 344,
        "options": [
            557,
            37,
            344,
            487,
            673
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 305 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 64 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 299,
        "options": [
            299,
            321,
            575,
            217,
            382
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 12 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 512 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 3,
        "options": [
            6,
            3,
            3,
            6,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 147 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 146,
        "options": [
            241,
            101,
            34,
            146,
            51
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 203 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 64 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 197,
        "options": [
            191,
            326,
            262,
            198,
            197
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 89 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 128 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 82,
        "options": [
            82,
            158,
            4,
            49,
            61
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 173 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 128 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 166,
        "options": [
            212,
            220,
            45,
            180,
            166
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 125 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 64 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 119,
        "options": [
            119,
            105,
            58,
            13,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 172 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 171,
        "options": [
            273,
            286,
            22,
            106,
            171
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 126 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 32 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 121,
        "options": [
            121,
            235,
            211,
            182,
            198
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 114 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 64 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 108,
        "options": [
            102,
            181,
            108,
            141,
            181
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 332 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 4 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 330,
        "options": [
            330,
            185,
            628,
            494,
            115
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 74 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 32 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 69,
        "options": [
            28,
            103,
            69,
            36,
            136
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 350 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 349,
        "options": [
            642,
            289,
            349,
            518,
            96
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 67 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 64 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 61,
        "options": [
            75,
            104,
            77,
            3,
            61
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 321 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 128 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 314,
        "options": [
            314,
            40,
            349,
            290,
            445
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 53 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 16 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 49,
        "options": [
            36,
            77,
            24,
            74,
            49
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 205 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2048 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 194,
        "options": [
            103,
            112,
            258,
            194,
            199
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 69 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 256 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 61,
        "options": [
            35,
            28,
            68,
            116,
            61
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 157 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2048 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 146,
        "options": [
            125,
            146,
            59,
            124,
            14
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 302 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 256 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 294,
        "options": [
            294,
            8,
            584,
            422,
            424
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 333 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 332,
        "options": [
            531,
            632,
            179,
            332,
            319
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 42 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 64 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 36,
        "options": [
            36,
            5,
            35,
            39,
            46
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 68 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 512 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 59,
        "options": [
            59,
            98,
            67,
            118,
            39
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 253 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 252,
        "options": [
            333,
            252,
            16,
            24,
            65
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 218 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 32 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 213,
        "options": [
            19,
            28,
            137,
            213,
            331
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 86 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2048 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 75,
        "options": [
            26,
            93,
            142,
            75,
            75
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 283 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 512 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 274,
        "options": [
            239,
            375,
            335,
            274,
            469
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 190 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2048 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 179,
        "options": [
            156,
            226,
            179,
            178,
            237
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 181 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 1024 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 171,
        "options": [
            331,
            203,
            12,
            170,
            171
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 111 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 110,
        "options": [
            72,
            173,
            7,
            110,
            106
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 120 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 256 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 112,
        "options": [
            2,
            86,
            218,
            13,
            112
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 188 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 64 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 182,
        "options": [
            295,
            305,
            182,
            299,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 322 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 256 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 314,
        "options": [
            314,
            515,
            184,
            362,
            354
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 281 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 64 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 275,
        "options": [
            18,
            350,
            275,
            301,
            201
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 99 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 8 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 96,
        "options": [
            80,
            96,
            160,
            143,
            84
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 152 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2048 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 141,
        "options": [
            93,
            140,
            198,
            71,
            141
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 200 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 256 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 192,
        "options": [
            8,
            235,
            79,
            30,
            192
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 283 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 128 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 276,
        "options": [
            382,
            276,
            381,
            427,
            165
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 333 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 16 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 329,
        "options": [
            329,
            563,
            617,
            616,
            575
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 121 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 32 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 116,
        "options": [
            116,
            136,
            171,
            127,
            181
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 273 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 512 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 264,
        "options": [
            237,
            435,
            115,
            120,
            264
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 194 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 512 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 185,
        "options": [
            185,
            231,
            181,
            28,
            255
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 196 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 4 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 194,
        "options": [
            194,
            185,
            172,
            152,
            229
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 334 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 64 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 328,
        "options": [
            70,
            534,
            620,
            368,
            328
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 164 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 1024 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 154,
        "options": [
            12,
            279,
            100,
            154,
            42
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 232 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 4 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 230,
        "options": [
            454,
            425,
            200,
            230,
            123
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 260 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 512 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 251,
        "options": [
            41,
            237,
            90,
            251,
            92
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 249 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 1024 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 239,
        "options": [
            239,
            264,
            4,
            435,
            349
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 49 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 4 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 47,
        "options": [
            55,
            7,
            54,
            47,
            35
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 172 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2048 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 161,
        "options": [
            311,
            172,
            75,
            161,
            176
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 213 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 128 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 206,
        "options": [
            206,
            208,
            380,
            349,
            227
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 148 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 8 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 145,
        "options": [
            115,
            223,
            3,
            145,
            202
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 300 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2048 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 289,
        "options": [
            281,
            187,
            289,
            568,
            108
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 218 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 32 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 213,
        "options": [
            328,
            213,
            252,
            385,
            204
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 109 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 1024 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 99,
        "options": [
            99,
            84,
            37,
            97,
            150
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 234 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 64 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 228,
        "options": [
            14,
            228,
            81,
            146,
            236
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 337 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 32 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 332,
        "options": [
            332,
            596,
            115,
            396,
            421
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 53 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 4 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 51,
        "options": [
            86,
            51,
            25,
            52,
            99
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 316 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 4 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 314,
        "options": [
            284,
            543,
            405,
            335,
            314
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 74 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 73,
        "options": [
            111,
            87,
            73,
            116,
            52
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 25 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 64 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 19,
        "options": [
            19,
            37,
            25,
            12,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 109 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 256 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 101,
        "options": [
            101,
            160,
            110,
            28,
            20
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 221 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 512 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 212,
        "options": [
            205,
            308,
            212,
            254,
            261
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 65 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 4 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 63,
        "options": [
            101,
            97,
            54,
            10,
            63
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 289 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 1024 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 279,
        "options": [
            279,
            213,
            127,
            264,
            381
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 74 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 16 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 70,
        "options": [
            47,
            70,
            118,
            49,
            62
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 309 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 256 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 301,
        "options": [
            261,
            451,
            511,
            301,
            602
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 322 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 16 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 318,
        "options": [
            433,
            318,
            288,
            623,
            622
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 279 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2048 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 268,
        "options": [
            445,
            536,
            348,
            163,
            268
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 232 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 231,
        "options": [
            150,
            63,
            288,
            231,
            317
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 45 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 1024 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 35,
        "options": [
            50,
            69,
            10,
            35,
            52
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 343 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 8 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 340,
        "options": [
            555,
            501,
            340,
            628,
            492
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 43 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 64 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 37,
        "options": [
            53,
            37,
            51,
            18,
            72
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 204 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 64 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 198,
        "options": [
            281,
            329,
            198,
            333,
            148
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 60 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 64 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 54,
        "options": [
            96,
            70,
            54,
            8,
            15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 237 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 16 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 233,
        "options": [
            194,
            220,
            237,
            233,
            427
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 225 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 64 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 219,
        "options": [
            357,
            61,
            339,
            219,
            264
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 124 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 128 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 117,
        "options": [
            182,
            79,
            234,
            117,
            103
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 75 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 74,
        "options": [
            74,
            76,
            92,
            113,
            111
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 94 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 512 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 85,
        "options": [
            136,
            157,
            85,
            152,
            47
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 256 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 128 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 249,
        "options": [
            88,
            109,
            249,
            10,
            37
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 105 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 1024 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 95,
        "options": [
            42,
            104,
            95,
            134,
            135
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 226 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 32 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 221,
        "options": [
            276,
            318,
            221,
            396,
            204
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 209 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 512 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 200,
        "options": [
            7,
            200,
            268,
            246,
            233
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 222 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 4 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 220,
        "options": [
            103,
            343,
            220,
            293,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 308 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2048 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 297,
        "options": [
            5,
            69,
            465,
            417,
            297
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 236 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2048 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 225,
        "options": [
            383,
            288,
            224,
            298,
            225
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 333 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 8 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 330,
        "options": [
            439,
            478,
            565,
            330,
            107
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 333 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 1024 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 323,
        "options": [
            349,
            160,
            323,
            207,
            396
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 225 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 1024 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 215,
        "options": [
            314,
            307,
            215,
            170,
            299
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 167 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 64 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 161,
        "options": [
            81,
            9,
            161,
            92,
            124
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 90 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 32 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 85,
        "options": [
            44,
            91,
            35,
            84,
            85
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 129 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 256 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 121,
        "options": [
            237,
            240,
            236,
            121,
            130
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 31 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 256 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 23,
        "options": [
            23,
            34,
            11,
            41,
            33
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 148 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 256 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 140,
        "options": [
            140,
            31,
            17,
            68,
            238
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 128 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 128 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 121,
        "options": [
            231,
            44,
            235,
            121,
            184
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 237 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 8 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 234,
        "options": [
            234,
            430,
            274,
            62,
            47
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 19 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 128 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 12,
        "options": [
            9,
            12,
            11,
            3,
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 340 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 4 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 338,
        "options": [
            522,
            44,
            43,
            338,
            125
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 54 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 32 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 49,
        "options": [
            83,
            49,
            95,
            18,
            13
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 41 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 512 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 32,
        "options": [
            27,
            37,
            53,
            32,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 327 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 326,
        "options": [
            517,
            643,
            326,
            448,
            629
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 327 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 32 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 322,
        "options": [
            185,
            139,
            322,
            60,
            505
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 99 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2048 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 88,
        "options": [
            108,
            18,
            88,
            74,
            60
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 40 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 1024 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 30,
        "options": [
            30,
            16,
            40,
            17,
            32
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 327 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 8 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 324,
        "options": [
            623,
            76,
            257,
            324,
            527
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 73 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 32 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 68,
        "options": [
            118,
            116,
            68,
            26,
            104
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 85 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2048 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 74,
        "options": [
            84,
            1,
            74,
            12,
            93
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 125 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 8 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 122,
        "options": [
            168,
            67,
            70,
            122,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 187 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 8 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 184,
        "options": [
            54,
            358,
            192,
            169,
            184
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 162 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 32 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 157,
        "options": [
            219,
            289,
            157,
            50,
            181
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 291 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 8 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 288,
        "options": [
            269,
            433,
            480,
            353,
            288
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 317 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 1024 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 307,
        "options": [
            563,
            553,
            307,
            155,
            165
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 315 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 314,
        "options": [
            544,
            585,
            44,
            314,
            25
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 171 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 4 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 169,
        "options": [
            295,
            130,
            169,
            338,
            208
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 169 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 64 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 163,
        "options": [
            130,
            257,
            235,
            155,
            163
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 346 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 64 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 340,
        "options": [
            340,
            607,
            467,
            420,
            84
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 115 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 32 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 110,
        "options": [
            76,
            110,
            3,
            127,
            80
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 288 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 64 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 282,
        "options": [
            528,
            86,
            423,
            175,
            282
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 50 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 4 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 48,
        "options": [
            19,
            47,
            48,
            6,
            54
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 279 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 4 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 277,
        "options": [
            277,
            206,
            382,
            524,
            162
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 337 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 128 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 330,
        "options": [
            295,
            480,
            62,
            330,
            659
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 182 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 512 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 173,
        "options": [
            173,
            11,
            13,
            236,
            311
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 134 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 8 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 131,
        "options": [
            130,
            172,
            131,
            245,
            118
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 282 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 128 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 275,
        "options": [
            313,
            275,
            307,
            443,
            209
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 21 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 2048 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 10,
        "options": [
            15,
            14,
            17,
            10,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 307 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 1024 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 297,
        "options": [
            400,
            297,
            449,
            38,
            402
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 257 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 64 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 251,
        "options": [
            251,
            74,
            367,
            285,
            371
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 302 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 1024 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 292,
        "options": [
            456,
            440,
            68,
            292,
            134
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "The radius of lotus doubles everyday. It took 76 days to cover the whole pond. How many days would have it taken to cover (1/ 8 )th of the pond?",
        "answer": 73,
        "options": [
            133,
            92,
            102,
            73,
            84
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Kai and Amos are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Kai consumes 1908 calories per day whereas Amos consumes 2185 calories per day. Kai is less weight than Amos.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Carlos and Jamir are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Carlos consumes 2249 calories per day whereas Jamir consumes 1776 calories per day. Carlos is less weight than Jamir.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Reid and Bronson are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Reid consumes 1684 calories per day whereas Bronson consumes 1655 calories per day. Reid is less weight than Bronson.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Emmett and Kaison are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Emmett consumes 2269 calories per day whereas Kaison consumes 2379 calories per day. Emmett is lighter than Kaison.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Dax and Raphael are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Dax consumes 2698 calories per day whereas Raphael consumes 2698 calories per day. Dax is lighter than Raphael.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": "Can't say"
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Francisco and Sylas are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Francisco consumes 2086 calories per day whereas Sylas consumes 2817 calories per day. Francisco is weaker than Sylas.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Jayceon and Joe are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Jayceon consumes 2264 calories per day whereas Joe consumes 2426 calories per day. Jayceon is less weight than Joe.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Kason and Callen are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Kason consumes 2445 calories per day whereas Callen consumes 2530 calories per day. Kason is lighter than Callen.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Muhammad and Payton are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Muhammad consumes 2657 calories per day whereas Payton consumes 2282 calories per day. Muhammad is less weight than Payton.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Dante and Merrick are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Dante consumes 2979 calories per day whereas Merrick consumes 1774 calories per day. Dante is less weight than Merrick.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Richard and Creed are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Richard consumes 1732 calories per day whereas Creed consumes 2436 calories per day. Richard is weaker than Creed.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Winston and Tristen are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Winston consumes 1983 calories per day whereas Tristen consumes 2673 calories per day. Winston is less weight than Tristen.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Spencer and Ryland are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Spencer consumes 2658 calories per day whereas Ryland consumes 2671 calories per day. Spencer is less weight than Ryland.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Amir and Eugene are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Amir consumes 2759 calories per day whereas Eugene consumes 2365 calories per day. Amir is lighter than Eugene.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Jose and Magnus are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Jose consumes 2547 calories per day whereas Magnus consumes 1936 calories per day. Jose is less weight than Magnus.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both George and Maison are of same age. Both do same physical activity. George consumes 2736 calories per day whereas Maison consumes 1949 calories per day. George is lighter than Maison.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Jamison and Layne are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Jamison consumes 2475 calories per day whereas Layne consumes 1938 calories per day. Jamison is lighter than Layne.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Jay and Reese are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Jay consumes 1971 calories per day whereas Reese consumes 1929 calories per day. Jay is lighter than Reese.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Edgar and Lochlan are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Edgar consumes 2984 calories per day whereas Lochlan consumes 2213 calories per day. Edgar is weaker than Lochlan.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both River and Graysen are of same age. Both do same physical activity. River consumes 2353 calories per day whereas Graysen consumes 2660 calories per day. River is less weight than Graysen.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Bruce and Vicente are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Bruce consumes 1974 calories per day whereas Vicente consumes 2975 calories per day. Bruce is less weight than Vicente.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Zion and Yousef are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Zion consumes 2808 calories per day whereas Yousef consumes 2355 calories per day. Zion is less weight than Yousef.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Royce and Brecken are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Royce consumes 1818 calories per day whereas Brecken consumes 1789 calories per day. Royce is less weight than Brecken.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Ivan and Carl are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Ivan consumes 2321 calories per day whereas Carl consumes 2292 calories per day. Ivan is weaker than Carl.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Cash and Tony are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Cash consumes 1833 calories per day whereas Tony consumes 2356 calories per day. Cash is less weight than Tony.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Kash and Justice are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Kash consumes 2870 calories per day whereas Justice consumes 1762 calories per day. Kash is weaker than Justice.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Diego and Watson are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Diego consumes 2872 calories per day whereas Watson consumes 2866 calories per day. Diego is less weight than Watson.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Cole and Terrence are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Cole consumes 2694 calories per day whereas Terrence consumes 2672 calories per day. Cole is weaker than Terrence.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Kaiden and Kalel are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Kaiden consumes 2602 calories per day whereas Kalel consumes 2161 calories per day. Kaiden is weaker than Kalel.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Tanner and Asa are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Tanner consumes 1943 calories per day whereas Asa consumes 2148 calories per day. Tanner is lighter than Asa.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Parker and Quentin are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Parker consumes 2868 calories per day whereas Quentin consumes 1967 calories per day. Parker is less weight than Quentin.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Maximus and Ernest are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Maximus consumes 2103 calories per day whereas Ernest consumes 1575 calories per day. Maximus is weaker than Ernest.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Shawn and Samir are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Shawn consumes 2869 calories per day whereas Samir consumes 2310 calories per day. Shawn is less weight than Samir.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Richard and Dominik are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Richard consumes 1990 calories per day whereas Dominik consumes 2133 calories per day. Richard is lighter than Dominik.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Camden and Melvin are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Camden consumes 1741 calories per day whereas Melvin consumes 1677 calories per day. Camden is weaker than Melvin.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Eduardo and Zeke are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Eduardo consumes 2257 calories per day whereas Zeke consumes 1865 calories per day. Eduardo is less weight than Zeke.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Atlas and Alessandro are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Atlas consumes 2064 calories per day whereas Alessandro consumes 1616 calories per day. Atlas is weaker than Alessandro.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Jay and Colson are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Jay consumes 2475 calories per day whereas Colson consumes 2540 calories per day. Jay is lighter than Colson.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Nathan and Bowie are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Nathan consumes 2319 calories per day whereas Bowie consumes 2094 calories per day. Nathan is lighter than Bowie.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Royce and Ty are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Royce consumes 2415 calories per day whereas Ty consumes 1984 calories per day. Royce is lighter than Ty.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Ethan and Harlan are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Ethan consumes 2964 calories per day whereas Harlan consumes 1528 calories per day. Ethan is lighter than Harlan.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Dante and Tristian are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Dante consumes 2675 calories per day whereas Tristian consumes 1921 calories per day. Dante is less weight than Tristian.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Sterling and Lennon are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Sterling consumes 1788 calories per day whereas Lennon consumes 2805 calories per day. Sterling is lighter than Lennon.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Rocco and Jaziel are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Rocco consumes 1840 calories per day whereas Jaziel consumes 2888 calories per day. Rocco is weaker than Jaziel.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Rhys and Titan are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Rhys consumes 1983 calories per day whereas Titan consumes 2236 calories per day. Rhys is less weight than Titan.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Malcolm and Mathew are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Malcolm consumes 1929 calories per day whereas Mathew consumes 2694 calories per day. Malcolm is weaker than Mathew.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Liam and Lennon are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Liam consumes 1574 calories per day whereas Lennon consumes 2674 calories per day. Liam is lighter than Lennon.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Micah and Reuben are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Micah consumes 2664 calories per day whereas Reuben consumes 2070 calories per day. Micah is weaker than Reuben.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Cameron and Tommy are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Cameron consumes 2463 calories per day whereas Tommy consumes 2761 calories per day. Cameron is weaker than Tommy.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Eden and Genesis are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Eden consumes 2661 calories per day whereas Genesis consumes 2508 calories per day. Eden is less weight than Genesis.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Zayden and Aries are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Zayden consumes 2654 calories per day whereas Aries consumes 2368 calories per day. Zayden is lighter than Aries.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Remy and Gary are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Remy consumes 1751 calories per day whereas Gary consumes 2932 calories per day. Remy is weaker than Gary.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Jayce and Cason are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Jayce consumes 2027 calories per day whereas Cason consumes 2368 calories per day. Jayce is less weight than Cason.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Caden and Bobby are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Caden consumes 1554 calories per day whereas Bobby consumes 2033 calories per day. Caden is weaker than Bobby.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Theodore and Ridge are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Theodore consumes 2938 calories per day whereas Ridge consumes 2970 calories per day. Theodore is lighter than Ridge.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Dakota and Brayan are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Dakota consumes 2248 calories per day whereas Brayan consumes 1668 calories per day. Dakota is less weight than Brayan.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Drew and Colby are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Drew consumes 1828 calories per day whereas Colby consumes 2577 calories per day. Drew is lighter than Colby.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Romeo and Harlem are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Romeo consumes 2987 calories per day whereas Harlem consumes 2680 calories per day. Romeo is weaker than Harlem.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Karter and Dennis are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Karter consumes 2914 calories per day whereas Dennis consumes 1999 calories per day. Karter is less weight than Dennis.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Ismael and Cedric are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Ismael consumes 2605 calories per day whereas Cedric consumes 2723 calories per day. Ismael is less weight than Cedric.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Remy and Davis are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Remy consumes 2802 calories per day whereas Davis consumes 1840 calories per day. Remy is lighter than Davis.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Jared and Archie are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Jared consumes 1552 calories per day whereas Archie consumes 1990 calories per day. Jared is weaker than Archie.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Beckham and Tommy are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Beckham consumes 1627 calories per day whereas Tommy consumes 2952 calories per day. Beckham is weaker than Tommy.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Jeremiah and Quentin are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Jeremiah consumes 2722 calories per day whereas Quentin consumes 2693 calories per day. Jeremiah is less weight than Quentin.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Matteo and Turner are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Matteo consumes 2644 calories per day whereas Turner consumes 1763 calories per day. Matteo is lighter than Turner.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Alex and Emmitt are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Alex consumes 1570 calories per day whereas Emmitt consumes 2880 calories per day. Alex is weaker than Emmitt.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Lennox and Zahir are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Lennox consumes 2549 calories per day whereas Zahir consumes 2585 calories per day. Lennox is less weight than Zahir.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Franklin and Hamza are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Franklin consumes 1977 calories per day whereas Hamza consumes 2068 calories per day. Franklin is weaker than Hamza.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Nathan and Aden are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Nathan consumes 2760 calories per day whereas Aden consumes 2403 calories per day. Nathan is lighter than Aden.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Benson and Davian are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Benson consumes 2089 calories per day whereas Davian consumes 2884 calories per day. Benson is lighter than Davian.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Corbin and Stanley are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Corbin consumes 2224 calories per day whereas Stanley consumes 2667 calories per day. Corbin is less weight than Stanley.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Fabian and Javion are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Fabian consumes 1912 calories per day whereas Javion consumes 1636 calories per day. Fabian is weaker than Javion.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both William and Bronson are of same age. Both do same physical activity. William consumes 2863 calories per day whereas Bronson consumes 1543 calories per day. William is less weight than Bronson.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Zander and Korbin are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Zander consumes 2569 calories per day whereas Korbin consumes 1511 calories per day. Zander is weaker than Korbin.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Paul and Maximo are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Paul consumes 1854 calories per day whereas Maximo consumes 2761 calories per day. Paul is weaker than Maximo.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Rhys and Devon are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Rhys consumes 1858 calories per day whereas Devon consumes 2485 calories per day. Rhys is lighter than Devon.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Ari and Bowie are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Ari consumes 2898 calories per day whereas Bowie consumes 2808 calories per day. Ari is weaker than Bowie.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Brody and Ayaan are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Brody consumes 1818 calories per day whereas Ayaan consumes 1673 calories per day. Brody is less weight than Ayaan.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Hunter and Rene are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Hunter consumes 1654 calories per day whereas Rene consumes 2309 calories per day. Hunter is weaker than Rene.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Orion and Harlem are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Orion consumes 2124 calories per day whereas Harlem consumes 1612 calories per day. Orion is less weight than Harlem.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Jaiden and Orlando are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Jaiden consumes 2780 calories per day whereas Orlando consumes 1641 calories per day. Jaiden is less weight than Orlando.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Xavier and Torin are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Xavier consumes 2850 calories per day whereas Torin consumes 1507 calories per day. Xavier is less weight than Torin.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Enrique and Cullen are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Enrique consumes 2214 calories per day whereas Cullen consumes 1679 calories per day. Enrique is less weight than Cullen.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both James and Sincere are of same age. Both do same physical activity. James consumes 2597 calories per day whereas Sincere consumes 2421 calories per day. James is less weight than Sincere.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Kolton and Louie are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Kolton consumes 2915 calories per day whereas Louie consumes 2660 calories per day. Kolton is less weight than Louie.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Bentley and Kenzo are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Bentley consumes 1534 calories per day whereas Kenzo consumes 2263 calories per day. Bentley is weaker than Kenzo.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Skyler and Eddie are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Skyler consumes 2681 calories per day whereas Eddie consumes 1839 calories per day. Skyler is less weight than Eddie.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Cyrus and Maddux are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Cyrus consumes 2305 calories per day whereas Maddux consumes 2271 calories per day. Cyrus is lighter than Maddux.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Kendrick and Kaysen are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Kendrick consumes 2122 calories per day whereas Kaysen consumes 1531 calories per day. Kendrick is less weight than Kaysen.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Manuel and Leandro are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Manuel consumes 2235 calories per day whereas Leandro consumes 1532 calories per day. Manuel is lighter than Leandro.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Hector and Heath are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Hector consumes 2088 calories per day whereas Heath consumes 2728 calories per day. Hector is weaker than Heath.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Milan and Jadiel are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Milan consumes 1636 calories per day whereas Jadiel consumes 2920 calories per day. Milan is lighter than Jadiel.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Graham and Donald are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Graham consumes 2399 calories per day whereas Donald consumes 1602 calories per day. Graham is less weight than Donald.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Avery and Reginald are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Avery consumes 1559 calories per day whereas Reginald consumes 1835 calories per day. Avery is less weight than Reginald.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Adan and Harlan are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Adan consumes 2583 calories per day whereas Harlan consumes 2190 calories per day. Adan is lighter than Harlan.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Steven and Bobby are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Steven consumes 2468 calories per day whereas Bobby consumes 2157 calories per day. Steven is weaker than Bobby.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Julius and Donald are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Julius consumes 2971 calories per day whereas Donald consumes 1969 calories per day. Julius is weaker than Donald.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Atticus and Kristian are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Atticus consumes 1961 calories per day whereas Kristian consumes 2271 calories per day. Atticus is lighter than Kristian.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Jax and Jasiah are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Jax consumes 2553 calories per day whereas Jasiah consumes 2478 calories per day. Jax is weaker than Jasiah.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Ayden and Eliseo are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Ayden consumes 2620 calories per day whereas Eliseo consumes 2872 calories per day. Ayden is less weight than Eliseo.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Vincent and Marc are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Vincent consumes 1788 calories per day whereas Marc consumes 1754 calories per day. Vincent is weaker than Marc.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Jordan and Juelz are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Jordan consumes 1861 calories per day whereas Juelz consumes 2816 calories per day. Jordan is less weight than Juelz.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Beckham and Kenzo are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Beckham consumes 2437 calories per day whereas Kenzo consumes 1710 calories per day. Beckham is less weight than Kenzo.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Omari and Felipe are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Omari consumes 1978 calories per day whereas Felipe consumes 2605 calories per day. Omari is less weight than Felipe.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Ezekiel and Davis are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Ezekiel consumes 2232 calories per day whereas Davis consumes 1739 calories per day. Ezekiel is lighter than Davis.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Abram and Achilles are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Abram consumes 2119 calories per day whereas Achilles consumes 2716 calories per day. Abram is weaker than Achilles.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Ruben and Blaine are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Ruben consumes 2189 calories per day whereas Blaine consumes 1705 calories per day. Ruben is weaker than Blaine.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Easton and Felipe are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Easton consumes 2644 calories per day whereas Felipe consumes 2977 calories per day. Easton is less weight than Felipe.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Enrique and Marvin are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Enrique consumes 1995 calories per day whereas Marvin consumes 1658 calories per day. Enrique is lighter than Marvin.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Matthew and Keenan are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Matthew consumes 2279 calories per day whereas Keenan consumes 2857 calories per day. Matthew is weaker than Keenan.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Hudson and Douglas are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Hudson consumes 2939 calories per day whereas Douglas consumes 2500 calories per day. Hudson is less weight than Douglas.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Harrison and Jaziel are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Harrison consumes 2973 calories per day whereas Jaziel consumes 2788 calories per day. Harrison is lighter than Jaziel.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Adonis and Forrest are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Adonis consumes 2161 calories per day whereas Forrest consumes 2220 calories per day. Adonis is lighter than Forrest.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Jonah and Sylas are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Jonah consumes 2307 calories per day whereas Sylas consumes 1720 calories per day. Jonah is less weight than Sylas.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Roman and Raylan are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Roman consumes 2840 calories per day whereas Raylan consumes 1639 calories per day. Roman is weaker than Raylan.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Remy and Ira are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Remy consumes 2403 calories per day whereas Ira consumes 1804 calories per day. Remy is weaker than Ira.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Wyatt and Leonard are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Wyatt consumes 2125 calories per day whereas Leonard consumes 1857 calories per day. Wyatt is less weight than Leonard.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Malakai and Casey are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Malakai consumes 2460 calories per day whereas Casey consumes 1623 calories per day. Malakai is less weight than Casey.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Muhammad and Jaime are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Muhammad consumes 1500 calories per day whereas Jaime consumes 1621 calories per day. Muhammad is less weight than Jaime.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Benson and Leroy are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Benson consumes 2260 calories per day whereas Leroy consumes 1505 calories per day. Benson is less weight than Leroy.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Solomon and Tony are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Solomon consumes 2379 calories per day whereas Tony consumes 2790 calories per day. Solomon is lighter than Tony.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both James and Alvaro are of same age. Both do same physical activity. James consumes 2530 calories per day whereas Alvaro consumes 2376 calories per day. James is lighter than Alvaro.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Alexis and Amos are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Alexis consumes 2565 calories per day whereas Amos consumes 2086 calories per day. Alexis is less weight than Amos.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Kairo and Vincenzo are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Kairo consumes 2733 calories per day whereas Vincenzo consumes 2811 calories per day. Kairo is weaker than Vincenzo.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Moses and Dakari are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Moses consumes 1592 calories per day whereas Dakari consumes 2222 calories per day. Moses is weaker than Dakari.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Antonio and Kace are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Antonio consumes 1982 calories per day whereas Kace consumes 1709 calories per day. Antonio is less weight than Kace.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Jacob and Boden are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Jacob consumes 2866 calories per day whereas Boden consumes 2191 calories per day. Jacob is weaker than Boden.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Rowan and Bronson are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Rowan consumes 2755 calories per day whereas Bronson consumes 2050 calories per day. Rowan is weaker than Bronson.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Maximilian and Quentin are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Maximilian consumes 2553 calories per day whereas Quentin consumes 1788 calories per day. Maximilian is weaker than Quentin.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Connor and Wilson are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Connor consumes 1668 calories per day whereas Wilson consumes 2231 calories per day. Connor is lighter than Wilson.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Walter and Danny are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Walter consumes 2664 calories per day whereas Danny consumes 1942 calories per day. Walter is weaker than Danny.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Rylan and Alberto are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Rylan consumes 2206 calories per day whereas Alberto consumes 2932 calories per day. Rylan is less weight than Alberto.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Matteo and London are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Matteo consumes 2281 calories per day whereas London consumes 2672 calories per day. Matteo is weaker than London.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Gabriel and Ramon are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Gabriel consumes 2311 calories per day whereas Ramon consumes 2792 calories per day. Gabriel is weaker than Ramon.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Brady and Graysen are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Brady consumes 1766 calories per day whereas Graysen consumes 2627 calories per day. Brady is less weight than Graysen.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Messiah and Mitchell are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Messiah consumes 2640 calories per day whereas Mitchell consumes 2682 calories per day. Messiah is weaker than Mitchell.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Kashton and Conrad are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Kashton consumes 1738 calories per day whereas Conrad consumes 2597 calories per day. Kashton is lighter than Conrad.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Colt and Danny are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Colt consumes 2815 calories per day whereas Danny consumes 2206 calories per day. Colt is lighter than Danny.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Tobias and Bishop are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Tobias consumes 2835 calories per day whereas Bishop consumes 2595 calories per day. Tobias is weaker than Bishop.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Solomon and Jesiah are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Solomon consumes 2719 calories per day whereas Jesiah consumes 2852 calories per day. Solomon is lighter than Jesiah.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Jasper and Branson are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Jasper consumes 2178 calories per day whereas Branson consumes 1785 calories per day. Jasper is lighter than Branson.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Shane and Fisher are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Shane consumes 1539 calories per day whereas Fisher consumes 1720 calories per day. Shane is less weight than Fisher.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Andy and Finnley are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Andy consumes 2316 calories per day whereas Finnley consumes 1915 calories per day. Andy is less weight than Finnley.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Ronan and Zaire are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Ronan consumes 2468 calories per day whereas Zaire consumes 2883 calories per day. Ronan is lighter than Zaire.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both George and Vivaan are of same age. Both do same physical activity. George consumes 1871 calories per day whereas Vivaan consumes 2546 calories per day. George is lighter than Vivaan.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Jesus and Briar are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Jesus consumes 2313 calories per day whereas Briar consumes 2335 calories per day. Jesus is weaker than Briar.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Chase and Jaxtyn are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Chase consumes 2086 calories per day whereas Jaxtyn consumes 1785 calories per day. Chase is lighter than Jaxtyn.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Erick and Dario are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Erick consumes 1641 calories per day whereas Dario consumes 2723 calories per day. Erick is lighter than Dario.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Ronald and Terry are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Ronald consumes 2362 calories per day whereas Terry consumes 2635 calories per day. Ronald is lighter than Terry.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Kendrick and Kase are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Kendrick consumes 1589 calories per day whereas Kase consumes 2016 calories per day. Kendrick is lighter than Kase.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Jose and Mustafa are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Jose consumes 2628 calories per day whereas Mustafa consumes 2488 calories per day. Jose is weaker than Mustafa.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Harvey and Kody are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Harvey consumes 2885 calories per day whereas Kody consumes 1831 calories per day. Harvey is weaker than Kody.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Jonah and Gatlin are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Jonah consumes 1869 calories per day whereas Gatlin consumes 2564 calories per day. Jonah is lighter than Gatlin.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Gage and Chad are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Gage consumes 1675 calories per day whereas Chad consumes 2333 calories per day. Gage is lighter than Chad.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Parker and Callen are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Parker consumes 2104 calories per day whereas Callen consumes 2690 calories per day. Parker is lighter than Callen.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Michael and Dominik are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Michael consumes 2494 calories per day whereas Dominik consumes 1889 calories per day. Michael is less weight than Dominik.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Alan and Kase are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Alan consumes 1596 calories per day whereas Kase consumes 1962 calories per day. Alan is lighter than Kase.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Maximus and Quincy are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Maximus consumes 1781 calories per day whereas Quincy consumes 2240 calories per day. Maximus is weaker than Quincy.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Kenneth and Boston are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Kenneth consumes 1588 calories per day whereas Boston consumes 1507 calories per day. Kenneth is weaker than Boston.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Kyson and Dayton are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Kyson consumes 2017 calories per day whereas Dayton consumes 2780 calories per day. Kyson is weaker than Dayton.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Cristian and Kabir are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Cristian consumes 2775 calories per day whereas Kabir consumes 2189 calories per day. Cristian is lighter than Kabir.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Jesus and Roy are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Jesus consumes 2462 calories per day whereas Roy consumes 2764 calories per day. Jesus is weaker than Roy.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Uriel and Bo are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Uriel consumes 2552 calories per day whereas Bo consumes 1947 calories per day. Uriel is weaker than Bo.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Gideon and Larry are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Gideon consumes 2676 calories per day whereas Larry consumes 2396 calories per day. Gideon is lighter than Larry.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Lane and Colten are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Lane consumes 1711 calories per day whereas Colten consumes 2672 calories per day. Lane is weaker than Colten.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Frederick and Kristopher are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Frederick consumes 1579 calories per day whereas Kristopher consumes 2040 calories per day. Frederick is less weight than Kristopher.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Brayden and Douglas are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Brayden consumes 2809 calories per day whereas Douglas consumes 1816 calories per day. Brayden is less weight than Douglas.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Beau and Chandler are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Beau consumes 2002 calories per day whereas Chandler consumes 1671 calories per day. Beau is weaker than Chandler.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Kasen and Cannon are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Kasen consumes 2914 calories per day whereas Cannon consumes 1835 calories per day. Kasen is lighter than Cannon.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Dawson and Ahmad are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Dawson consumes 1569 calories per day whereas Ahmad consumes 2927 calories per day. Dawson is weaker than Ahmad.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Zayne and Rudy are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Zayne consumes 2220 calories per day whereas Rudy consumes 1949 calories per day. Zayne is less weight than Rudy.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Rory and Tommy are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Rory consumes 2412 calories per day whereas Tommy consumes 2554 calories per day. Rory is lighter than Tommy.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Bryson and Kendall are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Bryson consumes 2927 calories per day whereas Kendall consumes 1563 calories per day. Bryson is less weight than Kendall.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Reed and Brycen are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Reed consumes 1899 calories per day whereas Brycen consumes 1725 calories per day. Reed is weaker than Brycen.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Ellis and Ramon are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Ellis consumes 2236 calories per day whereas Ramon consumes 2584 calories per day. Ellis is less weight than Ramon.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Harrison and Junior are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Harrison consumes 2021 calories per day whereas Junior consumes 2479 calories per day. Harrison is less weight than Junior.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Maximus and Larry are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Maximus consumes 2562 calories per day whereas Larry consumes 1588 calories per day. Maximus is less weight than Larry.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Fabian and Eliseo are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Fabian consumes 1914 calories per day whereas Eliseo consumes 2883 calories per day. Fabian is weaker than Eliseo.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Kaiden and Duke are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Kaiden consumes 2692 calories per day whereas Duke consumes 2653 calories per day. Kaiden is weaker than Duke.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Logan and Wells are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Logan consumes 2403 calories per day whereas Wells consumes 1541 calories per day. Logan is lighter than Wells.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Knox and Scott are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Knox consumes 1956 calories per day whereas Scott consumes 2949 calories per day. Knox is weaker than Scott.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Jared and Jon are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Jared consumes 2922 calories per day whereas Jon consumes 2725 calories per day. Jared is less weight than Jon.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Erik and Marcel are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Erik consumes 1563 calories per day whereas Marcel consumes 1548 calories per day. Erik is less weight than Marcel.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Kaiden and Amos are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Kaiden consumes 2010 calories per day whereas Amos consumes 1988 calories per day. Kaiden is weaker than Amos.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Luca and Keith are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Luca consumes 1730 calories per day whereas Keith consumes 2004 calories per day. Luca is weaker than Keith.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Marco and Axton are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Marco consumes 2065 calories per day whereas Axton consumes 1553 calories per day. Marco is weaker than Axton.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Mohamed and Flynn are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Mohamed consumes 2578 calories per day whereas Flynn consumes 2784 calories per day. Mohamed is lighter than Flynn.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Zayne and Kristopher are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Zayne consumes 1846 calories per day whereas Kristopher consumes 1596 calories per day. Zayne is weaker than Kristopher.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Trevor and Korbin are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Trevor consumes 2100 calories per day whereas Korbin consumes 2232 calories per day. Trevor is less weight than Korbin.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Ryder and Davion are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Ryder consumes 2275 calories per day whereas Davion consumes 1667 calories per day. Ryder is less weight than Davion.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Jack and Stetson are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Jack consumes 1793 calories per day whereas Stetson consumes 2378 calories per day. Jack is less weight than Stetson.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Jase and Douglas are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Jase consumes 2375 calories per day whereas Douglas consumes 2885 calories per day. Jase is weaker than Douglas.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Vincent and Gibson are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Vincent consumes 2366 calories per day whereas Gibson consumes 2438 calories per day. Vincent is less weight than Gibson.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Ali and Darren are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Ali consumes 1769 calories per day whereas Darren consumes 2805 calories per day. Ali is weaker than Darren.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Maximiliano and Salvatore are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Maximiliano consumes 2027 calories per day whereas Salvatore consumes 2758 calories per day. Maximiliano is less weight than Salvatore.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Reed and Jalen are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Reed consumes 2698 calories per day whereas Jalen consumes 2135 calories per day. Reed is lighter than Jalen.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Luis and Dayton are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Luis consumes 2617 calories per day whereas Dayton consumes 2758 calories per day. Luis is weaker than Dayton.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Thomas and Gary are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Thomas consumes 2708 calories per day whereas Gary consumes 2881 calories per day. Thomas is lighter than Gary.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Lawson and Harry are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Lawson consumes 2419 calories per day whereas Harry consumes 2557 calories per day. Lawson is weaker than Harry.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Harrison and Braden are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Harrison consumes 2263 calories per day whereas Braden consumes 2763 calories per day. Harrison is lighter than Braden.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Joseph and Konnor are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Joseph consumes 1680 calories per day whereas Konnor consumes 2647 calories per day. Joseph is weaker than Konnor.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Elliot and Tristen are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Elliot consumes 1649 calories per day whereas Tristen consumes 1574 calories per day. Elliot is lighter than Tristen.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Michael and Valentino are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Michael consumes 2466 calories per day whereas Valentino consumes 2309 calories per day. Michael is less weight than Valentino.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Ryder and Stefan are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Ryder consumes 1661 calories per day whereas Stefan consumes 2567 calories per day. Ryder is lighter than Stefan.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Ibrahim and Marvin are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Ibrahim consumes 2240 calories per day whereas Marvin consumes 1894 calories per day. Ibrahim is less weight than Marvin.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Alex and Ulises are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Alex consumes 1662 calories per day whereas Ulises consumes 2793 calories per day. Alex is weaker than Ulises.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Marshall and Harper are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Marshall consumes 2949 calories per day whereas Harper consumes 1559 calories per day. Marshall is less weight than Harper.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both George and Gerardo are of same age. Both do same physical activity. George consumes 1554 calories per day whereas Gerardo consumes 2679 calories per day. George is less weight than Gerardo.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Preston and Allan are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Preston consumes 2563 calories per day whereas Allan consumes 2394 calories per day. Preston is weaker than Allan.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Cooper and Marlon are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Cooper consumes 1683 calories per day whereas Marlon consumes 1791 calories per day. Cooper is lighter than Marlon.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Walter and Creed are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Walter consumes 2199 calories per day whereas Creed consumes 2642 calories per day. Walter is weaker than Creed.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Conner and Jedidiah are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Conner consumes 1979 calories per day whereas Jedidiah consumes 2124 calories per day. Conner is weaker than Jedidiah.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Alejandro and Javion are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Alejandro consumes 2780 calories per day whereas Javion consumes 2426 calories per day. Alejandro is less weight than Javion.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Kade and Rayden are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Kade consumes 2484 calories per day whereas Rayden consumes 2314 calories per day. Kade is lighter than Rayden.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Bryan and Darren are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Bryan consumes 1889 calories per day whereas Darren consumes 1552 calories per day. Bryan is weaker than Darren.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Richard and Duke are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Richard consumes 2584 calories per day whereas Duke consumes 2462 calories per day. Richard is less weight than Duke.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Ari and Jaxtyn are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Ari consumes 2494 calories per day whereas Jaxtyn consumes 2306 calories per day. Ari is lighter than Jaxtyn.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Nicolas and Jad are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Nicolas consumes 2415 calories per day whereas Jad consumes 2349 calories per day. Nicolas is less weight than Jad.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Sean and Leandro are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Sean consumes 2424 calories per day whereas Leandro consumes 2724 calories per day. Sean is lighter than Leandro.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Waylon and Rodney are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Waylon consumes 1764 calories per day whereas Rodney consumes 1571 calories per day. Waylon is less weight than Rodney.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Esteban and Santana are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Esteban consumes 2615 calories per day whereas Santana consumes 2031 calories per day. Esteban is less weight than Santana.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Kash and Draven are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Kash consumes 2789 calories per day whereas Draven consumes 2301 calories per day. Kash is lighter than Draven.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Sawyer and Jad are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Sawyer consumes 2416 calories per day whereas Jad consumes 2222 calories per day. Sawyer is less weight than Jad.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Israel and Edison are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Israel consumes 2309 calories per day whereas Edison consumes 2727 calories per day. Israel is lighter than Edison.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Beckham and Roland are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Beckham consumes 2514 calories per day whereas Roland consumes 1656 calories per day. Beckham is less weight than Roland.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Graham and Koda are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Graham consumes 2486 calories per day whereas Koda consumes 2391 calories per day. Graham is lighter than Koda.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Vincent and Ariel are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Vincent consumes 2395 calories per day whereas Ariel consumes 1986 calories per day. Vincent is less weight than Ariel.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Raiden and Dane are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Raiden consumes 1860 calories per day whereas Dane consumes 1516 calories per day. Raiden is weaker than Dane.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Pedro and Mordechai are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Pedro consumes 2048 calories per day whereas Mordechai consumes 2321 calories per day. Pedro is weaker than Mordechai.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Bradley and Xzavier are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Bradley consumes 1962 calories per day whereas Xzavier consumes 2799 calories per day. Bradley is lighter than Xzavier.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Sage and Lee are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Sage consumes 2961 calories per day whereas Lee consumes 2181 calories per day. Sage is weaker than Lee.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Gunnar and Gerardo are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Gunnar consumes 2820 calories per day whereas Gerardo consumes 2702 calories per day. Gunnar is weaker than Gerardo.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Gavin and Khalid are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Gavin consumes 2417 calories per day whereas Khalid consumes 2679 calories per day. Gavin is lighter than Khalid.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Antonio and Aron are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Antonio consumes 2016 calories per day whereas Aron consumes 1635 calories per day. Antonio is lighter than Aron.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Eric and Emmitt are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Eric consumes 2503 calories per day whereas Emmitt consumes 2466 calories per day. Eric is less weight than Emmitt.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Malakai and Brendan are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Malakai consumes 1589 calories per day whereas Brendan consumes 2660 calories per day. Malakai is weaker than Brendan.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Brian and Kristian are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Brian consumes 2382 calories per day whereas Kristian consumes 1517 calories per day. Brian is weaker than Kristian.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Karson and Onyx are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Karson consumes 2852 calories per day whereas Onyx consumes 2170 calories per day. Karson is less weight than Onyx.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Daxton and Benedict are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Daxton consumes 2154 calories per day whereas Benedict consumes 2545 calories per day. Daxton is weaker than Benedict.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Johnathan and Justus are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Johnathan consumes 2792 calories per day whereas Justus consumes 1533 calories per day. Johnathan is lighter than Justus.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Jayden and Clay are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Jayden consumes 2692 calories per day whereas Clay consumes 1958 calories per day. Jayden is weaker than Clay.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Weston and Khari are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Weston consumes 1529 calories per day whereas Khari consumes 1605 calories per day. Weston is weaker than Khari.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Isaiah and Jimmy are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Isaiah consumes 2362 calories per day whereas Jimmy consumes 1758 calories per day. Isaiah is less weight than Jimmy.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Colton and Benedict are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Colton consumes 2826 calories per day whereas Benedict consumes 1875 calories per day. Colton is weaker than Benedict.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Dalton and Colby are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Dalton consumes 2705 calories per day whereas Colby consumes 1947 calories per day. Dalton is weaker than Colby.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Remington and Houston are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Remington consumes 1947 calories per day whereas Houston consumes 2934 calories per day. Remington is weaker than Houston.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "Can't say",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Jeremy and Jaxxon are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Jeremy consumes 2312 calories per day whereas Jaxxon consumes 1891 calories per day. Jeremy is less weight than Jaxxon.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Matias and Enoch are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Matias consumes 1631 calories per day whereas Enoch consumes 2167 calories per day. Matias is less weight than Enoch.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "Can't say",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Kaiden and Kareem are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Kaiden consumes 1677 calories per day whereas Kareem consumes 2007 calories per day. Kaiden is weaker than Kareem.",
        "options": [
            "False",
            "True",
            "Can't say"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "Both Ronan and Rayden are of same age. Both do same physical activity. Ronan consumes 2148 calories per day whereas Rayden consumes 2998 calories per day. Ronan is lighter than Rayden.",
        "options": [
            "Can't say",
            "False",
            "True"
        ],
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 498 meter pole. It climbs 14 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 25 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            77,
            22,
            45,
            "Not possible",
            14
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 394 meter pole. It climbs 19 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 24 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            78,
            "Not possible",
            88,
            58,
            57
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 342 meter pole. It climbs 18 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 43 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            25,
            51,
            46,
            "Not possible",
            20,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 396 meter pole. It climbs 36 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 33 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "241",
        "options": [
            29,
            "Not possible",
            42,
            59,
            40,
            "241"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 438 meter pole. It climbs 24 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 48 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            81,
            72,
            64,
            88,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 474 meter pole. It climbs 36 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 6 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "31",
        "options": [
            "31",
            41,
            69,
            "Not possible",
            78,
            65
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 127 meter pole. It climbs 37 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 25 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "17",
        "options": [
            59,
            33,
            "17",
            74,
            8,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 114 meter pole. It climbs 25 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 13 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "17",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            83,
            99,
            17,
            "17",
            92
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 160 meter pole. It climbs 35 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 49 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            49,
            "Not possible",
            2,
            2,
            "Not possible",
            11
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 322 meter pole. It climbs 4 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 17 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            72,
            28,
            31,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            53
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 124 meter pole. It climbs 46 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 45 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "157",
        "options": [
            29,
            "Not possible",
            58,
            "157",
            94,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 416 meter pole. It climbs 32 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 14 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "45",
        "options": [
            18,
            50,
            2,
            "45",
            96,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 440 meter pole. It climbs 39 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 21 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "47",
        "options": [
            87,
            80,
            "47",
            43,
            81,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 190 meter pole. It climbs 29 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 12 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "21",
        "options": [
            17,
            "Not possible",
            60,
            41,
            57,
            "21"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 381 meter pole. It climbs 7 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 9 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            67,
            "Not possible",
            8,
            "Not possible",
            85,
            84
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 394 meter pole. It climbs 1 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 23 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            54,
            96,
            7,
            "Not possible",
            15,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 170 meter pole. It climbs 31 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 3 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "11",
        "options": [
            21,
            28,
            "11",
            "Not possible",
            93,
            92
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 470 meter pole. It climbs 20 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 31 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            20,
            "Not possible",
            62,
            53,
            81
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 437 meter pole. It climbs 6 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 33 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            29,
            73,
            "Not possible",
            45,
            93
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 140 meter pole. It climbs 3 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 25 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            11,
            "Not possible",
            84,
            39,
            "Not possible",
            23
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 288 meter pole. It climbs 20 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 9 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "51",
        "options": [
            93,
            "51",
            "Not possible",
            80,
            62,
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 304 meter pole. It climbs 7 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 48 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            93,
            "Not possible",
            84,
            "Not possible",
            64,
            43
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 234 meter pole. It climbs 42 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 50 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            31,
            10,
            62,
            59
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 392 meter pole. It climbs 2 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 37 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            7,
            "Not possible",
            49,
            98,
            62,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 107 meter pole. It climbs 22 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 36 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            31,
            26,
            13,
            "Not possible",
            78
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 139 meter pole. It climbs 15 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 17 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            51,
            73,
            2,
            1,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 102 meter pole. It climbs 29 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 18 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "15",
        "options": [
            67,
            "Not possible",
            35,
            47,
            9,
            "15"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 429 meter pole. It climbs 4 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 39 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            12,
            34,
            60,
            "Not possible",
            27
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 319 meter pole. It climbs 16 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 7 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "69",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            40,
            50,
            "69",
            61,
            65
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 236 meter pole. It climbs 31 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 31 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            84,
            10,
            86,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            52
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 489 meter pole. It climbs 16 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 27 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            58,
            "Not possible",
            13,
            9,
            100,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 126 meter pole. It climbs 23 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 20 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "71",
        "options": [
            8,
            "71",
            22,
            "Not possible",
            99,
            75
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 435 meter pole. It climbs 35 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 41 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            1,
            57,
            37,
            "Not possible",
            19,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 465 meter pole. It climbs 48 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 33 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "57",
        "options": [
            67,
            33,
            "57",
            77,
            38,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 189 meter pole. It climbs 9 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 25 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            69,
            "Not possible",
            13,
            34,
            93
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 271 meter pole. It climbs 32 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 39 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            1,
            "Not possible",
            43,
            3,
            73,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 438 meter pole. It climbs 40 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 49 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            60,
            "Not possible",
            14,
            52,
            59,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 377 meter pole. It climbs 2 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 10 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            78,
            100,
            "Not possible",
            4,
            "Not possible",
            63
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 472 meter pole. It climbs 1 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 22 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            64,
            "Not possible",
            45,
            73,
            72,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 141 meter pole. It climbs 50 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 30 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "11",
        "options": [
            34,
            95,
            16,
            "Not possible",
            "11",
            33
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 360 meter pole. It climbs 50 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 29 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "31",
        "options": [
            68,
            "Not possible",
            "31",
            52,
            4,
            82
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 165 meter pole. It climbs 27 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 40 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            1,
            58,
            "Not possible",
            6,
            70,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 244 meter pole. It climbs 15 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 33 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            3,
            "Not possible",
            15,
            4,
            "Not possible",
            27
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 108 meter pole. It climbs 33 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 14 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "9",
        "options": [
            9,
            51,
            "Not possible",
            "9",
            36,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 162 meter pole. It climbs 25 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 2 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "13",
        "options": [
            18,
            30,
            21,
            25,
            "Not possible",
            "13"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 237 meter pole. It climbs 12 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 13 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            3,
            "Not possible",
            35,
            17,
            "Not possible",
            97
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 175 meter pole. It climbs 28 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 40 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            63,
            70,
            "Not possible",
            5,
            91
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 391 meter pole. It climbs 38 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 37 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "707",
        "options": [
            70,
            67,
            6,
            "707",
            "Not possible",
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 474 meter pole. It climbs 41 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 33 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "111",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            2,
            38,
            71,
            "111",
            32
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 417 meter pole. It climbs 4 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 46 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            100,
            6,
            13,
            3,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 497 meter pole. It climbs 42 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 23 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "49",
        "options": [
            39,
            2,
            "49",
            12,
            99,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 158 meter pole. It climbs 22 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 48 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            63,
            "Not possible",
            49,
            18,
            "Not possible",
            7
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 256 meter pole. It climbs 7 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 22 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            90,
            79,
            92,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            89
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 176 meter pole. It climbs 16 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 49 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            23,
            68,
            25,
            66
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 254 meter pole. It climbs 16 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 9 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "69",
        "options": [
            55,
            "Not possible",
            23,
            "69",
            79,
            68
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 379 meter pole. It climbs 23 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 28 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            11,
            100,
            42,
            29,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 103 meter pole. It climbs 27 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 35 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            78,
            "Not possible",
            73,
            46,
            "Not possible",
            29
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 116 meter pole. It climbs 23 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 2 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "11",
        "options": [
            82,
            "11",
            44,
            "Not possible",
            92,
            48
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 334 meter pole. It climbs 37 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 13 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "27",
        "options": [
            97,
            "27",
            61,
            "Not possible",
            12,
            38
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 480 meter pole. It climbs 26 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 23 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "305",
        "options": [
            "305",
            22,
            93,
            "Not possible",
            54,
            70
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 361 meter pole. It climbs 28 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 43 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            67,
            86,
            18,
            55
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 288 meter pole. It climbs 29 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 47 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            14,
            21,
            87,
            70,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 349 meter pole. It climbs 20 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 43 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            92,
            "Not possible",
            26,
            65,
            47,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 195 meter pole. It climbs 3 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 16 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            29,
            6,
            18,
            "Not possible",
            66
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 324 meter pole. It climbs 18 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 26 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            56,
            51,
            25,
            "Not possible",
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 449 meter pole. It climbs 15 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 3 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "75",
        "options": [
            "75",
            "Not possible",
            88,
            59,
            77,
            88
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 156 meter pole. It climbs 12 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 9 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "97",
        "options": [
            2,
            "Not possible",
            44,
            51,
            31,
            "97"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 419 meter pole. It climbs 27 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 15 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "67",
        "options": [
            "67",
            81,
            22,
            54,
            "Not possible",
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 307 meter pole. It climbs 25 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 38 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            98,
            "Not possible",
            12,
            22,
            85,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 416 meter pole. It climbs 36 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 18 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "45",
        "options": [
            74,
            57,
            69,
            57,
            "Not possible",
            "45"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 415 meter pole. It climbs 8 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 5 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "273",
        "options": [
            70,
            "Not possible",
            "273",
            56,
            8,
            44
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 113 meter pole. It climbs 34 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 20 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "13",
        "options": [
            58,
            3,
            "Not possible",
            97,
            "13",
            25
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 217 meter pole. It climbs 2 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 3 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            60,
            37,
            36,
            "Not possible",
            54,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 112 meter pole. It climbs 14 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 30 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            4,
            5,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            28,
            74
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 405 meter pole. It climbs 21 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 14 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "111",
        "options": [
            26,
            16,
            "Not possible",
            "111",
            77,
            99
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 157 meter pole. It climbs 37 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 14 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "13",
        "options": [
            14,
            74,
            76,
            98,
            "Not possible",
            "13"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 144 meter pole. It climbs 36 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 13 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "11",
        "options": [
            32,
            46,
            "11",
            "Not possible",
            38,
            67
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 353 meter pole. It climbs 35 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 40 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            89,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            7,
            1,
            75
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 486 meter pole. It climbs 50 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 46 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "219",
        "options": [
            7,
            "219",
            4,
            18,
            "Not possible",
            98
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 298 meter pole. It climbs 22 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 21 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "553",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            27,
            "553",
            79,
            95,
            97
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 260 meter pole. It climbs 2 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 44 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            52,
            67,
            29,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            42
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 391 meter pole. It climbs 41 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 5 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "21",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            41,
            "21",
            31,
            55,
            53
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 358 meter pole. It climbs 1 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 40 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            92,
            39,
            33,
            "Not possible",
            29,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 286 meter pole. It climbs 26 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 41 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            44,
            "Not possible",
            28,
            53,
            "Not possible",
            54
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 434 meter pole. It climbs 43 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 32 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "73",
        "options": [
            37,
            40,
            "Not possible",
            71,
            "73",
            53
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 392 meter pole. It climbs 22 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 2 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "39",
        "options": [
            "39",
            97,
            86,
            "Not possible",
            65,
            40
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 191 meter pole. It climbs 4 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 3 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "375",
        "options": [
            77,
            57,
            "Not possible",
            50,
            18,
            "375"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 141 meter pole. It climbs 43 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 8 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "7",
        "options": [
            10,
            "Not possible",
            "7",
            25,
            29,
            75
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 381 meter pole. It climbs 28 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 15 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "57",
        "options": [
            98,
            30,
            82,
            "Not possible",
            "57",
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 482 meter pole. It climbs 7 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 31 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            92,
            "Not possible",
            62,
            69,
            15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 397 meter pole. It climbs 38 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 22 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "47",
        "options": [
            32,
            "Not possible",
            58,
            "47",
            85,
            35
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 299 meter pole. It climbs 37 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 5 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "19",
        "options": [
            54,
            "Not possible",
            2,
            36,
            "19",
            23
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 362 meter pole. It climbs 48 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 33 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "43",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            47,
            "43",
            8,
            53,
            43
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 236 meter pole. It climbs 33 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 9 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "19",
        "options": [
            "19",
            46,
            21,
            "Not possible",
            8,
            56
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 256 meter pole. It climbs 33 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 25 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "57",
        "options": [
            "57",
            9,
            80,
            "Not possible",
            2,
            71
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 436 meter pole. It climbs 45 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 23 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "37",
        "options": [
            "37",
            53,
            73,
            "Not possible",
            19,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 295 meter pole. It climbs 30 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 24 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "91",
        "options": [
            63,
            18,
            "Not possible",
            "91",
            8,
            37
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 171 meter pole. It climbs 1 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 43 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            50,
            76,
            60,
            56
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 151 meter pole. It climbs 12 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 28 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            58,
            27,
            24,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            38
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 446 meter pole. It climbs 28 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 8 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "43",
        "options": [
            52,
            77,
            45,
            8,
            "43",
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 280 meter pole. It climbs 1 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 8 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            63,
            53,
            "Not possible",
            49,
            15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 157 meter pole. It climbs 20 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 36 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            48,
            99,
            "Not possible",
            76,
            81
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 416 meter pole. It climbs 12 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 34 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            49,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            8,
            22,
            43
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 402 meter pole. It climbs 4 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 35 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            68,
            83,
            72,
            "Not possible",
            57,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 407 meter pole. It climbs 32 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 39 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            57,
            "Not possible",
            6,
            10,
            38,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 452 meter pole. It climbs 31 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 19 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "73",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            4,
            92,
            80,
            100,
            "73"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 158 meter pole. It climbs 35 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 13 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "13",
        "options": [
            "13",
            90,
            "Not possible",
            86,
            33,
            29
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 459 meter pole. It climbs 20 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 35 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            77,
            37,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            41,
            64
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 149 meter pole. It climbs 41 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 16 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "11",
        "options": [
            97,
            22,
            2,
            48,
            "Not possible",
            "11"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 187 meter pole. It climbs 8 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 22 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            59,
            54,
            9,
            68,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 282 meter pole. It climbs 32 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 5 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "21",
        "options": [
            "21",
            "Not possible",
            26,
            28,
            11,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 178 meter pole. It climbs 22 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 19 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "105",
        "options": [
            4,
            "Not possible",
            54,
            "105",
            83,
            51
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 315 meter pole. It climbs 6 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 47 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            75,
            65,
            7,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            88
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 356 meter pole. It climbs 43 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 29 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "47",
        "options": [
            8,
            25,
            "47",
            33,
            71,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 422 meter pole. It climbs 39 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 19 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "41",
        "options": [
            61,
            8,
            8,
            "41",
            55,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 208 meter pole. It climbs 44 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 39 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "67",
        "options": [
            59,
            68,
            "67",
            71,
            88,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 138 meter pole. It climbs 49 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 5 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "7",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            25,
            26,
            46,
            "7",
            18
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 289 meter pole. It climbs 22 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 41 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            32,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            89,
            76,
            12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 106 meter pole. It climbs 24 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 23 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "165",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            57,
            5,
            "165",
            55,
            80
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 401 meter pole. It climbs 11 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 12 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            73,
            31,
            61,
            31,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 383 meter pole. It climbs 32 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 34 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            24,
            80,
            27,
            "Not possible",
            85,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 488 meter pole. It climbs 8 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 25 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            3,
            "Not possible",
            95,
            24,
            "Not possible",
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 201 meter pole. It climbs 31 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 1 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "13",
        "options": [
            86,
            "Not possible",
            "13",
            73,
            56,
            32
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 376 meter pole. It climbs 31 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 27 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "175",
        "options": [
            47,
            21,
            "175",
            59,
            "Not possible",
            88
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 354 meter pole. It climbs 32 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 24 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "83",
        "options": [
            "83",
            52,
            79,
            "Not possible",
            8,
            15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 251 meter pole. It climbs 29 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 6 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "21",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            "21",
            14,
            20,
            52,
            41
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 229 meter pole. It climbs 12 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 16 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            52,
            28,
            34,
            2,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 406 meter pole. It climbs 45 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 40 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "147",
        "options": [
            "147",
            41,
            56,
            "Not possible",
            25,
            11
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 250 meter pole. It climbs 49 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 49 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            86,
            "Not possible",
            41,
            31,
            27
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 409 meter pole. It climbs 17 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 50 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            19,
            11,
            79,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            34
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 208 meter pole. It climbs 29 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 10 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "21",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            "21",
            99,
            35,
            33,
            91
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 331 meter pole. It climbs 10 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 10 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            5,
            "Not possible",
            26,
            43,
            100,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 197 meter pole. It climbs 15 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 38 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            5,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            86,
            47,
            59
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 382 meter pole. It climbs 46 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 26 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "35",
        "options": [
            18,
            "35",
            39,
            56,
            14,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 370 meter pole. It climbs 44 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 23 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "33",
        "options": [
            29,
            72,
            "Not possible",
            93,
            "33",
            15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 357 meter pole. It climbs 45 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 15 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "23",
        "options": [
            43,
            "Not possible",
            "23",
            45,
            97,
            78
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 273 meter pole. It climbs 48 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 39 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "51",
        "options": [
            16,
            60,
            46,
            "Not possible",
            "51",
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 118 meter pole. It climbs 27 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 22 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "39",
        "options": [
            "39",
            "Not possible",
            89,
            47,
            15,
            46
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 358 meter pole. It climbs 8 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 45 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            33,
            "Not possible",
            10,
            34,
            46
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 454 meter pole. It climbs 29 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 44 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            94,
            65,
            "Not possible",
            79,
            39
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 306 meter pole. It climbs 50 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 7 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "13",
        "options": [
            70,
            65,
            63,
            "Not possible",
            66,
            "13"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 348 meter pole. It climbs 15 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 48 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            85,
            "Not possible",
            67,
            "Not possible",
            51,
            80
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 351 meter pole. It climbs 18 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 14 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "169",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            93,
            49,
            "169",
            1,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 353 meter pole. It climbs 24 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 45 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            52,
            "Not possible",
            35,
            52,
            54
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 382 meter pole. It climbs 18 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 15 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "245",
        "options": [
            69,
            "245",
            32,
            "Not possible",
            4,
            93
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 432 meter pole. It climbs 7 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 27 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            90,
            73,
            99,
            3,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 371 meter pole. It climbs 11 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 18 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            28,
            29,
            42,
            "Not possible",
            77
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 443 meter pole. It climbs 24 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 45 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            60,
            51,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            15,
            12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 191 meter pole. It climbs 45 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 11 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "11",
        "options": [
            33,
            52,
            51,
            84,
            "11",
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 480 meter pole. It climbs 31 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 6 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "37",
        "options": [
            63,
            94,
            "Not possible",
            19,
            65,
            "37"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 130 meter pole. It climbs 9 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 24 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            60,
            "Not possible",
            61,
            24,
            99
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 279 meter pole. It climbs 34 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 11 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "23",
        "options": [
            90,
            15,
            "23",
            22,
            15,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 338 meter pole. It climbs 24 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 23 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "629",
        "options": [
            78,
            "629",
            19,
            40,
            4,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 398 meter pole. It climbs 12 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 44 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            60,
            92,
            51,
            20,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 308 meter pole. It climbs 50 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 40 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "53",
        "options": [
            "53",
            "Not possible",
            1,
            22,
            16,
            66
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 323 meter pole. It climbs 17 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 20 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            27,
            37,
            "Not possible",
            4,
            54
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 170 meter pole. It climbs 19 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 26 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            3,
            24,
            "Not possible",
            56,
            67,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 244 meter pole. It climbs 24 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 38 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            59,
            34,
            9,
            51,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 488 meter pole. It climbs 50 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 24 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "35",
        "options": [
            "35",
            30,
            "Not possible",
            52,
            11,
            99
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 257 meter pole. It climbs 8 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 8 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            7,
            100,
            "Not possible",
            70,
            "Not possible",
            87
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 454 meter pole. It climbs 40 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 5 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "25",
        "options": [
            94,
            "25",
            30,
            56,
            95,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 439 meter pole. It climbs 33 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 36 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            79,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            86,
            99,
            33
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 480 meter pole. It climbs 24 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 11 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "73",
        "options": [
            79,
            "73",
            "Not possible",
            8,
            69,
            18
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 428 meter pole. It climbs 30 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 24 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "135",
        "options": [
            59,
            32,
            28,
            "135",
            31,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 256 meter pole. It climbs 1 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 19 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            95,
            79,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            17,
            33
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 456 meter pole. It climbs 14 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 36 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            50,
            "Not possible",
            74,
            52,
            32
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 177 meter pole. It climbs 18 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 7 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "31",
        "options": [
            79,
            14,
            47,
            "31",
            "Not possible",
            49
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 310 meter pole. It climbs 2 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 47 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            24,
            90,
            64,
            78,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 449 meter pole. It climbs 30 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 33 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            81,
            54,
            82,
            90,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 445 meter pole. It climbs 46 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 22 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "35",
        "options": [
            98,
            "Not possible",
            "35",
            14,
            70,
            25
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 176 meter pole. It climbs 36 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 30 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "49",
        "options": [
            31,
            "49",
            6,
            "Not possible",
            45,
            87
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 127 meter pole. It climbs 31 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 43 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            55,
            43,
            25,
            27
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 485 meter pole. It climbs 41 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 21 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "47",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            6,
            70,
            "47",
            97,
            90
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 256 meter pole. It climbs 8 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 8 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            15,
            11,
            46,
            92
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 365 meter pole. It climbs 8 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 18 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            39,
            "Not possible",
            66,
            72,
            95,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 428 meter pole. It climbs 38 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 49 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            77,
            38,
            "Not possible",
            93,
            25,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 111 meter pole. It climbs 22 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 27 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            16,
            "Not possible",
            90,
            57,
            "Not possible",
            31
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 158 meter pole. It climbs 37 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 35 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "123",
        "options": [
            22,
            76,
            63,
            "Not possible",
            14,
            "123"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 276 meter pole. It climbs 34 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 30 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "123",
        "options": [
            23,
            "Not possible",
            23,
            81,
            "123",
            20
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 332 meter pole. It climbs 9 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 2 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "95",
        "options": [
            "95",
            91,
            25,
            "Not possible",
            16,
            97
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 112 meter pole. It climbs 5 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 13 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            39,
            6,
            94,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            41
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 399 meter pole. It climbs 39 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 48 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            84,
            60,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            10,
            16
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 125 meter pole. It climbs 34 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 3 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "7",
        "options": [
            "7",
            37,
            27,
            88,
            "Not possible",
            53
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 437 meter pole. It climbs 35 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 34 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "805",
        "options": [
            88,
            1,
            "805",
            37,
            100,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 274 meter pole. It climbs 9 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 36 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            40,
            13,
            66,
            "Not possible",
            54,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 196 meter pole. It climbs 8 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 37 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            9,
            72,
            25,
            "Not possible",
            65,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 103 meter pole. It climbs 27 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 49 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            98,
            73,
            27,
            83,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 201 meter pole. It climbs 18 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 39 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            16,
            29,
            49,
            90,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 137 meter pole. It climbs 1 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 16 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            24,
            49,
            "Not possible",
            33,
            55
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 214 meter pole. It climbs 25 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 24 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "379",
        "options": [
            81,
            13,
            95,
            39,
            "379",
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 404 meter pole. It climbs 7 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 46 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            5,
            76,
            82,
            "Not possible",
            90,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 485 meter pole. It climbs 16 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 8 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "119",
        "options": [
            92,
            9,
            44,
            "Not possible",
            46,
            "119"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 103 meter pole. It climbs 5 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 8 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            68,
            36,
            "Not possible",
            46,
            22
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 214 meter pole. It climbs 7 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 27 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            26,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            3,
            33,
            50
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 249 meter pole. It climbs 38 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 10 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "17",
        "options": [
            15,
            4,
            "Not possible",
            71,
            "17",
            25
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 404 meter pole. It climbs 1 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 35 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            4,
            65,
            65,
            92
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 436 meter pole. It climbs 26 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 15 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "77",
        "options": [
            2,
            89,
            "Not possible",
            90,
            "77",
            27
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 204 meter pole. It climbs 3 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 6 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            78,
            91,
            30,
            "Not possible",
            53
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 463 meter pole. It climbs 2 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 46 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            13,
            46,
            15,
            "Not possible",
            15,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 339 meter pole. It climbs 40 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 3 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "19",
        "options": [
            7,
            73,
            "19",
            16,
            "Not possible",
            48
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 188 meter pole. It climbs 29 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 26 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "107",
        "options": [
            "107",
            82,
            "Not possible",
            21,
            5,
            15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 168 meter pole. It climbs 1 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 40 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            92,
            67,
            34,
            26
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 158 meter pole. It climbs 46 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 33 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "19",
        "options": [
            15,
            "19",
            92,
            81,
            78,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 446 meter pole. It climbs 9 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 7 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "439",
        "options": [
            87,
            "439",
            "Not possible",
            3,
            19,
            57
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 412 meter pole. It climbs 50 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 16 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "23",
        "options": [
            100,
            "23",
            50,
            85,
            62,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 398 meter pole. It climbs 4 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 43 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            19,
            "Not possible",
            94,
            73,
            83
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 267 meter pole. It climbs 11 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 17 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            91,
            "Not possible",
            66,
            8,
            "Not possible",
            33
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 258 meter pole. It climbs 8 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 14 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            69,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            30,
            95,
            77
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 416 meter pole. It climbs 28 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 36 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            72,
            55,
            20,
            "Not possible",
            2,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 176 meter pole. It climbs 36 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 7 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "11",
        "options": [
            13,
            96,
            34,
            85,
            "Not possible",
            "11"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 330 meter pole. It climbs 10 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 30 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            36,
            15,
            "Not possible",
            46,
            100
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 247 meter pole. It climbs 32 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 46 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            8,
            "Not possible",
            73,
            98,
            58,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 458 meter pole. It climbs 48 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 36 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "71",
        "options": [
            "71",
            83,
            96,
            30,
            "Not possible",
            18
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 345 meter pole. It climbs 50 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 17 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "19",
        "options": [
            82,
            "Not possible",
            19,
            72,
            40,
            "19"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 111 meter pole. It climbs 31 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 10 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "9",
        "options": [
            34,
            20,
            83,
            "Not possible",
            "9",
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 224 meter pole. It climbs 41 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 41 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            67,
            71,
            "Not possible",
            54,
            65
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 294 meter pole. It climbs 47 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 5 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "13",
        "options": [
            26,
            11,
            89,
            85,
            "Not possible",
            "13"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 113 meter pole. It climbs 11 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 25 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            94,
            54,
            17,
            100
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 450 meter pole. It climbs 27 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 30 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            28,
            "Not possible",
            18,
            58,
            49,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 220 meter pole. It climbs 13 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 45 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            2,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            71,
            35,
            83
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 346 meter pole. It climbs 14 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 46 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            1,
            49,
            33,
            21
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 409 meter pole. It climbs 37 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 11 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "31",
        "options": [
            17,
            "Not possible",
            76,
            8,
            "31",
            49
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 359 meter pole. It climbs 12 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 8 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "175",
        "options": [
            67,
            "Not possible",
            21,
            "175",
            75,
            65
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 131 meter pole. It climbs 19 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 23 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            64,
            54,
            15,
            "Not possible",
            67,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 481 meter pole. It climbs 19 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 40 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            97,
            45,
            48,
            "Not possible",
            49
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 276 meter pole. It climbs 8 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 16 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            4,
            "Not possible",
            29,
            27,
            67
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 421 meter pole. It climbs 8 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 50 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            87,
            "Not possible",
            82,
            "Not possible",
            66,
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 262 meter pole. It climbs 47 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 30 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "27",
        "options": [
            66,
            32,
            "Not possible",
            64,
            61,
            "27"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 396 meter pole. It climbs 35 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 36 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            40,
            "Not possible",
            89,
            28,
            43
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 129 meter pole. It climbs 16 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 42 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            40,
            "Not possible",
            99,
            86,
            44
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 412 meter pole. It climbs 35 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 16 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "41",
        "options": [
            "41",
            "Not possible",
            22,
            22,
            66,
            100
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 499 meter pole. It climbs 7 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 25 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            32,
            "Not possible",
            97,
            52,
            49
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 174 meter pole. It climbs 10 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 45 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            41,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            80,
            82,
            91
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 288 meter pole. It climbs 28 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 8 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "27",
        "options": [
            34,
            "27",
            100,
            92,
            90,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 375 meter pole. It climbs 22 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 36 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            70,
            44,
            30,
            "Not possible",
            34
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 268 meter pole. It climbs 45 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 30 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "31",
        "options": [
            10,
            93,
            "Not possible",
            "31",
            46,
            48
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 138 meter pole. It climbs 38 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 46 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            98,
            27,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            99,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 480 meter pole. It climbs 37 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 48 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            16,
            91,
            44,
            68,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 221 meter pole. It climbs 31 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 14 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "25",
        "options": [
            78,
            67,
            "Not possible",
            47,
            42,
            "25"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 411 meter pole. It climbs 7 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 18 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            9,
            75,
            71,
            65,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 460 meter pole. It climbs 22 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 44 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            66,
            10,
            34,
            "Not possible",
            70,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 295 meter pole. It climbs 3 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 5 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            86,
            23,
            67,
            88,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 127 meter pole. It climbs 21 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 32 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            29,
            29,
            "Not possible",
            8,
            97
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 446 meter pole. It climbs 27 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 3 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "37",
        "options": [
            30,
            "37",
            60,
            39,
            36,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 115 meter pole. It climbs 12 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 44 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            85,
            18,
            15,
            74
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 334 meter pole. It climbs 17 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 29 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            47,
            62,
            39,
            67,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 166 meter pole. It climbs 8 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 26 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            48,
            8,
            7,
            30,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 388 meter pole. It climbs 18 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 31 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            1,
            "Not possible",
            82,
            57,
            92
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 411 meter pole. It climbs 40 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 24 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "49",
        "options": [
            11,
            "49",
            46,
            75,
            4,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 360 meter pole. It climbs 12 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 1 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "65",
        "options": [
            2,
            3,
            "65",
            3,
            "Not possible",
            4
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 168 meter pole. It climbs 4 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 44 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            45,
            30,
            "Not possible",
            90,
            "Not possible",
            2
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 467 meter pole. It climbs 44 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 7 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "25",
        "options": [
            1,
            61,
            5,
            56,
            "25",
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 183 meter pole. It climbs 2 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 41 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            94,
            "Not possible",
            71,
            25,
            "Not possible",
            65
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 462 meter pole. It climbs 44 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 36 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "107",
        "options": [
            "107",
            55,
            74,
            64,
            11,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 385 meter pole. It climbs 24 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 23 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "723",
        "options": [
            72,
            61,
            "723",
            66,
            56,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 492 meter pole. It climbs 19 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 45 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            99,
            "Not possible",
            52,
            "Not possible",
            96,
            53
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 280 meter pole. It climbs 34 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 19 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "35",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            83,
            "35",
            3,
            60,
            33
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 194 meter pole. It climbs 24 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 8 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "23",
        "options": [
            14,
            "Not possible",
            51,
            71,
            1,
            "23"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 204 meter pole. It climbs 23 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 4 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "21",
        "options": [
            37,
            "Not possible",
            48,
            "21",
            15,
            24
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 254 meter pole. It climbs 15 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 38 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            23,
            3,
            "Not possible",
            56,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 320 meter pole. It climbs 29 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 35 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            48,
            94,
            42,
            23,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 148 meter pole. It climbs 27 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 23 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "63",
        "options": [
            29,
            "63",
            67,
            77,
            "Not possible",
            28
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 154 meter pole. It climbs 36 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 12 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "11",
        "options": [
            "11",
            77,
            66,
            "Not possible",
            16,
            93
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 283 meter pole. It climbs 13 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 8 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "109",
        "options": [
            "109",
            8,
            18,
            68,
            "Not possible",
            90
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 372 meter pole. It climbs 22 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 37 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            86,
            83,
            12,
            45,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 443 meter pole. It climbs 44 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 21 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "37",
        "options": [
            74,
            22,
            "Not possible",
            "37",
            88,
            97
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 371 meter pole. It climbs 40 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 19 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "33",
        "options": [
            44,
            "Not possible",
            88,
            34,
            21,
            "33"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 353 meter pole. It climbs 3 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 11 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            44,
            63,
            "Not possible",
            80,
            30
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 221 meter pole. It climbs 50 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 35 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "25",
        "options": [
            78,
            "Not possible",
            9,
            85,
            "25",
            66
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 196 meter pole. It climbs 13 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 21 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            44,
            20,
            12,
            33,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 338 meter pole. It climbs 13 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 10 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "219",
        "options": [
            44,
            39,
            "219",
            36,
            "Not possible",
            61
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 104 meter pole. It climbs 7 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 17 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            90,
            80,
            58,
            "Not possible",
            36
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 476 meter pole. It climbs 50 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 38 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "73",
        "options": [
            95,
            15,
            9,
            "Not possible",
            42,
            "73"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 215 meter pole. It climbs 20 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 8 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "35",
        "options": [
            63,
            "35",
            67,
            30,
            73,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 283 meter pole. It climbs 47 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 20 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "19",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            25,
            35,
            80,
            59,
            "19"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 303 meter pole. It climbs 37 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 31 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "91",
        "options": [
            82,
            71,
            38,
            17,
            "Not possible",
            "91"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 295 meter pole. It climbs 10 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 15 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            52,
            "Not possible",
            89,
            "Not possible",
            97,
            17
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 123 meter pole. It climbs 16 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 19 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            96,
            "Not possible",
            19,
            39,
            79
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 181 meter pole. It climbs 11 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 31 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            47,
            "Not possible",
            97,
            "Not possible",
            93,
            56
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 157 meter pole. It climbs 8 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 7 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "299",
        "options": [
            72,
            "Not possible",
            27,
            44,
            "299",
            79
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 126 meter pole. It climbs 28 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 6 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "11",
        "options": [
            "11",
            "Not possible",
            23,
            73,
            87,
            71
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 242 meter pole. It climbs 4 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 20 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            87,
            40,
            28,
            19,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 372 meter pole. It climbs 15 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 35 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            24,
            29,
            79,
            91,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 281 meter pole. It climbs 39 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 31 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "63",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            85,
            "63",
            51,
            76,
            98
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 440 meter pole. It climbs 11 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 16 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            100,
            70,
            "Not possible",
            67,
            34
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 363 meter pole. It climbs 25 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 14 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "63",
        "options": [
            31,
            "Not possible",
            "63",
            24,
            8,
            39
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 113 meter pole. It climbs 33 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 40 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            76,
            83,
            90,
            "Not possible",
            17
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 161 meter pole. It climbs 1 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 20 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            20,
            "Not possible",
            95,
            67,
            "Not possible",
            58
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 357 meter pole. It climbs 4 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 6 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            1,
            59,
            21,
            "Not possible",
            43
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 413 meter pole. It climbs 27 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 44 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            23,
            65,
            72,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            83
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 273 meter pole. It climbs 34 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 6 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "19",
        "options": [
            13,
            "Not possible",
            51,
            "19",
            42,
            71
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 375 meter pole. It climbs 48 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 31 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "41",
        "options": [
            75,
            "Not possible",
            9,
            82,
            23,
            "41"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 166 meter pole. It climbs 39 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 2 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "9",
        "options": [
            39,
            2,
            "9",
            50,
            93,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 397 meter pole. It climbs 19 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 22 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            20,
            95,
            65,
            45,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 276 meter pole. It climbs 46 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 41 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "93",
        "options": [
            "93",
            52,
            44,
            30,
            13,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 110 meter pole. It climbs 28 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 24 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "43",
        "options": [
            83,
            21,
            "Not possible",
            3,
            65,
            "43"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 393 meter pole. It climbs 46 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 11 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "21",
        "options": [
            49,
            32,
            6,
            "Not possible",
            "21",
            3
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 338 meter pole. It climbs 27 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 31 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            29,
            "Not possible",
            45,
            38,
            15,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 310 meter pole. It climbs 34 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 8 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "23",
        "options": [
            55,
            79,
            "Not possible",
            "23",
            97,
            16
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 440 meter pole. It climbs 10 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 16 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            93,
            47,
            89,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            59
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 255 meter pole. It climbs 41 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 9 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "15",
        "options": [
            45,
            84,
            25,
            97,
            "Not possible",
            "15"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 105 meter pole. It climbs 21 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 46 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            48,
            81,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            32,
            36
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 381 meter pole. It climbs 3 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 43 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            68,
            75,
            79,
            "Not possible",
            79,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 352 meter pole. It climbs 15 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 15 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            61,
            "Not possible",
            27,
            61,
            28,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 387 meter pole. It climbs 41 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 19 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "33",
        "options": [
            14,
            "33",
            42,
            81,
            "Not possible",
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 285 meter pole. It climbs 48 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 34 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "35",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            49,
            54,
            68,
            75,
            "35"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 313 meter pole. It climbs 21 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 23 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            49,
            43,
            "Not possible",
            94,
            47,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 443 meter pole. It climbs 14 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 50 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            99,
            28,
            58,
            90,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 336 meter pole. It climbs 46 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 47 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            62,
            "Not possible",
            35,
            6,
            "Not possible",
            94
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 496 meter pole. It climbs 33 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 22 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "87",
        "options": [
            68,
            54,
            "Not possible",
            42,
            52,
            "87"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 338 meter pole. It climbs 11 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 20 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            64,
            53,
            37,
            "Not possible",
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 192 meter pole. It climbs 8 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 5 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "125",
        "options": [
            78,
            "Not possible",
            15,
            "125",
            26,
            59
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 254 meter pole. It climbs 17 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 6 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "45",
        "options": [
            "45",
            7,
            99,
            "Not possible",
            15,
            74
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 251 meter pole. It climbs 48 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 25 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "19",
        "options": [
            7,
            71,
            "Not possible",
            89,
            "19",
            84
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 108 meter pole. It climbs 39 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 43 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            45,
            "Not possible",
            20,
            "Not possible",
            13,
            99
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 360 meter pole. It climbs 38 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 40 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            28,
            97,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            21,
            62
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 367 meter pole. It climbs 42 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 10 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "23",
        "options": [
            28,
            "Not possible",
            3,
            75,
            "23",
            40
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 405 meter pole. It climbs 21 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 12 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "87",
        "options": [
            61,
            68,
            "87",
            21,
            25,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 453 meter pole. It climbs 23 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 25 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            67,
            "Not possible",
            54,
            "Not possible",
            35,
            41
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 223 meter pole. It climbs 31 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 3 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "15",
        "options": [
            79,
            "Not possible",
            61,
            87,
            32,
            "15"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 128 meter pole. It climbs 9 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 13 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            87,
            48,
            "Not possible",
            31,
            24
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 239 meter pole. It climbs 14 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 33 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            21,
            "Not possible",
            90,
            13,
            33
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 410 meter pole. It climbs 33 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 24 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "85",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            "85",
            19,
            58,
            51,
            30
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 381 meter pole. It climbs 45 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 13 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "23",
        "options": [
            77,
            2,
            51,
            "23",
            "Not possible",
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 358 meter pole. It climbs 29 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 28 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "659",
        "options": [
            66,
            67,
            57,
            "Not possible",
            "659",
            56
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 138 meter pole. It climbs 35 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 38 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            63,
            56,
            20,
            87,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 389 meter pole. It climbs 7 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 29 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            61,
            70,
            79,
            68
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 302 meter pole. It climbs 25 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 6 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "31",
        "options": [
            "31",
            56,
            "Not possible",
            18,
            42,
            52
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 245 meter pole. It climbs 10 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 41 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            44,
            53,
            78,
            9
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 256 meter pole. It climbs 45 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 20 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "19",
        "options": [
            34,
            58,
            30,
            31,
            "19",
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 123 meter pole. It climbs 36 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 30 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "31",
        "options": [
            8,
            3,
            "Not possible",
            69,
            "31",
            31
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 235 meter pole. It climbs 27 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 18 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "49",
        "options": [
            28,
            "Not possible",
            84,
            15,
            "49",
            30
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 380 meter pole. It climbs 24 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 6 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "41",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            "41",
            17,
            66,
            30,
            25
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 203 meter pole. It climbs 15 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 46 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            28,
            53,
            54,
            35,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 351 meter pole. It climbs 20 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 11 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "75",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            "75",
            22,
            12,
            58,
            90
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 103 meter pole. It climbs 44 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 11 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "5",
        "options": [
            35,
            19,
            "5",
            21,
            54,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 450 meter pole. It climbs 5 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 5 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            77,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            94,
            65,
            86
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 391 meter pole. It climbs 10 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 15 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            3,
            7,
            94,
            56,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 340 meter pole. It climbs 25 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 24 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "631",
        "options": [
            "631",
            "Not possible",
            26,
            10,
            30,
            34
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 412 meter pole. It climbs 18 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 4 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "59",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            93,
            56,
            95,
            "59",
            100
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 493 meter pole. It climbs 14 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 44 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            100,
            62,
            45,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            87
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 206 meter pole. It climbs 26 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 50 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            100,
            95,
            53,
            "Not possible",
            79,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 193 meter pole. It climbs 34 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 33 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "319",
        "options": [
            42,
            74,
            "Not possible",
            "319",
            87,
            83
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 261 meter pole. It climbs 30 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 9 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "23",
        "options": [
            "23",
            10,
            39,
            "Not possible",
            79,
            43
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 373 meter pole. It climbs 2 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 38 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            16,
            89,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            52,
            98
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 417 meter pole. It climbs 11 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 16 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            83,
            8,
            79,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 400 meter pole. It climbs 18 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 35 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            68,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            57,
            89,
            89
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 270 meter pole. It climbs 2 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 43 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            1,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            71,
            36,
            15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 319 meter pole. It climbs 37 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 32 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "115",
        "options": [
            64,
            50,
            97,
            "115",
            31,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 372 meter pole. It climbs 32 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 14 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "39",
        "options": [
            17,
            44,
            "39",
            "Not possible",
            84,
            88
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 256 meter pole. It climbs 41 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 1 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "13",
        "options": [
            41,
            90,
            "Not possible",
            "13",
            24,
            100
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 112 meter pole. It climbs 12 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 29 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            79,
            28,
            85,
            80
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 377 meter pole. It climbs 21 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 14 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "103",
        "options": [
            74,
            "103",
            "Not possible",
            91,
            26,
            77
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 340 meter pole. It climbs 38 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 47 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            18,
            68,
            "Not possible",
            45,
            61,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 131 meter pole. It climbs 24 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 22 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "109",
        "options": [
            2,
            "109",
            92,
            20,
            "Not possible",
            76
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 470 meter pole. It climbs 21 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 43 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            38,
            "Not possible",
            38,
            "Not possible",
            64,
            53
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 303 meter pole. It climbs 14 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 28 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            5,
            91,
            70,
            41,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 198 meter pole. It climbs 12 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 5 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "55",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            73,
            47,
            89,
            "55",
            13
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 131 meter pole. It climbs 1 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 20 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            81,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            10,
            76,
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 120 meter pole. It climbs 34 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 37 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            57,
            17,
            "Not possible",
            77,
            9,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 295 meter pole. It climbs 38 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 23 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "37",
        "options": [
            94,
            "37",
            25,
            92,
            16,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 342 meter pole. It climbs 49 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 33 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "39",
        "options": [
            2,
            "39",
            "Not possible",
            7,
            56,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 378 meter pole. It climbs 11 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 3 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "93",
        "options": [
            "93",
            96,
            77,
            37,
            75,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 446 meter pole. It climbs 23 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 42 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            30,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            27,
            47,
            57
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 403 meter pole. It climbs 5 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 21 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            40,
            81,
            27,
            96
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 280 meter pole. It climbs 48 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 42 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "79",
        "options": [
            57,
            68,
            "79",
            30,
            56,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 298 meter pole. It climbs 9 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 6 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "195",
        "options": [
            23,
            99,
            "Not possible",
            58,
            "195",
            74
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 298 meter pole. It climbs 24 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 8 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "37",
        "options": [
            20,
            25,
            "37",
            "Not possible",
            30,
            70
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 323 meter pole. It climbs 29 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 8 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "29",
        "options": [
            "29",
            65,
            99,
            "Not possible",
            12,
            26
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 370 meter pole. It climbs 9 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 23 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            5,
            "Not possible",
            26,
            59,
            56
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 301 meter pole. It climbs 43 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 35 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "67",
        "options": [
            98,
            52,
            "Not possible",
            "67",
            87,
            20
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 141 meter pole. It climbs 17 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 36 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            20,
            88,
            28,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 160 meter pole. It climbs 5 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 30 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            99,
            "Not possible",
            28,
            5,
            41
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 107 meter pole. It climbs 50 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 32 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "9",
        "options": [
            9,
            23,
            54,
            "9",
            "Not possible",
            19
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 185 meter pole. It climbs 1 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 2 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            66,
            90,
            57,
            67
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 491 meter pole. It climbs 2 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 9 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            43,
            18,
            8,
            67,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 239 meter pole. It climbs 27 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 36 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            5,
            13,
            32,
            "Not possible",
            14,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 404 meter pole. It climbs 40 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 4 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "23",
        "options": [
            "23",
            35,
            "Not possible",
            6,
            51,
            25
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 180 meter pole. It climbs 41 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 3 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "9",
        "options": [
            1,
            64,
            "9",
            66,
            "Not possible",
            73
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 334 meter pole. It climbs 5 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 25 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            75,
            76,
            99,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            56
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 168 meter pole. It climbs 43 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 19 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "13",
        "options": [
            45,
            86,
            47,
            "13",
            5,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 469 meter pole. It climbs 9 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 45 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            20,
            63,
            55,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            55
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 239 meter pole. It climbs 35 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 34 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "409",
        "options": [
            "409",
            21,
            18,
            50,
            "Not possible",
            21
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 378 meter pole. It climbs 7 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 39 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            39,
            31,
            72,
            89,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 271 meter pole. It climbs 44 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 8 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "15",
        "options": [
            "15",
            "Not possible",
            58,
            21,
            26,
            82
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 317 meter pole. It climbs 5 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 25 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            27,
            94,
            29,
            69,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 334 meter pole. It climbs 26 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 2 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "27",
        "options": [
            54,
            72,
            "27",
            "Not possible",
            69,
            16
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 296 meter pole. It climbs 14 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 12 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "283",
        "options": [
            "283",
            79,
            73,
            21,
            "Not possible",
            92
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 385 meter pole. It climbs 42 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 7 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "21",
        "options": [
            "21",
            43,
            58,
            32,
            "Not possible",
            29
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 195 meter pole. It climbs 9 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 34 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            99,
            49,
            49,
            75,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 387 meter pole. It climbs 14 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 16 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            8,
            100,
            66,
            73,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 371 meter pole. It climbs 24 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 10 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "51",
        "options": [
            18,
            84,
            "Not possible",
            35,
            48,
            "51"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 364 meter pole. It climbs 46 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 3 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "17",
        "options": [
            "17",
            5,
            91,
            29,
            83,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 118 meter pole. It climbs 39 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 20 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "11",
        "options": [
            "11",
            33,
            73,
            "Not possible",
            38,
            48
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 238 meter pole. It climbs 49 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 23 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "17",
        "options": [
            "17",
            82,
            7,
            100,
            27,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 380 meter pole. It climbs 49 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 24 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "29",
        "options": [
            85,
            88,
            "Not possible",
            "29",
            5,
            5
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 172 meter pole. It climbs 37 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 49 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            37,
            57,
            75,
            76,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 170 meter pole. It climbs 18 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 34 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            39,
            "Not possible",
            50,
            "Not possible",
            50,
            70
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 111 meter pole. It climbs 47 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 17 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "7",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            "7",
            27,
            73,
            69,
            66
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 238 meter pole. It climbs 22 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 30 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            62,
            "Not possible",
            56,
            14,
            45
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 192 meter pole. It climbs 7 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 9 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            100,
            "Not possible",
            72,
            26,
            47
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 497 meter pole. It climbs 2 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 47 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            26,
            15,
            10,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            85
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 458 meter pole. It climbs 21 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 28 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            44,
            64,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            63,
            85
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 250 meter pole. It climbs 22 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 5 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "29",
        "options": [
            41,
            "Not possible",
            20,
            "29",
            46,
            80
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 494 meter pole. It climbs 47 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 41 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "151",
        "options": [
            28,
            61,
            "151",
            90,
            "Not possible",
            52
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 181 meter pole. It climbs 21 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 31 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            9,
            65,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            16,
            87
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 337 meter pole. It climbs 13 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 36 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            35,
            99,
            "Not possible",
            33,
            28,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 433 meter pole. It climbs 28 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 12 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "53",
        "options": [
            "53",
            99,
            "Not possible",
            61,
            20,
            21
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 227 meter pole. It climbs 39 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 49 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            92,
            63,
            20,
            "Not possible",
            69
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 131 meter pole. It climbs 1 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 37 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            67,
            46,
            98,
            "Not possible",
            61,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 158 meter pole. It climbs 36 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 8 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "11",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            83,
            "11",
            22,
            87,
            24
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 433 meter pole. It climbs 46 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 26 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "41",
        "options": [
            5,
            87,
            27,
            "41",
            "Not possible",
            91
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 268 meter pole. It climbs 11 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 22 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            45,
            42,
            "Not possible",
            52,
            12,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 333 meter pole. It climbs 19 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 44 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            17,
            38,
            28,
            57,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 481 meter pole. It climbs 23 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 37 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            33,
            100,
            5,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            10
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 134 meter pole. It climbs 39 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 40 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            31,
            44,
            "Not possible",
            87,
            "Not possible",
            94
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 144 meter pole. It climbs 9 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 1 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "35",
        "options": [
            25,
            "35",
            50,
            49,
            94,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 271 meter pole. It climbs 8 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 10 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            98,
            "Not possible",
            94,
            15,
            "Not possible",
            58
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 369 meter pole. It climbs 31 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 36 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            65,
            39,
            "Not possible",
            91,
            78,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 271 meter pole. It climbs 45 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 34 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "43",
        "options": [
            59,
            "Not possible",
            11,
            98,
            "43",
            84
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 168 meter pole. It climbs 44 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 20 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "13",
        "options": [
            "13",
            45,
            61,
            14,
            3,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 282 meter pole. It climbs 42 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 47 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            21,
            29,
            38,
            "Not possible",
            58
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 194 meter pole. It climbs 25 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 33 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            6,
            "Not possible",
            92,
            "Not possible",
            49,
            20
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 232 meter pole. It climbs 46 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 34 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "33",
        "options": [
            72,
            70,
            "33",
            44,
            "Not possible",
            80
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 229 meter pole. It climbs 21 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 10 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "39",
        "options": [
            69,
            "Not possible",
            76,
            "39",
            83,
            38
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 333 meter pole. It climbs 26 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 6 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "33",
        "options": [
            72,
            22,
            "Not possible",
            16,
            "33",
            29
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 430 meter pole. It climbs 28 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 16 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "69",
        "options": [
            86,
            95,
            49,
            "Not possible",
            "69",
            88
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 321 meter pole. It climbs 26 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 47 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            51,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            100,
            29,
            50
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 291 meter pole. It climbs 35 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 12 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "25",
        "options": [
            17,
            49,
            "25",
            16,
            15,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 499 meter pole. It climbs 28 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 5 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "43",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            44,
            71,
            85,
            76,
            "43"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 220 meter pole. It climbs 48 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 47 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "345",
        "options": [
            11,
            "Not possible",
            45,
            90,
            22,
            "345"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 294 meter pole. It climbs 10 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 10 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            77,
            55,
            15,
            70,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 337 meter pole. It climbs 34 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 13 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "31",
        "options": [
            32,
            5,
            9,
            "Not possible",
            64,
            "31"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 283 meter pole. It climbs 1 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 46 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            51,
            39,
            74,
            73,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 382 meter pole. It climbs 16 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 25 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            50,
            "Not possible",
            20,
            "Not possible",
            29,
            14
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 207 meter pole. It climbs 38 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 42 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            84,
            39,
            27,
            30,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 220 meter pole. It climbs 9 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 50 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            53,
            7,
            36,
            "Not possible",
            66
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 342 meter pole. It climbs 47 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 19 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "23",
        "options": [
            61,
            "23",
            32,
            59,
            "Not possible",
            26
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 177 meter pole. It climbs 34 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 36 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            18,
            78,
            68,
            45,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 303 meter pole. It climbs 37 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 39 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            41,
            "Not possible",
            100,
            24,
            97
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 425 meter pole. It climbs 45 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 2 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "19",
        "options": [
            76,
            "Not possible",
            77,
            "19",
            67,
            1
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 418 meter pole. It climbs 11 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 44 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            42,
            100,
            "Not possible",
            2,
            58,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 307 meter pole. It climbs 24 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 6 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "33",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            58,
            63,
            76,
            "33",
            26
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 367 meter pole. It climbs 41 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 32 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "75",
        "options": [
            89,
            "Not possible",
            43,
            88,
            98,
            "75"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 312 meter pole. It climbs 47 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 19 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "21",
        "options": [
            37,
            18,
            38,
            "Not possible",
            4,
            "21"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 194 meter pole. It climbs 5 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 24 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            70,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            90,
            47,
            79
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 458 meter pole. It climbs 37 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 43 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            26,
            47,
            93,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            100
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 139 meter pole. It climbs 23 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 17 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "41",
        "options": [
            91,
            "Not possible",
            75,
            66,
            "41",
            32
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 108 meter pole. It climbs 40 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 36 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "35",
        "options": [
            2,
            67,
            "Not possible",
            96,
            "35",
            32
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 279 meter pole. It climbs 30 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 31 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            8,
            "Not possible",
            61,
            65,
            "Not possible",
            12
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 114 meter pole. It climbs 48 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 2 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "5",
        "options": [
            54,
            "5",
            "Not possible",
            93,
            2,
            76
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 455 meter pole. It climbs 12 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 14 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            38,
            54,
            71,
            "Not possible",
            6
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 356 meter pole. It climbs 48 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 44 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "155",
        "options": [
            "155",
            "Not possible",
            30,
            89,
            33,
            61
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 401 meter pole. It climbs 31 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 47 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            97,
            77,
            25,
            52
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 208 meter pole. It climbs 49 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 13 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "11",
        "options": [
            27,
            97,
            19,
            85,
            "Not possible",
            "11"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 395 meter pole. It climbs 34 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 42 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            39,
            70,
            60,
            66,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 110 meter pole. It climbs 6 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 2 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "53",
        "options": [
            48,
            84,
            83,
            32,
            "Not possible",
            "53"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 239 meter pole. It climbs 14 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 43 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            49,
            92,
            73,
            15
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 311 meter pole. It climbs 5 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 13 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            9,
            95,
            "Not possible",
            59,
            69
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 465 meter pole. It climbs 22 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 21 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "887",
        "options": [
            61,
            58,
            "Not possible",
            91,
            90,
            "887"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 355 meter pole. It climbs 8 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 44 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            36,
            92,
            "Not possible",
            53,
            "Not possible",
            88
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 281 meter pole. It climbs 23 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 42 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            99,
            82,
            "Not possible",
            41,
            69,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 219 meter pole. It climbs 1 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 42 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            53,
            21,
            "Not possible",
            10,
            73,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 230 meter pole. It climbs 45 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 16 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "15",
        "options": [
            73,
            "15",
            9,
            5,
            93,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 492 meter pole. It climbs 18 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 18 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            43,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            41,
            28,
            90
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 203 meter pole. It climbs 37 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 38 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            1,
            35,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            4,
            72
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 291 meter pole. It climbs 42 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 50 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            47,
            "Not possible",
            87,
            61,
            36
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 418 meter pole. It climbs 38 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 14 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "33",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            88,
            38,
            33,
            95,
            "33"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 369 meter pole. It climbs 16 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 8 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "91",
        "options": [
            19,
            "91",
            76,
            "Not possible",
            14,
            11
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 225 meter pole. It climbs 10 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 8 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "217",
        "options": [
            49,
            30,
            96,
            "Not possible",
            42,
            "217"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 254 meter pole. It climbs 32 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 26 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "75",
        "options": [
            50,
            "Not possible",
            "75",
            12,
            23,
            26
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 344 meter pole. It climbs 16 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 38 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            4,
            59,
            19,
            39,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 442 meter pole. It climbs 11 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 3 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "109",
        "options": [
            41,
            13,
            "Not possible",
            "109",
            19,
            44
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 298 meter pole. It climbs 37 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 28 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "59",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            52,
            90,
            "59",
            39,
            77
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 447 meter pole. It climbs 23 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 35 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            67,
            91,
            15,
            8
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 390 meter pole. It climbs 36 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 5 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "25",
        "options": [
            21,
            34,
            "Not possible",
            "25",
            44,
            27
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 429 meter pole. It climbs 45 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 14 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "27",
        "options": [
            99,
            "27",
            "Not possible",
            72,
            30,
            47
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 380 meter pole. It climbs 12 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 44 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            8,
            81,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            25,
            42
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 169 meter pole. It climbs 37 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 5 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "11",
        "options": [
            19,
            "11",
            "Not possible",
            91,
            42,
            48
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 352 meter pole. It climbs 14 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 12 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "339",
        "options": [
            "339",
            7,
            99,
            1,
            "Not possible",
            66
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A mosquito is climbing a 153 meter pole. It climbs 22 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 46 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            1,
            6,
            93,
            "Not possible",
            5,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A fly is climbing a 498 meter pole. It climbs 13 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 17 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            94,
            3,
            45,
            62,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A monkey is climbing a 122 meter pole. It climbs 33 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 37 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            26,
            33,
            92,
            82
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 136 meter pole. It climbs 1 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 6 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            22,
            "Not possible",
            69,
            "Not possible",
            86,
            70
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 265 meter pole. It climbs 3 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 17 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            93,
            "Not possible",
            23,
            36,
            97,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 351 meter pole. It climbs 38 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 27 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "59",
        "options": [
            61,
            77,
            "Not possible",
            "59",
            74,
            52
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snake is climbing a 361 meter pole. It climbs 45 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 39 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "107",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            62,
            100,
            64,
            90,
            "107"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 386 meter pole. It climbs 34 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 34 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            53,
            35,
            "Not possible",
            2,
            "Not possible",
            41
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 350 meter pole. It climbs 27 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 45 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            12,
            8,
            91,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            99
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 312 meter pole. It climbs 40 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 24 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "35",
        "options": [
            66,
            49,
            "Not possible",
            23,
            "35",
            39
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 161 meter pole. It climbs 35 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 47 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            52,
            "Not possible",
            39,
            36,
            "Not possible",
            40
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A caterpillar is climbing a 447 meter pole. It climbs 21 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 39 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            7,
            28,
            "Not possible",
            67,
            57,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 244 meter pole. It climbs 24 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 34 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            64,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            34,
            11,
            19
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 189 meter pole. It climbs 25 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 1 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "15",
        "options": [
            98,
            52,
            "15",
            "Not possible",
            67,
            14
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A snail is climbing a 425 meter pole. It climbs 2 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 14 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            27,
            56,
            2,
            75
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 240 meter pole. It climbs 22 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 14 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "57",
        "options": [
            53,
            95,
            54,
            91,
            "Not possible",
            "57"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A bee is climbing a 176 meter pole. It climbs 10 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 44 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            78,
            3,
            85,
            24
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A squirrel is climbing a 364 meter pole. It climbs 4 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 14 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            97,
            91,
            15,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            85
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A girl is climbing a 227 meter pole. It climbs 5 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 5 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            96,
            79,
            26,
            "Not possible",
            "Not possible",
            86
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "A man is climbing a 276 meter pole. It climbs 16 meter in one sec and in the next second it comes 42 meter down. How much time will it take to climb the poll? ",
        "answer": "Not possible",
        "options": [
            22,
            48,
            48,
            "Not possible",
            5,
            "Not possible"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Grant sold a book to Nova at a price of 903 after giving 41 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1530.51",
        "options": [
            "749.38",
            "1530.51",
            "679.97",
            "640.43",
            "690.63"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Kayden sold a book to Emmitt at a price of 775 after giving 29 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1091.55",
        "options": [
            "600.78",
            "676.86",
            "1091.55",
            "636.55",
            "629.06"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Grant sold a book to Madden at a price of 914 after giving 24 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1202.63",
        "options": [
            "1202.63",
            "774.58",
            "816.07",
            "766.78",
            "737.10"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "George sold a book to Cairo at a price of 743 after giving 12 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "844.32",
        "options": [
            "677.92",
            "844.32",
            "681.65",
            "663.39",
            "700.94"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Phillip sold a book to Byron at a price of 961 after giving 36 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1501.56",
        "options": [
            "814.41",
            "706.62",
            "746.12",
            "756.69",
            "1501.56"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Leo sold a book to Shepard at a price of 680 after giving 56 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1545.45",
        "options": [
            "435.90",
            "531.25",
            "478.87",
            "1545.45",
            "469.61"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Cash sold a book to Thaddeus at a price of 819 after giving 79 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "3900.00",
        "options": [
            "587.10",
            "501.84",
            "3900.00",
            "457.54",
            "514.29"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Milan sold a book to Boston at a price of 198 after giving 30 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "282.86",
        "options": [
            "172.17",
            "282.86",
            "159.68",
            "161.63",
            "152.31"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Pierce sold a book to Braydon at a price of 234 after giving 75 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "936.00",
        "options": [
            "133.71",
            "936.00",
            "149.76",
            "170.18",
            "146.25"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Hector sold a book to Scott at a price of 753 after giving 29 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1060.56",
        "options": [
            "611.20",
            "618.48",
            "583.72",
            "657.64",
            "1060.56"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jayden sold a book to Duke at a price of 226 after giving 4 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "235.42",
        "options": [
            "217.31",
            "221.57",
            "219.42",
            "218.99",
            "235.42"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Parker sold a book to Kamari at a price of 582 after giving 51 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1187.76",
        "options": [
            "1187.76",
            "385.43",
            "420.98",
            "413.35",
            "463.75"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Malachi sold a book to Misael at a price of 673 after giving 35 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1035.38",
        "options": [
            "525.78",
            "1035.38",
            "572.77",
            "498.52",
            "533.07"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jacob sold a book to Abdullah at a price of 536 after giving 55 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1191.11",
        "options": [
            "379.47",
            "345.81",
            "1191.11",
            "420.39",
            "372.22"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Louis sold a book to Zain at a price of 349 after giving 3 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "359.79",
        "options": [
            "340.82",
            "343.84",
            "338.83",
            "359.79",
            "341.32"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Edgar sold a book to Kylan at a price of 111 after giving 44 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "198.21",
        "options": [
            "90.98",
            "82.10",
            "198.21",
            "77.08",
            "83.46"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Patrick sold a book to Brentley at a price of 240 after giving 74 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "923.08",
        "options": [
            "137.93",
            "154.34",
            "923.08",
            "150.75",
            "175.18"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Isaiah sold a book to Judson at a price of 402 after giving 77 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1747.83",
        "options": [
            "227.12",
            "254.83",
            "290.25",
            "248.76",
            "1747.83"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Cade sold a book to Roland at a price of 875 after giving 13 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1005.75",
        "options": [
            "1005.75",
            "774.34",
            "821.60",
            "792.57",
            "797.27"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Enrique sold a book to Samir at a price of 207 after giving 56 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "470.45",
        "options": [
            "142.96",
            "145.77",
            "132.69",
            "161.72",
            "470.45"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Cohen sold a book to Clyde at a price of 788 after giving 45 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1432.73",
        "options": [
            "1432.73",
            "579.41",
            "589.16",
            "643.27",
            "543.45"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Corbin sold a book to Kamdyn at a price of 454 after giving 67 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1375.76",
        "options": [
            "295.57",
            "1375.76",
            "271.86",
            "302.16",
            "340.07"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Grant sold a book to Roger at a price of 345 after giving 1 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "348.48",
        "options": [
            "348.48",
            "342.43",
            "343.28",
            "342.26",
            "341.58"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Maximiliano sold a book to Brock at a price of 950 after giving 38 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1532.26",
        "options": [
            "1532.26",
            "688.41",
            "728.53",
            "739.30",
            "798.32"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Nathan sold a book to Duke at a price of 455 after giving 21 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "575.95",
        "options": [
            "389.55",
            "376.03",
            "411.76",
            "575.95",
            "393.09"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Lennox sold a book to Ignacio at a price of 785 after giving 58 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1869.05",
        "options": [
            "536.20",
            "1869.05",
            "496.84",
            "608.53",
            "547.04"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Fabian sold a book to Morgan at a price of 694 after giving 16 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "826.19",
        "options": [
            "619.64",
            "598.28",
            "615.25",
            "826.19",
            "642.59"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Hayes sold a book to Kingsley at a price of 177 after giving 15 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "208.24",
        "options": [
            "153.91",
            "164.65",
            "208.24",
            "158.04",
            "159.10"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Marcus sold a book to Carmelo at a price of 428 after giving 52 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "891.67",
        "options": [
            "281.58",
            "307.91",
            "891.67",
            "302.26",
            "339.68"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Malakai sold a book to Westley at a price of 502 after giving 80 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "2510.00",
        "options": [
            "306.10",
            "313.75",
            "2510.00",
            "358.57",
            "278.89"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jensen sold a book to Jamal at a price of 185 after giving 25 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "246.67",
        "options": [
            "164.44",
            "148.00",
            "246.67",
            "155.79",
            "154.17"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Angelo sold a book to Alfredo at a price of 739 after giving 5 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "777.89",
        "options": [
            "710.58",
            "703.81",
            "712.29",
            "720.98",
            "777.89"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Maximus sold a book to Reign at a price of 844 after giving 10 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "937.78",
        "options": [
            "781.48",
            "937.78",
            "767.27",
            "785.12",
            "803.81"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Frank sold a book to Makai at a price of 102 after giving 76 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "425.00",
        "options": [
            "425.00",
            "64.97",
            "63.43",
            "73.91",
            "57.95"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Tyler sold a book to Van at a price of 593 after giving 35 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "912.31",
        "options": [
            "469.70",
            "463.28",
            "912.31",
            "439.26",
            "504.68"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Bryson sold a book to Kylen at a price of 891 after giving 58 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "2121.43",
        "options": [
            "563.92",
            "608.61",
            "690.70",
            "2121.43",
            "620.91"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jax sold a book to Callen at a price of 382 after giving 76 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1591.67",
        "options": [
            "1591.67",
            "217.05",
            "243.31",
            "237.56",
            "276.81"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ryder sold a book to Toby at a price of 596 after giving 1 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "602.02",
        "options": [
            "602.02",
            "590.10",
            "591.27",
            "593.03",
            "591.56"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Bennett sold a book to Lachlan at a price of 435 after giving 9 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "478.02",
        "options": [
            "478.02",
            "416.27",
            "405.78",
            "399.08",
            "407.49"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Mohamed sold a book to Zaid at a price of 912 after giving 43 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1600.00",
        "options": [
            "689.60",
            "678.57",
            "1600.00",
            "637.76",
            "750.62"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Barrett sold a book to Benton at a price of 705 after giving 59 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1719.51",
        "options": [
            "488.73",
            "544.40",
            "1719.51",
            "478.94",
            "443.40"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Benson sold a book to Santino at a price of 700 after giving 68 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "2187.50",
        "options": [
            "453.37",
            "463.58",
            "2187.50",
            "522.39",
            "416.67"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ibrahim sold a book to Jadiel at a price of 967 after giving 16 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1151.19",
        "options": [
            "1151.19",
            "895.37",
            "857.27",
            "833.62",
            "863.39"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Hank sold a book to Lance at a price of 303 after giving 3 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "312.37",
        "options": [
            "298.52",
            "296.33",
            "295.90",
            "294.17",
            "312.37"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Wesley sold a book to Heath at a price of 687 after giving 8 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "746.74",
        "options": [
            "660.58",
            "746.74",
            "648.11",
            "645.68",
            "636.11"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Emmanuel sold a book to Wayne at a price of 629 after giving 51 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1283.67",
        "options": [
            "446.73",
            "501.20",
            "416.56",
            "454.97",
            "1283.67"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Joshua sold a book to Gerald at a price of 292 after giving 41 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "494.92",
        "options": [
            "242.32",
            "223.33",
            "207.09",
            "219.88",
            "494.92"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Stephen sold a book to Bodie at a price of 200 after giving 77 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "869.57",
        "options": [
            "112.99",
            "126.78",
            "869.57",
            "123.76",
            "144.40"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jameson sold a book to Dakari at a price of 680 after giving 57 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1581.40",
        "options": [
            "476.36",
            "529.18",
            "1581.40",
            "467.03",
            "433.12"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Hayes sold a book to Skylar at a price of 143 after giving 70 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "476.67",
        "options": [
            "476.67",
            "93.77",
            "84.12",
            "91.67",
            "105.93"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jay sold a book to Lucian at a price of 909 after giving 43 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1594.74",
        "options": [
            "635.66",
            "748.15",
            "676.34",
            "687.33",
            "1594.74"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Henry sold a book to Alessandro at a price of 475 after giving 72 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1696.43",
        "options": [
            "1696.43",
            "308.44",
            "349.26",
            "276.16",
            "301.40"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Brayden sold a book to Jeremias at a price of 169 after giving 61 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "433.33",
        "options": [
            "433.33",
            "129.50",
            "113.58",
            "115.95",
            "104.97"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Declan sold a book to Jamie at a price of 564 after giving 49 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1105.88",
        "options": [
            "1105.88",
            "412.43",
            "453.01",
            "378.52",
            "405.17"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Andre sold a book to Colson at a price of 904 after giving 27 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1238.36",
        "options": [
            "1238.36",
            "796.48",
            "711.81",
            "751.77",
            "743.42"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Elliot sold a book to Kellan at a price of 648 after giving 53 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1378.72",
        "options": [
            "463.69",
            "455.06",
            "512.25",
            "423.53",
            "1378.72"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Odin sold a book to Bowie at a price of 162 after giving 15 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "190.59",
        "options": [
            "140.87",
            "190.59",
            "150.70",
            "145.62",
            "144.64"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Avery sold a book to Zev at a price of 740 after giving 5 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "778.95",
        "options": [
            "704.76",
            "721.95",
            "778.95",
            "713.25",
            "711.54"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Derek sold a book to Devon at a price of 104 after giving 55 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "231.11",
        "options": [
            "231.11",
            "73.63",
            "67.10",
            "72.22",
            "81.57"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jordan sold a book to Zahir at a price of 317 after giving 2 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "323.47",
        "options": [
            "323.47",
            "312.01",
            "313.86",
            "310.78",
            "312.32"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Matteo sold a book to Westin at a price of 552 after giving 61 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1415.38",
        "options": [
            "342.86",
            "370.97",
            "1415.38",
            "378.73",
            "422.99"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Hugo sold a book to Ralph at a price of 852 after giving 59 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "2078.05",
        "options": [
            "578.80",
            "535.85",
            "2078.05",
            "657.92",
            "590.64"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Moises sold a book to Wallace at a price of 294 after giving 58 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "700.00",
        "options": [
            "186.08",
            "700.00",
            "227.91",
            "200.82",
            "204.88"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "George sold a book to Gustavo at a price of 786 after giving 20 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "982.50",
        "options": [
            "677.59",
            "655.00",
            "683.48",
            "982.50",
            "714.55"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Dylan sold a book to Coen at a price of 840 after giving 32 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1235.29",
        "options": [
            "1235.29",
            "668.79",
            "636.36",
            "677.42",
            "724.14"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Austin sold a book to Jabari at a price of 402 after giving 30 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "574.29",
        "options": [
            "324.19",
            "574.29",
            "349.57",
            "328.16",
            "309.23"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Gael sold a book to Harley at a price of 296 after giving 54 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "643.48",
        "options": [
            "643.48",
            "206.70",
            "210.68",
            "233.07",
            "192.21"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Moises sold a book to Darwin at a price of 810 after giving 52 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1687.50",
        "options": [
            "582.73",
            "532.89",
            "642.86",
            "1687.50",
            "572.03"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Hugo sold a book to Kylen at a price of 926 after giving 4 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "964.58",
        "options": [
            "897.29",
            "899.03",
            "964.58",
            "890.38",
            "907.84"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Kayden sold a book to Ridge at a price of 380 after giving 14 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "441.86",
        "options": [
            "355.14",
            "343.89",
            "441.86",
            "333.33",
            "341.73"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Remy sold a book to Alessandro at a price of 398 after giving 13 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "457.47",
        "options": [
            "457.47",
            "352.21",
            "360.51",
            "373.71",
            "362.64"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Kyrie sold a book to Lewis at a price of 694 after giving 62 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1826.32",
        "options": [
            "529.77",
            "463.90",
            "1826.32",
            "473.72",
            "428.40"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Conner sold a book to Kyng at a price of 975 after giving 63 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "2635.14",
        "options": [
            "598.16",
            "662.14",
            "2635.14",
            "741.44",
            "648.27"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Solomon sold a book to Arian at a price of 483 after giving 61 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1238.46",
        "options": [
            "300.00",
            "331.39",
            "370.11",
            "1238.46",
            "324.60"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Mark sold a book to Ricky at a price of 937 after giving 36 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1464.06",
        "options": [
            "737.80",
            "727.48",
            "1464.06",
            "688.97",
            "794.07"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jamison sold a book to Coleman at a price of 467 after giving 5 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "491.58",
        "options": [
            "449.04",
            "450.12",
            "455.61",
            "491.58",
            "444.76"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Finn sold a book to Jamari at a price of 772 after giving 21 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "977.22",
        "options": [
            "977.22",
            "638.02",
            "660.96",
            "698.64",
            "666.95"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Nolan sold a book to Jaxen at a price of 887 after giving 1 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "895.96",
        "options": [
            "880.40",
            "882.59",
            "895.96",
            "879.96",
            "878.22"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jaxton sold a book to Talon at a price of 632 after giving 63 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1708.11",
        "options": [
            "387.73",
            "480.61",
            "1708.11",
            "429.20",
            "420.21"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Kamden sold a book to Jalen at a price of 680 after giving 24 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "894.74",
        "options": [
            "548.39",
            "607.14",
            "894.74",
            "570.47",
            "576.27"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Preston sold a book to Ira at a price of 357 after giving 59 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "870.73",
        "options": [
            "224.53",
            "242.53",
            "870.73",
            "247.49",
            "275.68"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Trevor sold a book to Louie at a price of 236 after giving 53 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "502.13",
        "options": [
            "154.25",
            "186.56",
            "165.73",
            "502.13",
            "168.87"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Devin sold a book to Boone at a price of 932 after giving 64 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "2588.89",
        "options": [
            "568.29",
            "2588.89",
            "616.40",
            "706.06",
            "629.73"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jaiden sold a book to Leandro at a price of 280 after giving 63 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "756.76",
        "options": [
            "190.15",
            "186.17",
            "756.76",
            "171.78",
            "212.93"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Pablo sold a book to Genesis at a price of 407 after giving 33 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "607.46",
        "options": [
            "321.99",
            "326.25",
            "306.02",
            "607.46",
            "349.36"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Calvin sold a book to Dario at a price of 633 after giving 79 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "3014.29",
        "options": [
            "397.49",
            "387.87",
            "353.63",
            "3014.29",
            "453.76"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Memphis sold a book to Sincere at a price of 663 after giving 31 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "960.87",
        "options": [
            "506.11",
            "960.87",
            "531.25",
            "574.03",
            "537.93"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Calvin sold a book to Guillermo at a price of 821 after giving 69 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "2648.39",
        "options": [
            "610.41",
            "485.80",
            "528.99",
            "541.02",
            "2648.39"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Emanuel sold a book to Danny at a price of 332 after giving 43 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "582.46",
        "options": [
            "232.17",
            "251.04",
            "273.25",
            "247.02",
            "582.46"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Daxton sold a book to Lee at a price of 750 after giving 10 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "833.33",
        "options": [
            "697.67",
            "694.44",
            "714.29",
            "833.33",
            "681.82"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Franklin sold a book to Crew at a price of 212 after giving 4 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "220.83",
        "options": [
            "205.83",
            "207.84",
            "220.83",
            "203.85",
            "205.43"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Beckett sold a book to Bjorn at a price of 801 after giving 44 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1430.36",
        "options": [
            "602.26",
            "592.46",
            "1430.36",
            "556.25",
            "656.56"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "John sold a book to Dario at a price of 187 after giving 64 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "519.44",
        "options": [
            "123.68",
            "141.67",
            "126.35",
            "114.02",
            "519.44"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Deacon sold a book to Karsyn at a price of 982 after giving 77 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "4269.57",
        "options": [
            "709.03",
            "4269.57",
            "622.50",
            "607.67",
            "554.80"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Grant sold a book to Hezekiah at a price of 671 after giving 42 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1156.90",
        "options": [
            "502.25",
            "554.55",
            "510.27",
            "472.54",
            "1156.90"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Kenneth sold a book to Landyn at a price of 435 after giving 28 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "604.17",
        "options": [
            "359.50",
            "604.17",
            "355.39",
            "381.58",
            "339.84"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Johnny sold a book to Mitchell at a price of 714 after giving 63 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1929.73",
        "options": [
            "542.97",
            "438.04",
            "474.73",
            "484.89",
            "1929.73"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Bruce sold a book to Kenzo at a price of 438 after giving 24 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "576.32",
        "options": [
            "576.32",
            "371.19",
            "353.23",
            "367.45",
            "391.07"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Kyrie sold a book to Clay at a price of 828 after giving 74 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "3184.62",
        "options": [
            "475.86",
            "532.48",
            "520.10",
            "3184.62",
            "604.38"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Hayes sold a book to Gustavo at a price of 464 after giving 32 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "682.35",
        "options": [
            "351.52",
            "682.35",
            "400.00",
            "369.43",
            "374.19"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Wade sold a book to Kendall at a price of 145 after giving 28 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "201.39",
        "options": [
            "127.19",
            "118.46",
            "119.83",
            "113.28",
            "201.39"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Luca sold a book to Cedric at a price of 125 after giving 18 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "152.44",
        "options": [
            "152.44",
            "110.13",
            "109.27",
            "114.68",
            "105.93"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Dallas sold a book to Tristian at a price of 612 after giving 18 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "746.34",
        "options": [
            "561.47",
            "518.64",
            "539.21",
            "534.97",
            "746.34"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Nasir sold a book to Chaim at a price of 164 after giving 27 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "224.66",
        "options": [
            "144.49",
            "129.13",
            "134.87",
            "136.38",
            "224.66"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jose sold a book to Makai at a price of 553 after giving 48 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1063.46",
        "options": [
            "373.65",
            "406.62",
            "445.97",
            "399.57",
            "1063.46"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Landon sold a book to Marcellus at a price of 255 after giving 72 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "910.71",
        "options": [
            "910.71",
            "148.26",
            "165.58",
            "161.80",
            "187.50"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Kason sold a book to Ephraim at a price of 775 after giving 49 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1519.61",
        "options": [
            "622.49",
            "520.13",
            "556.75",
            "566.73",
            "1519.61"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Royal sold a book to Aden at a price of 228 after giving 74 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "876.92",
        "options": [
            "166.42",
            "143.22",
            "131.03",
            "876.92",
            "146.62"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Damien sold a book to Dakari at a price of 364 after giving 77 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1582.61",
        "options": [
            "205.65",
            "225.25",
            "230.74",
            "1582.61",
            "262.82"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sergio sold a book to Kalel at a price of 881 after giving 73 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "3262.96",
        "options": [
            "509.25",
            "645.42",
            "569.31",
            "556.19",
            "3262.96"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Landon sold a book to Ridge at a price of 365 after giving 28 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "506.94",
        "options": [
            "301.65",
            "320.18",
            "285.16",
            "298.20",
            "506.94"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ronan sold a book to Harper at a price of 521 after giving 18 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "635.37",
        "options": [
            "477.98",
            "441.53",
            "459.03",
            "455.42",
            "635.37"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jack sold a book to Koa at a price of 536 after giving 6 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "570.21",
        "options": [
            "570.21",
            "511.45",
            "520.39",
            "505.66",
            "512.92"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Remington sold a book to Dillon at a price of 423 after giving 17 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "509.64",
        "options": [
            "375.17",
            "372.36",
            "389.86",
            "509.64",
            "361.54"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Arjun sold a book to Junior at a price of 402 after giving 40 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "670.00",
        "options": [
            "309.23",
            "670.00",
            "335.00",
            "287.14",
            "304.55"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jensen sold a book to Marc at a price of 266 after giving 1 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "268.69",
        "options": [
            "268.69",
            "263.37",
            "264.68",
            "263.89",
            "264.02"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Brayden sold a book to Roy at a price of 735 after giving 29 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1035.21",
        "options": [
            "569.77",
            "603.70",
            "641.92",
            "1035.21",
            "596.59"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alejandro sold a book to Salvatore at a price of 257 after giving 61 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "658.97",
        "options": [
            "159.63",
            "176.33",
            "172.72",
            "658.97",
            "196.93"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Kash sold a book to Keagan at a price of 829 after giving 34 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1256.06",
        "options": [
            "651.73",
            "618.66",
            "1256.06",
            "660.56",
            "708.55"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ezequiel sold a book to Camdyn at a price of 536 after giving 47 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1011.32",
        "options": [
            "396.30",
            "389.53",
            "1011.32",
            "434.01",
            "364.63"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Liam sold a book to Westin at a price of 977 after giving 36 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1526.56",
        "options": [
            "769.29",
            "758.54",
            "827.97",
            "1526.56",
            "718.38"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Angelo sold a book to Junior at a price of 965 after giving 78 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "4386.36",
        "options": [
            "4386.36",
            "608.83",
            "542.13",
            "694.24",
            "594.21"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Kaiden sold a book to Vihaan at a price of 828 after giving 55 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1840.00",
        "options": [
            "586.19",
            "1840.00",
            "575.00",
            "649.41",
            "534.19"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Adan sold a book to Kace at a price of 617 after giving 78 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "2804.55",
        "options": [
            "389.27",
            "2804.55",
            "443.88",
            "346.63",
            "379.93"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Kyson sold a book to Elisha at a price of 284 after giving 33 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "423.88",
        "options": [
            "243.78",
            "224.68",
            "227.66",
            "423.88",
            "213.53"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Leonardo sold a book to Kamdyn at a price of 716 after giving 43 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1256.14",
        "options": [
            "532.74",
            "589.30",
            "1256.14",
            "500.70",
            "541.40"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Corbin sold a book to Bishop at a price of 935 after giving 70 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "3116.67",
        "options": [
            "692.59",
            "3116.67",
            "550.00",
            "613.11",
            "599.36"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Elliot sold a book to Judson at a price of 934 after giving 56 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "2122.73",
        "options": [
            "598.72",
            "729.69",
            "645.03",
            "657.75",
            "2122.73"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Myles sold a book to Dash at a price of 682 after giving 57 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1586.05",
        "options": [
            "530.74",
            "1586.05",
            "477.76",
            "468.41",
            "434.39"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ryan sold a book to Wallace at a price of 775 after giving 60 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1937.50",
        "options": [
            "596.15",
            "523.65",
            "1937.50",
            "534.48",
            "484.38"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Eden sold a book to Camilo at a price of 441 after giving 43 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "773.68",
        "options": [
            "328.12",
            "308.39",
            "362.96",
            "773.68",
            "333.46"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Wade sold a book to Immanuel at a price of 885 after giving 1 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "893.94",
        "options": [
            "880.60",
            "876.24",
            "878.41",
            "893.94",
            "877.98"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Louis sold a book to Jerry at a price of 762 after giving 46 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1411.11",
        "options": [
            "619.51",
            "566.54",
            "521.92",
            "557.02",
            "1411.11"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ibrahim sold a book to Hassan at a price of 575 after giving 50 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1150.00",
        "options": [
            "410.71",
            "460.00",
            "418.18",
            "383.33",
            "1150.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Otto sold a book to Terrance at a price of 217 after giving 53 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "461.70",
        "options": [
            "461.70",
            "141.83",
            "152.39",
            "171.54",
            "155.28"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "George sold a book to Kase at a price of 202 after giving 7 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "217.20",
        "options": [
            "191.29",
            "191.92",
            "188.79",
            "217.20",
            "195.17"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Landon sold a book to Gary at a price of 600 after giving 72 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "2142.86",
        "options": [
            "2142.86",
            "441.18",
            "348.84",
            "389.61",
            "380.71"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Paxton sold a book to Rogelio at a price of 386 after giving 22 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "494.87",
        "options": [
            "494.87",
            "347.75",
            "328.23",
            "316.39",
            "331.33"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Anderson sold a book to Julien at a price of 969 after giving 49 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1900.00",
        "options": [
            "650.34",
            "708.59",
            "696.12",
            "1900.00",
            "778.31"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jayce sold a book to Alec at a price of 644 after giving 2 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "657.14",
        "options": [
            "631.37",
            "634.48",
            "657.14",
            "633.86",
            "637.62"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Leland sold a book to Terrance at a price of 716 after giving 36 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1118.75",
        "options": [
            "606.78",
            "526.47",
            "563.78",
            "1118.75",
            "555.90"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Damon sold a book to Louie at a price of 460 after giving 44 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "821.43",
        "options": [
            "340.24",
            "345.86",
            "377.05",
            "821.43",
            "319.44"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Kade sold a book to Jaziel at a price of 372 after giving 45 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "676.36",
        "options": [
            "303.67",
            "278.13",
            "256.55",
            "273.53",
            "676.36"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Eden sold a book to Nathanael at a price of 267 after giving 68 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "834.38",
        "options": [
            "172.93",
            "834.38",
            "158.93",
            "176.82",
            "199.25"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Keegan sold a book to Landry at a price of 678 after giving 1 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "684.85",
        "options": [
            "672.95",
            "674.63",
            "672.62",
            "684.85",
            "671.29"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Caden sold a book to Johan at a price of 567 after giving 6 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "603.19",
        "options": [
            "534.91",
            "542.58",
            "541.03",
            "603.19",
            "550.49"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Waylon sold a book to Tristian at a price of 912 after giving 22 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1169.23",
        "options": [
            "1169.23",
            "775.51",
            "747.54",
            "821.62",
            "782.83"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jasper sold a book to Jad at a price of 752 after giving 47 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1418.87",
        "options": [
            "511.56",
            "1418.87",
            "556.01",
            "546.51",
            "608.91"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Eric sold a book to Alfonso at a price of 264 after giving 13 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "303.45",
        "options": [
            "239.13",
            "247.89",
            "233.63",
            "303.45",
            "240.55"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Mohamed sold a book to Alfonso at a price of 217 after giving 34 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "328.79",
        "options": [
            "170.60",
            "328.79",
            "161.94",
            "185.47",
            "172.91"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Russell sold a book to Deangelo at a price of 343 after giving 51 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "700.00",
        "options": [
            "273.31",
            "227.15",
            "243.61",
            "700.00",
            "248.10"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Memphis sold a book to Marcel at a price of 155 after giving 8 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "168.48",
        "options": [
            "149.04",
            "146.23",
            "168.48",
            "145.68",
            "143.52"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ronan sold a book to Jerome at a price of 879 after giving 27 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1204.11",
        "options": [
            "730.98",
            "692.13",
            "722.86",
            "774.45",
            "1204.11"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Marshall sold a book to Kyng at a price of 605 after giving 73 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "2240.74",
        "options": [
            "381.94",
            "390.95",
            "443.22",
            "2240.74",
            "349.71"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Reid sold a book to Jabari at a price of 690 after giving 37 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1095.24",
        "options": [
            "532.41",
            "582.28",
            "503.65",
            "1095.24",
            "540.12"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ruben sold a book to Noe at a price of 748 after giving 40 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1246.67",
        "options": [
            "575.38",
            "1246.67",
            "623.33",
            "566.67",
            "534.29"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Julian sold a book to Jagger at a price of 851 after giving 40 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1418.33",
        "options": [
            "1418.33",
            "644.70",
            "709.17",
            "654.62",
            "607.86"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Dax sold a book to Canaan at a price of 627 after giving 65 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1791.43",
        "options": [
            "421.51",
            "1791.43",
            "473.21",
            "412.50",
            "380.00"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sullivan sold a book to Mack at a price of 847 after giving 48 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1628.85",
        "options": [
            "622.79",
            "611.99",
            "683.06",
            "1628.85",
            "572.30"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Luis sold a book to Brecken at a price of 942 after giving 62 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "2478.95",
        "options": [
            "2478.95",
            "719.08",
            "629.68",
            "643.00",
            "581.48"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Tate sold a book to Tommy at a price of 598 after giving 21 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "756.96",
        "options": [
            "511.99",
            "516.63",
            "541.18",
            "756.96",
            "494.21"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Remington sold a book to Ray at a price of 694 after giving 28 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "963.89",
        "options": [
            "542.19",
            "608.77",
            "573.55",
            "963.89",
            "566.99"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Cade sold a book to Rey at a price of 141 after giving 73 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "522.22",
        "options": [
            "81.50",
            "522.22",
            "103.30",
            "91.11",
            "89.02"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Memphis sold a book to Jericho at a price of 964 after giving 1 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "973.74",
        "options": [
            "954.46",
            "956.35",
            "956.82",
            "973.74",
            "959.20"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Colt sold a book to Ramon at a price of 450 after giving 35 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "692.31",
        "options": [
            "692.31",
            "382.98",
            "333.33",
            "351.56",
            "356.44"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Cayden sold a book to Jalen at a price of 504 after giving 3 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "519.59",
        "options": [
            "489.32",
            "496.55",
            "492.19",
            "519.59",
            "492.91"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Vincent sold a book to Grey at a price of 497 after giving 6 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "528.72",
        "options": [
            "468.87",
            "474.24",
            "528.72",
            "482.52",
            "475.60"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Logan sold a book to Blaze at a price of 344 after giving 62 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "905.26",
        "options": [
            "229.95",
            "234.81",
            "905.26",
            "212.35",
            "262.60"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Sage sold a book to Khalid at a price of 417 after giving 20 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "521.25",
        "options": [
            "359.48",
            "362.61",
            "379.09",
            "521.25",
            "347.50"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Malcolm sold a book to Noe at a price of 139 after giving 15 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "163.53",
        "options": [
            "129.30",
            "120.87",
            "124.94",
            "163.53",
            "124.11"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Malcolm sold a book to Danny at a price of 320 after giving 26 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "432.43",
        "options": [
            "432.43",
            "264.90",
            "267.78",
            "283.19",
            "253.97"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Kingston sold a book to Grey at a price of 704 after giving 42 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1213.79",
        "options": [
            "1213.79",
            "526.95",
            "495.77",
            "535.36",
            "581.82"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Nico sold a book to Baylor at a price of 175 after giving 41 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "296.61",
        "options": [
            "145.23",
            "133.84",
            "124.11",
            "131.78",
            "296.61"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Johnny sold a book to Harlan at a price of 535 after giving 67 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1621.21",
        "options": [
            "1621.21",
            "356.07",
            "400.75",
            "348.31",
            "320.36"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jayson sold a book to Kaiser at a price of 498 after giving 2 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "508.16",
        "options": [
            "488.24",
            "493.07",
            "508.16",
            "490.16",
            "490.64"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Thiago sold a book to Jimmy at a price of 973 after giving 47 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1835.85",
        "options": [
            "707.12",
            "1835.85",
            "787.85",
            "719.41",
            "661.90"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Elliott sold a book to Alfred at a price of 370 after giving 9 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "406.59",
        "options": [
            "339.45",
            "345.15",
            "406.59",
            "346.60",
            "354.07"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Oliver sold a book to Coen at a price of 481 after giving 76 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "2004.17",
        "options": [
            "273.30",
            "299.13",
            "306.37",
            "2004.17",
            "348.55"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Lawson sold a book to Ray at a price of 652 after giving 53 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1387.23",
        "options": [
            "515.42",
            "1387.23",
            "426.14",
            "457.87",
            "466.55"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alejandro sold a book to Kyng at a price of 502 after giving 27 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "687.67",
        "options": [
            "395.28",
            "417.46",
            "442.29",
            "412.83",
            "687.67"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Nico sold a book to Kamdyn at a price of 359 after giving 11 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "403.37",
        "options": [
            "403.37",
            "340.28",
            "323.42",
            "329.96",
            "331.64"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Edwin sold a book to Houston at a price of 404 after giving 56 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "918.18",
        "options": [
            "279.01",
            "284.51",
            "918.18",
            "315.62",
            "258.97"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Andy sold a book to Callan at a price of 241 after giving 15 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "283.53",
        "options": [
            "224.19",
            "215.18",
            "283.53",
            "209.57",
            "216.63"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Adrian sold a book to Ahmed at a price of 293 after giving 48 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "563.46",
        "options": [
            "563.46",
            "236.29",
            "197.97",
            "211.71",
            "215.44"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Fabian sold a book to Kenzo at a price of 399 after giving 36 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "623.44",
        "options": [
            "623.44",
            "338.14",
            "309.78",
            "314.17",
            "293.38"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Emanuel sold a book to Lian at a price of 707 after giving 42 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1218.97",
        "options": [
            "537.64",
            "497.89",
            "584.30",
            "529.19",
            "1218.97"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Zander sold a book to Harley at a price of 297 after giving 46 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "550.00",
        "options": [
            "241.46",
            "217.11",
            "550.00",
            "203.42",
            "220.82"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Owen sold a book to Jermaine at a price of 452 after giving 7 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "486.02",
        "options": [
            "422.43",
            "436.71",
            "428.03",
            "429.45",
            "486.02"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Milan sold a book to Gus at a price of 312 after giving 79 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1485.71",
        "options": [
            "195.92",
            "223.66",
            "1485.71",
            "191.18",
            "174.30"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Russell sold a book to Colson at a price of 241 after giving 18 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "293.90",
        "options": [
            "212.33",
            "221.10",
            "210.66",
            "293.90",
            "204.24"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Greyson sold a book to Dash at a price of 522 after giving 63 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1410.81",
        "options": [
            "1410.81",
            "396.96",
            "347.07",
            "354.50",
            "320.25"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Zion sold a book to Saul at a price of 755 after giving 48 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1451.92",
        "options": [
            "1451.92",
            "510.14",
            "545.52",
            "555.15",
            "608.87"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Gregory sold a book to Thatcher at a price of 604 after giving 3 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "622.68",
        "options": [
            "589.84",
            "590.71",
            "586.41",
            "622.68",
            "595.07"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Bowen sold a book to Bo at a price of 570 after giving 66 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1676.47",
        "options": [
            "428.57",
            "373.04",
            "343.37",
            "1676.47",
            "381.27"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Kingston sold a book to Zavier at a price of 166 after giving 22 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "212.82",
        "options": [
            "141.16",
            "136.07",
            "142.49",
            "149.55",
            "212.82"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Brantley sold a book to Julio at a price of 429 after giving 23 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "557.14",
        "options": [
            "557.14",
            "362.33",
            "365.88",
            "348.78",
            "384.75"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Alexander sold a book to Huxley at a price of 973 after giving 31 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1410.14",
        "options": [
            "789.45",
            "742.75",
            "842.42",
            "779.65",
            "1410.14"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Lorenzo sold a book to Anakin at a price of 611 after giving 17 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "736.14",
        "options": [
            "541.91",
            "537.85",
            "522.22",
            "563.13",
            "736.14"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Jasper sold a book to Chris at a price of 919 after giving 9 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "1009.89",
        "options": [
            "860.89",
            "843.12",
            "857.28",
            "1009.89",
            "879.43"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Colton sold a book to Kannon at a price of 866 after giving 66 pecent discount. What is the original price of the book?",
        "answer": "2547.06",
        "options": [
            "521.69",
            "579.26",
            "2547.06",
            "651.13",
            "566.75"
        ]
    }
]